Two... two, three...
ANNOUNCER:
It's the Futurama
Holiday Spectacular,
brought to you by...
Ah, the Xmas season.
Who wants a delicious
unshelled nut?
Ooh, I'll have one!
(loud crack)
Mmm! Mmm!
It's nut so good!
(groans quietly)
What's wrong, Fry?
Are you regretting
another wasted year?
I don't know.
Something about Xmas
just doesn't feel
like Christmas.
(alarm blaring)
Santa's coming!
Initiate defenses!
(rattling, clanking, thudding)
God rest ye
merry gentlemen...
in peace.
Can someone please explain
how you celebrate
this crazy holiday?
Preferably in song?
(others gasp)
It's the violent-est
season of the year
And Krinklebot has
come dispensing mugs
Of Xmas fear
Sugarplummy visions
Will be dancing in your head
When I cane you
from the comfort
Of my sled
Ow!
On Xmas Eve,
we don our gay apparel
Kevlar vests
Asbestos stockings
and a barrel
And if grandma's
Xmas fruitcake
Finally reaches
critical mass
It can be re-gifted
Straight to Santa's ass
But the ornamental armaments
Are merely superficial
The tinsel and the trappings
are just icing on the missile
The one thing that you need
To make your Xmas day
splendiferous
Is a pine tree
A pine tree
that's coniferous
We have to have a pine tree
that's coniferous!
You're welcome!
You know, Santa may
have killed Scruffy,
but he makes
a good point.
What we need is
an old-fashioned pine tree!
Cram it, Virginia!
Pine trees have been extinct
for over 800 years.
LEELA:
Professor,
maybe there's some way
to bring the pine trees
back to life.
Like we did with
the barking snakes.
(barking)
Pine trees aren't
barking snakes!
They won't just turn up
in a salad at Olive Garden.
But there is one hope,
and, as usual, it's Norwegian.
(whirring)
PASSENGERS:
Ooh! Whoa! Oh! Whoa...!
Behold!
The Svalbard Global Seed Vault!
Since 2008, the vault
has preserved seeds
of every known plant species,
in case of extinction.
And I brought a few
seeds of my own.
(snakes barking)
Halt! Wh-What's your business
pokey-pokin' about
de seed vault, uh,
guardian of mankind's precious
botanical heritage dere?
We just want to come in
and rummage about a bit.
Oh. So... okay.
Yo, Abba, what's
that next-door?
(wind rushing)
GUARD: Oh, dat's de germ
warfare repository.
LEELA:
It's so close.
Is there any chance
of cross-contamination?
No.
Now, your pine trees
were all chopped down
to make emergency
toilet paper
during the 50-Year Squirts.
Lucky de seeds have
been preserved here
in de vault dere.
What's that
splork on them?
It's not germs, is it?
No.
Now, that's a tree
worth chopping down.
Indeed!
It's a loverly tree!
'Twill truly be
my finest Xmas ev...
Oh!
(tires screech)
Arooo!
That's what my
poll numbers need--
happy voters enjoying
some holiday cheer.
As your vice president,
I order you to steal that tree.
(cheering)
NIXON:
My fellow Earthicans,
welcome to the annual
White House Xmas tree lighting,
brought to you by...
Gunderson's Nuts!
(electricity crackles)
(cheering)
(cracking, creaking, rumbling)
(people gasping)
Oh, no!
Could the seed have
been contaminated
by a virus from
the germ vault?
Uh, yeah, I suppose.
Wait! This could
be a good thing.
That weaponized virus
made the sickly little tree
grow big and strong!
(rumbling continues,
pine cones whizzing)
(people gasping, yelling)
(yells, whimpers)
(rumbling stops)
(wood crackling)
Wait-- this could be
a good thing.
Reforestation has begun.
(rumbling)
Aw, geez with this, hah?
(rumbling continues)
(gasping, panicked shouts)
(clattering, glass shattering)
Arguably, this could be
a good thing.
The planet has returned
to its primeval state!
Earth is just the way it was
before the white man came!
(device beeping)
Good news!
All these pine trees
are fighting global warming
by producing oxygen!
Happy now, Gore?
Yeah. But I'd be happier
if I had a set of lungs.
(device beeping)
Hey, wait a second!
Oxygen levels are
rising too rapidly!
Ten percent...
20 percent...
60 percent!
As long as it
doesn't hit 70.
80 percent!
You know, I don't recall
having done anything
for a while,
but I still feel
I deserve a smoke.
Hey, cool.
The air's on fire.
(deep whoosh)
(explosions)
Ho, ho, ho!
Everyone's dead!
Stay tuned for another tale
of holiday hilarity.
w back to the...
Okay, crew, Xmas
break is over.
It's time to destroy
these gifts
we forgot to deliver.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
How come we get off
for every dumb human holiday
but not for robot holidays?!
Oh, Lord, not Robanukah.
I'm talking about Robanukah!
The holiest six and a half weeks
in the robot calendar.
Pfft! That's just a fake holiday
you make up every year
to get out of work.
Yeah! If it's real,
how come there's no song
that explains how
to celebrate it?
Because there is!
Hit it!
Hit what?
I placed instruments
under your seats.
Play 'em or I'll break 'em
over your heads!
(lively intro plays)
Robanukah may sound
as if it's Jewish
But its
ancient-sounding customs
Are exceptionally new-ish
So take a hearty swallow
from your robo-kiddush cup
Which will give me time
to quickly make them up
(belches)
Do you spin a dreidel
Made from clay?
Mine is called a "droidl," and
it's rigged to make you pay
Do you eat these yummy
tin-wrapped chocolate coins?
Better! We got fembots with
illegal five-speed groins!
Shalom,
Ruth and Esther!
Why with the music
so loud?
Would it kill them to turn up
the heat a little in here?
But by far the most
important thing is oil
To keep the lamplight burning
or to help the latkes broil?
No, we pour the holy lubricant
out from the sacred vessel
Into this blessed pit
so they can wrestle
The extra made-up touch that
makes Robanukah so special
Is the oil in which
the nasty fembots wrestle!
We shall now begin
the traditional oil wrestling.
Will the referee bring out
the ceremonial cruse
of petroleum oil?
(chittering)
Thank you, Abraham.
Not in the hair, please.
I just had it did.
(oilcan splutters)
(hollow knocking)
Aw, no!
These broads are supposed to
wrestle for six and half weeks,
but there's only enough
petroleum oil
for four and a half weeks!
(dramatic sting)
We're still getting paid, right?
I told you, it's an audition!
Bender, four and a half weeks
of oil wrestling
sounds like plenty.
This isn't a lousy
reformed Robanukah!
We need more petroleum oil!
(ship whooshing)
(quiet, metallic creak)
I got me some whale oil,
some squirrel oil...
Not kosher!
It has to be
petroleum oil!
Do you not give a damn
about the hallowed
traditions of Robanukah?!
I reckon I do not.
Anyways, Earth done
run out of petroleum oil.
(all gasp)
I tried to warn you.
One unit of free,
limitless solar power, please?
(deep whirring)
(beeping)
That'll be...
I don't know, ten bucks?
Um, can you make change
for a Nobel Prize?
Aw, man, can't we just
make more petroleum oil?
I'm afraid
not, son.
Petroleum only forms
when organic matter
is subjected to
intense pressure
for hundreds of
millions of years.
(spluttering)
I can't wait that long!
I've got A.D.D.!
This is so unfair!
I don't wrestle
dry, Bender.
I went to Vassar.
Professor, I want you
to look these poor
floozies in the eye
and tell them they're
oil-wrestling days are over.
(sighs) Oh... I suppose there
could be a minute quantity
of petroleum left,
but it would be insanely deep
within the Earth, at pressures
so dangerously high that--
(horn honks twice)
Let's go already!
(clanking, whirring)
(engine whooshing)
(rumbling)
Setting Bachman turners
to overdrive.
We're getting pretty deep.
(gasps)
Look-- more coffins.
(crunching)
(clattering)
AMY: Oh, no!
We tunneled into a tunnel.
What's that loud boring sound
you'll hear when I stop talking?
(Professor gasps)
It's an albino humping worm!
Why do they
call it that?
Because it doesn't
have any pigment.
What's our
depth, Captain?
40 kilometers... 50...
There must be petroleum
oil down here somewhere.
Go deeper, deeper!
No, Bender.
The ship can't withstand
this much pressure.
Sometimes it falls apart
just sitting in the hangar.
Professor, I've never asked
for anything before.
But seeing those fembots
glistening with oil
means more to me
than life itself.
Oh...
Call me an old fool,
but I believe the Lord
is speaking through you.
Brace yourselves,
everyone!
100 kilometers!
Two hundred!
I hate to complain
about the heat,
but the air
conditioner's on fire.
My ice cream manwich!
What the hell
are we doing?
We're all gonna die
so this junkyard golem
can celebrate Robanukah!
You vile racist.
Haven't my people
suffered enough?
Now keep drilling
for that petroleum oil,
you selfish cowards!
Although, then again,
I guess any kind
of oil would be just as...
(metal crunching,
glass shattering)
Not my fault.
I am so great
Bender is great
Bender, Bender,
Bender, Ben--
Man, where did the time go?
Hey, you guys wanna--
Oh, right.
(gasps)
They turned
into petroleum oil.
I thought they were selfish,
yet in the end,
it turns out it was I
who thought
they were selfish.
(whirring)
Hey, ladies.
I found some--
What the...
There was only
enough petroleum
for four and a half
weeks of oil wrestling,
but it lasted
500 million years!
It's a miracle!
BENDER:
Happy Robanukah, everyone.
Coming up next, more thoughtful
interfaith hilarity.
(doorbell rings)
(all greeting)
What's up?
LaBarbara, Hermes,
happy Kwanzaa!
We brought
a chocolate cake,
but now I'm worried that might
be offensive in some way.
Just sit down.
(doorbell rings)
Happy Kwanzaa,
brothermen and sistermen!
Well, look at the cat
the cat dragged in!
Kwanzaa tradition
encourages educational gifts.
So I brought Dwight
my book on Mathketball.
DWIGHT:
Whoa!
Let me see that.
I'll sign it
for you later.
Man, it's a cold
one out there.
Barbados Slim?
Come in, Barbados.
Look at yourself,
all throbbing and shirtless
for the holiday.
I hope you're ready
to celebrate.
All night long, woman.
(clinking)
I'm glad you all could
be here with my family.
Kwanzaa traditions
are quite ancient,
dating back
over one thousand years.
Whoa.
If only someone
could tell us more
about these traditions.
Oh, yeah!
Hey, Kool-Aid's here.
No, child,
that's not a made-up character,
It's Kwanzaabot!
And I'm-a tell y'all
how we celebrate Kwanzaa.
Zoidberg,
lay down a beat.
How 'bout I
just lay down?
(playing upbeat intro)
There's seven basic principles
that go to make up Kwanzaa
So sit your asses down
And have some knowledge
dropped upons ya
Kujichagulia
And Umoja
And the rest
ALL:
Now we get it.
Sit back down,
there's gonna be a test
My favorite's Ujamaa
Cooperative
economics.
Yo, Boondocks,
I'm talkin' here
Put away the comics
(trilling)
Ku'umba is another one
It stands for creativity
Like the
ever-changing nature
Of my sexual
proclivities
I think there's one called
Nia
But I don't speak Swahili
Something about a pine tree
and an oil-wrestling dealie?
That's from Xmas and Robanukah
you plagiarizing lout.
Yeah, I'm kinda
losing interest here
I best be rollin' out
But before I go,
the most important thing
What's that,
black Santa?
You need seven
Kwanzaa candles
That you light up
every night
But they best be
made of beeswax
Or y'all might
as well be white
ALL:
They must be made of beeswax,
or we might as well be white.
Well, we got
no beeswax candles,
but these scented regular wax
candles will do just fine.
Girl, those stank sticks are for
single women who take baths!
If your Kwanzaa candles
ain't 100% beeswax,
you bring shame
on your people.
Well, now that won't do.
Husband, show
a little ku'umba
and fetch some beeswax
before Kwanzaa ends.
Sweet candelabra of
La Habra, LaBarbara!
Isn't this the last
night of Kwanzaa?
Who the hell knows?
(crickets chirping)
Finally, a bee farm that's
open late on Kwanzaa!
Madam, I need beeswax.
You sure you don't need
a little honey, handsome?
Maybe a taste of sweet nectar
straight from the hive?
(all gagging)
I just need some beeswax
to make Kwanzaa candles.
Well, that's too darn bad.
There ain't no beeswax
in the whole world!
Oh, no! This could be the
year without a Kwanzaa,
like every year
before 1966.
The bees are
acting all crazy,
like they've been drinking
Tang and cough syrup,
or, as I call it,
my Friday night.
(laughing hoarsely)
(coughing)
My God.
It's colony
collapse syndrome!
The bees are swarming
with parasites!
They're all dying.
Yeah, but
what a way to go.
Die young,
leave a pretty corpse,
that's what I say.
You should say
something else.
Wait-- I know where
we can get beeswax.
From those giant space bees
who nearly killed us,
and we swore we'd
never go back there!
Let's go back there!
(engine whooshing)
To communicate
with the bees,
we'll need to use these
transbumbleators.
Bender, say something
in bee talk.
(buzzing)
I'm sorry, Bender.
What do you want me
to put on the glass?
(buzzing)
Okay.
If we survive.
Something's wrong.
It's way too quiet.
Like the deadly Prius.
(buzzing approaches)
PROFESSOR:
Ah, here they come.
They're in attack formation!
They're going to kill us!
That was weird.
It's like the Jagermeister
Air Show all over again.
According to Google Hive,
we're at the exact center
of the honeycomb.
Ooh, and there's a Jamba Juice
point two miles that way!
Does that thing tell you
where the Queen Bee is?
The big, fat, ugly,
compound-eyed, hairy-thorax--
(grunts)
Don't be applying your
Euro-centric standards
of beauty to me, fool.
(gasps)
What's with the kamikaz-bees?
Man, my hive's been
going buck wild
since these blood ganking
butt crabs moved in.
(all groan and gag)
Been there.
Done that.
These bees are infected,
just like
the ones on Earth.
Brothasuckin' parasites
gone and disrupted
our hivemind.
Now instead of
working in harmony,
my bees just talk
smack to each other.
Are y'all black
with yellow stripes,
or ya yellow
with black stripes?
Yellow with black stripes, man.
Why don't you
just move along?
Let me ask you something.
You sting my wife?
What kinda buzzin'
question is that?
Where do you get the wings
big enough to ask me that?
(buzzing)
Okay, gang.
We have plenty
of beeswax.
Let's get back
to the ship.
No. We are not
going anywhere.
I can't abide all
this bee-on-bee conflict.
It's time to African-Americanize
these honeybees!
(buzzing)
Listen up, bees!
It's Kwanzaa,
a time of Umoja.
It means unity.
You have to learn
to work together again!
The crazy tablecloth man
is right.
It's time to set aside
our differences.
Black stripe,
yellow stripe...
at the end of the day,
we're just a couple dern
talkin' space bees.
Hey, forget
about it.
me here and
give me a sting.
Look! The spirit of Kwanzaa
is killing the parasites.
(all cheering)
Yech! But yay!
Thank you, my
human brother.
Your message of unity
has touched our souls.
We are once again
of a single hivemind.
(all muttering anxiously)
(crashing)
KWANZAABOT:
Oh, yeah.
Hooray! Kwanzaabot's
here to save--
(blow thuds)
Oh, they killed him.
(buzzing)
Joyous Kwanzaa, everybody.
(applause)
(chuckling)
Don't worry.
The Futurama crew will
be back next year
with all new episodes
featuring Bender, Leela,
and me, Al Gore, as
Captain Lance Starman.
And from all of us here
at Gunderson's Nuts,
happy holidays!
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
www.tvsubtitles.net