♪ Two... two, three... ♪
sync by honeybunny, corrected by gloriabg
www.addic7ed.com
Good news, everyone!
We've been hired to make
our 100th delivery.
One hundred!
That's almost ten per year.
This calls for a party, baby.
I'm ordering a hundred kegs,
a hundred hookers
and a hundred Elvis
impersonators who aren't above
a little hooking,
should the occasion arise.
Be very gentle, folks.
This is the soufflé you're
delivering to Mrs. Astor.
Oh, my God, it's Elzar!
Hi, Eelzar! Ooh, great soufflé, Elzar!
Whatever you do, don't drop it.
See, Mrs. Astor takes
nitroglycerine for her heart,
and being a class act,
she prefers it in soufflé form.
Bam.
To prevent the soufflé from exploding,
Bender will carry it.
He's gyroscopically stable.
Look!
Mrs. Astor's mansion,
just across that rickety rope bridge.
Wow, it's ricketier than it looks.
You better try to jump it, Bender.
Okay, let me back up for a running start.
Here I go!
I shall inform Mrs. Astor
that the circus is in town.
Your soufflé, madam.
I shall take it here, under my fork.
Mmm.
Where's the exploding?
One does not explode in Mrs. Astor's face.
I couldn't eat another bite.
Hobbsy?
Well done, sir.
Have you a name?
Hubert Farnsworth, at your service.
A Farnsworth, you say?
Well, if I'm not mistaken,
the Farnsworths have been
in New New York for almost 200 years.
Yes, I have.
And I'm his uncle.
How charmingly unconventional.
I can eat a hot dog underwater.
Say, would you Farnsworths
care to be my guests tomorrow
at the Astor endowment fund-raiser?
All the best families will be there.
We can take them.
On April 10, 2912, my late husband and I
set off down fifth Avenue
aboard the Land Titanic,
the largest street-going vessel ever built.
Just four days into her maiden voyage,
as we approached 32nd street,
the land liner struck a mailbox
and went down.
2,000 souls were lost that day,
including my dear husband.
In loving memory, I established
the Mr. Astor endowment, which this year
supports the united
mutant scholarship fund.
Mutants? That's the kind of thing you are.
Shh. You know mutants aren't
allowed on the surface.
If anyone asks, say I'm an alien, remember?
Oh, right. You gonna finish that roll?
Shh.
Now, a short film
about those pitiable creatures
so in need of our charity.
Far beneath the everyday rumble
of limousines and poodle feet,
there toil a downtrodden people
even less well off
than the upper-middle class:
The noble sewer mutants.
For, you see, generations
of exposure to toxic sewage
mutated them into horrific monsters!
- Ooh!
- Shut up.
These industrious,
uh, "people," I guess,
maintain the various pipes
and poop chutes
that keep decent, above-ground
society functioning.
And where do these proud toileteers
learn their menial skills?
At brown university,
the nation's premiere
institution of lower learning.
So please, give generously,
knowing some poor helpless
mutant will thank you.
Not in person, thank God.
Well, that was disturbing.
Oh, I understand, dear.
They are hideous.
Look, I guess you mean well,
but isn't that university
just a tax-deductible
sewer-cleaning service?
My dear, that school is about
much more than sewer pipes.
- Really?
- It's also about keeping
those filthy things busy.
There are thousands of them
down there, breeding like rats.
My great Uncle once saw a rat.
If we don't keep them busy,
they'll start jabbering about
equal rights in their ill-bred manner.
Let's go.
If I say one more thing,
I might say it with my evening boot.
Well! Rarely have I never!
Please, don't blame Leela.
She's just a little, uh, ill-bred.
You know how mutants are.
Your companion is a mutant?
But if anyone asks, say she's an alien.
Help! Police!
You may have eluded the authorities,
but don't nothing get past Mrs. Astor.
What's going to happen to me?!
Permanent deportation, you mutant.
You going downtown, baby.
Way down.
Incoming!
Thanks, Colonel.
Just doing my job, ma'am.
Oh, mom, dad, I can't believe
I have to spend the rest
of my life in this hellhole.
I'm sorry.
It's okay, sweetie.
Now that you're here,
this hellhole feels more
like a nice, regular hole.
What do you say
we go get some sewer coffee,
sewer cake and safeway ice cream.
Well, the bottom's all
stocked with cheap stuff.
Who's in the mood to party?
Whoo!
Poor Leela.
I feel like I ruined her life.
You did ruin her life.
You might be right, Hermes.
I am right.
I almost feel like we should
do something to help her.
We should do something!
I don't care what you say, Hermes.
Let's go.
Oh, mighty Mayor,
we're here about Turanga Leela.
You mean Leela?
Right.
I mean, sure she's a mutant,
we've known that for years,
but we kept it secret 'cause
she's a fine, upstanding...
Wait. You knowingly
attempted to harbor a mutant?!
We did harbor a mutant!
Uh-oh.
Look, Leela, there's old filthful.
And there's the West Side pipeway.
If those guys slack off for even a second,
it could explode.
Hey, guys!
This is my daughter Leela.
- Yeah. Oh, hey.
- How you doing, Leela?
Well, they're with the chuds now.
These conditions are deplorable.
I swear, I hate every single person
on the surface
for making us live like this.
Leela.
What are you doing here?
We were sentenced to
two weeks in the sewer
for harboring a mutant.
Three dollars at the drug store.
I'm so sorry I ratted you out,
but, you know, after two weeks down here,
I'll truly understand the
plight of the mutant people.
How dare you.
You want to understand something?
Look at that lake.
One dip in that toxic muck
and your DNA will be permanently mutated.
You'll grow a camel hump
or a Zoidberg face.
You want to know what
it's like to be a mutant?
Jump in and go for a swim.
Um, I would, but I j... I ate
a bunch of potato salad, so...
Yeah, that's what I thought.
You are all surface.
Fry, Hermes.
Where my humans at?
Ah, who cares?
It is on.
Hey, hey, hey.
I trust the orgy pit has
been scraped and buttered?
You know it,
and there's mini-quiches, too.
It's getting cold and smelly.
My odor eaters are going critical.
Maybe we could plotz in that giant cockle.
Shmeepers, it's the Land Titanic,
the biggest and onlyest
land boat ever constructed.
This was one hell of a bus.
Well, everyone debone a
bunk and get some shut-eye.
Zoidberg, show some respect.
This is a sacred shrine
to the thousands who lost their lives.
Hey, I found a safe.
It's coming loose.
Hand me some more of that cruise director.
The original passenger manifest.
Spreadsheets were so elegant back then.
Just one other item.
It's jewelry... jewelry!
It's jewelry, people!
It's a priceless quantum-force gemerald.
What's that enscribbled on it?
"My dear Mrs. Astor.
My love for you is
as unsinkable as this land ship
and as brilliant as this stone.
Dictated but not read, Mr. Astor."
Aw.
That's so valuable.
I'll never have love like that.
Leela hates me now.
Did you guys know
I have a crush on Leela?
What's the matter, Leela?
You've hardly touched
your toilet clams.
Maybe I was too harsh on Fry.
He didn't ruin my life on purpose.
Things will work out, honey.
Now, here.
Have some more
of what looks like lemonade.
Bender, I've been to wang-dang-doodles
all up and down the galaxy,
but this is the dangest
wang I ever doodled.
Oh, yeah!
Come on, baby, let's do it!
Shake your booty, baby.
Come on! Yeah!
Get out! Get out!
It's not fun anymore!
I want to be alone!
Alone with me?
I said scram, Grapey!
Fry? What are you doing?!
You were right.
I don't know what it's
like to be a mutant.
But I want to know.
Wait. I never meant for you to...
Oh, no!
Fry! Fry!
No!
Any effect?
Sorry.
I tried to scream, but I barfed.
I think I'm knowing
what it's like to be a mutant.
So what's with all the screaming?
Hey, guys.
Fry, this is the stupidest,
sweetest thing you've ever done.
And you know, maybe now, together,
we can be an inspiration to other mutants.
I hope so, Leela.
Aw. Come here.
Let me give you a kiss.
Uh... hug.
Handshake.
I'll text you.
My fellow mutants,
until recently, I dwelt on the surface,
where a man can gaze up
at the sky in wonder
without a wet clump falling in his mouth.
We can do that, too...
Who's ready to fight for equality?
The devolution
revolution has begun!
Beautiful mutants, please welcome... Devo!
Hello, sewer city.
As longtime mutants ourselves,
we support your righteous struggle,
and we'll do anything we can for you!
Play "Whip it!"
No. Play the other one.
Now that we've got their attention,
it's time to hit them where they sit
by bending the West Side pipeway
to return all sewage to the surface.
But who could possibly
bend such a huge pipe?
So lonely.
Poor, sad Bender.
Hey, buddy.
Ah, what the heck?
Mmm.
Crowd
Bend it! Bend it!
What goes down must back up.
Yucks.
I picked the wrong day
to wear my new crocses.
Prepare to storm the surface
for the million mutant march!
Move out, Fry.
We need our most disgusting
mutant leading the charge.
I'll meet you up there.
I need to check out something first.
Okay. Vyolet, you're up front.
Hey!
Mayor, this sewer debacle
has gone on long enough.
As your largest campaign contributor,
I demand action!
Very well.
$80 worth of action it is.
Voilá.
We simply pump the fruits of our excretion
into Madison Cube Garden.
Well, it seems everything is under...
- Two!
- Four!
Six eyes!
The mutant people will arise!
The segregation
of the mutant people ends today.
We demand equal rights,
equal access to the surface
and the blood of your first-born children.
That's so we have something
to give up in the negotiations.
I've never been so moved,
and I see no reason to begin now.
Hobbsy, flush those creatures
back down the hole they crawled out of.
Madam's sewage-seeking missile.
Let my people stay!
Neat.
Mrs. Astor, deep in the sewer,
we discovered the wreck
of the Land Titanic,
on which your husband land-drowned.
Inside was something
that might interest you.
The gemerald ring
my husband was to give me
in lieu of children.
Ah, so what?
I have a chandelier in
my car made of those.
Not the gem.
This passenger manifest.
It turns out there were
mutants on that ship
working below deck in the sewage galley.
Ma'am?
I was just a young girl.
Drain angels, they called us.
When the ship started going down,
my mother grabbed me and made
for the nearest life car.
But the places were all taken
by surface passengers.
As my mother held me tight,
I suddenly felt the gentle tap
of a cane on my face.
I turned to see
the kindly smile of Mr. Astor.
Thanks to your husband's humanity,
I lived to raise my own daughter,
and she a daughter in turn.
Mom, why have I never heard this?
My mother's nuts.
I beg you, Mrs. Astor,
if you truly want to honor
your husband's memory,
treat these people
with dignity, as he did.
Oh. He was a dear man... Mr. Astor.
Randall, let's grant
these mutants their freedom.
Okay.
Are we not men now?
I'm 40% potato, but close enough.
Thank you, Fry.
I think maybe I can stomach that kiss now.
What the...?
Good afternoon. I am Mr. Astor.
I did not perish that fateful day,
but rather plummeted into the toxic lake,
where I mutated and lived in solitude
until this ruddy lad here
stepped into my mouth and lodged there.
Mister...?
Is that really you?
Hooray!
A happy ending for the rich people!
Mom, dad, grandma, this is where I work.
Oh.
Was there a fire?
So, Bender, how was the party?
Only the greatest party ever!
I don't need to have
another party in my whole life.
I am partied out!
Dang. Sorry we missed it.
We could have another one...
If it would make you guys feel better.
Really? Nah, that's not necess...
Hit it, Bender!
sync by honeybunny, corrected by gloriabg
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net