Sync by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
(applause and cheering)
(dramatic music plays)
Silence, puny audience!
And welcome to...
Who Dares To Be A Millionaire?
Tremble before Morbo's mighty
likeability,
as I chit-chat with our first
contestant, Philip J. Fry.
(applause and cheering)
(dramatic music plays)
(raucous shouting)
Give him hell, Morbo!
Prepare for pleasantries!
So, Fry, what do you do
for a living?
Me? Um... can I phone a friend?
Chit-chat achieved!
(dramatic music plays)
Are you ready to play?
I didn't come to play;
I came to win.
Now let's play.
For one dollar...
Is it...
B: Nail!
Final answer!
(buzzer)
(dramatic music plays)
HERMES:
Sweet dodo of Lesotho!
Don't you ever stop to think
before you speak?
I never stop to think about it.
Aw, leave Fry alone.
His intelligence is just a
little... differenty.
(imitates Redd Foxx):
You a big dummy!
Hey, I'm beginning to think
you guys don't think
I'm very smart.
You can barely remember
your own name, Einstein.
Einstein is a hard name
to remember.
(groans) Ow!
Smeesh, Professor.
Don't have a shmaneurysm.
Fry's your distant relative.
Not distant enough.
I'll be a monkey's uncle
if I'm this monkey's nephew.
(sobs): But you're
my only family.
Who will hug me if I achieve
something?
Oh, perhaps I've been too harsh.
Come, lad, take my hand
and I'll explain
why I find you so repugnant.
All my life, I've been
inspired by great minds...
Euclid, Copernicus, Braino...
And my personal role model,
Leonardo Da Vinci.
What turned them to stone?
(groans): Oh...
Da Vinci was history's greatest
artist and inventor.
(beep)
(rumbling)
Voilà!
He invented flying machines,
war engines, submarines...
Uh-oh. Nibbler
died in the wall.
That's not Nibbler. That's my
most precious possession.
Leonardo's beard!
I paid a fortune for it at an
auction of historic body parts.
Oh, I suppose if I have an
Achilles' heel,
it's because I bought it at
that same auction.
Indeed so.
Most indeededly.
Careful with that, you fool!
(sneezes)
No!
But possibly yes.
What is it Professor?
Oh, my!
It's Da Vinci's fabled
lost invention.
Even the scholars who wrote
of this device had no
idea what it was for.
And now, at last, neither do I!
Maybe we can figure it out.
We? (laughs)
Well, I may not have
brain smarts,
but at least I have
street smarts.
(horn honks) (thud)
I was in the hospital two weeks.
No one visited me.
Quiet, you!
I'm trying to deduce
the function
of Da Vinci's lost invention.
Not even a card.
He might have hidden a clue
in one of his other works.
Ergo, I sent Bender out for
a copy of The Last Supper.
BENDER:
I'm back!
Everybody at Kinko's
was an idiot,
so I just brought the original.
(grunts)
Jesus Christ...
and his 12 Apostles.
That's odd.
This hand here doesn't
belong to anybody.
And it's pointing a knife
at James the Lesser.
That's the great thing about
that hand.
And what about these
funky table legs?
It's like they're from some
other, funkier painting.
Maybe Da Vinci painted over
something else.
It's called a pentimento.
That's true, Dr. Zoidberg.
Eh... how did you know that?
My doctorate is in art history.
Let's see what's under
The Last Supper.
(zapping)
HERMES:
Wait a second!
I'm not big-boned;
I'm just fat.
My God! Look!
(gasping)
My God! I'm looking!
FRY:
My God! Saint James was a robot!
My God! Da Vinci left his legs
unpainted as a clue.
My God! This is the greatest
mystery of all time.
We must fly to Rome
and exhume the body
of Saint James.
Didn't we used to be
a delivery company?
To the ship.
(Gregorian monks chanting
Futurama theme)
(chanting stops)
(rat squeaking)
PST! Leela, wanna join
the mile-deep club?
Sure, why not?
(gasps)
No time!
I've found a clue
that could unlock all
the secrets of history.
(groans)
Look at these Roman numerals.
Roman numerals?!
I've got it!
We're in Rome.
Don't be stupid.
It's a long-lost
mathematical code.
I'll need to consult
these ancient writings.
(blowing)
(mutters)
Some preposterous hogwash...
About the Fibonacci sequence...
Aha! The markings indicate how
many paces we need to take.
One...
Okay, we're there.
Brothers and sisters,
let us pry.
It's true!
Saint James really was a robot.
I bet he's up in
Robot Heaven right now.
So he won't miss his eyes.
(grunts) (rat squeaks)
(gasping)
My God! Robot Saint James
is a zombie.
Nay, I am not Saint James.
Enough of your lies,
Saint James.
We saw you in The Last Supper.
The great man Leonardo built me
as an artist's model.
When I took repose in this
coffin, I carefully tossed
the real Saint James
in yonder heap.
(Bender chuckles)
I'm sure you have many
questions.
Come, there is a chamber
where I used to speak
with Pope John the Pient.
Ah, I told him I'd be
back in five minutes.
Ah, well, he'll make
a nice heap.
(clattering)
I am Animatronio, guardian of
Da Vinci's great secret.
He left my legs visible in
the painting as a clue,
then dispatched me hither to
await his shadow society
of intellectuals.
Hi, Animatronio.
You personally knew Da Vinci?
(girlish squeal) Was he nice?
How did his hair smell?
And on a personal note, what is
the function of this device?
Halt! You know not the function
of the machina magnifica?
Then thou art not
members of the shadow society!
The what, now?
Not one more word
shall I breathe.
Not even about
the great fountain
where thou mayest find the...
Wait...
Thou didst not know about
the fountain, didst thou?
Curses!
I must be punished.
(yelling)
Quick, we must find out
what he knows,
before he
flays himself to death.
Where is the great fountain?
What makes it so great?
Why does a robot
need a codpiece?
Fie, thou fen-suckled
bumbailey!
Thou willst never pry
information
from these mechanical lips!
Just tell us, already.
Okay, the fountain
thou seekest is-is...
(gasps)
And so dies our hope of
solving this mystery.
Come on, gang.
Let's go home.
Wait! Let's not
give up so easily.
Animatronio mentioned
a fountain.
That's a statue of Neptune,
god of water.
The number of points on his
trident is three, or "trey."
The "U" in his name is written
like "V."
Trey... V...
Trey... Trevi!
It's the Trevi Fountain!
There can be no question!
But Professor...?
Wow, it hasn't changed
in a thousand years.
(growling) (camera snapping)
Okay, everyone,
into the fountain.
What are you, senile?
I'm not jumping in there.
Hey, look... coins.
(muffled shouting)
(grunting)
(growls)
(gun hammers cocking)
(gunshots)
(gurgling)
I got 48 cents.
(gasps) There's one more
nickel, and it's a big one!
(muffled gurgling)
(flushing)
Quickly, into the sewer hole.
Why?
(gasps)
(shouting)
(grunting)
What's this dump?
Professor:
My God!
It's the Pantheon!
LEELA:
This place is 3,000 years old.
What could possibly
be left to discover?
Maybe something
about ourselves, Leela.
Wait! What's under
that blanket?
My God!
Da Vinci's Vitruvian Man!
It's truly a masterpiece.
Note how the perspective lines
draw the eye right to his dong.
Say, what's this?
Anyone hear something?
It's a coin slot.
Bender, insert
that giant nickel.
Sure.
(laughing)
(clanking)
Aah!
Hush, Bender!
What's your game,
Vitruvian Man?
Ooh!
Professor: I withdraw the
question, Vitruvian Man.
Da Vinci's lost workshop.
At the risk of sounding stupid,
do these things actually work?
Of course not, stupid!
I mean... that flying machine's
as aerodynamic as a sofa!
How could it possibly get off
the ground?
In a way thou shalt
ne'er discover!
(all gasping)
Hi, Animatronio.
I feign death and stalk thee,
that I might preserve the
greatest of Leonardo's secrets.
Hee-yah!
All right, buddy,
we want secrets.
And they better be ancient!
Porco metallico!
Ne'er shall I reveal how these
wondrous machines fit together!
Professor:
They fit together?!
I said no such thing.
And then I died!
(raspy screech)
You're right, Professor.
This thing doesn't fly.
Don't sit in there, you idiot!
That's dangerous!
Heh-wha...?
(clicking, ratcheting)
(gasps)
No wonder this contraption
isn't aerodynamic!
It's not an aircraft,
it's a spacecraft!
Basta! As I live, thou shan't
discover the great secret!
FRY:
Bye, Animatronio!
(both grunt)
My God!
Why would Leonardo's machine
have brought us here?
Uh, I don't know.
I am Leonardo. guy.
(both gasp)
Welcome to Planet Vinci.
Professor:
My God!
FRY:
That's what I was gonna say!
Professor:
Leonardo!
You're alive?! Here?!
(sighs)
You've learned my great secret.
I was but a visitor to Earth.
In truth, I am what you call
"a space alien."
(gasps)
It's an honor to meet you,
Leonardo.
And might I say, you were great
in Titanic.
The Beach... eh.
That's Leonardo DiCaprio,
you blockhead!
(groans)
Heh.
Looks like eating rocks
wasn't as dumb as you said.
FRY: So what do people
do for fun here?
Do you enjoy partying
all night,
with plenty of ale
and lusty women?
I sure do!
Not us.
We spend our leisure time
in the mathematics museum.
Planet Vinci is basically
a single colossal university.
How's your football team?
Learned.
Ooh!
I'm going to check out
that math lecture.
All this knowledge is
giving me a raging "brainer."
Would, uh, you like to hear
the lecture, too, Fry?
No. It would just go in one ear
and our some other hole.
Come. Sit down.
Now, that I can do.
Ow!
I have a terrible secret
to confess, Mr. DiCaprio.
I'm not very smart.
I appreciate your candor.
I don't even know what
language you're speaking.
(sighs)
I, too, have a confession.
You see, here on Planet Vinci,
I am the stupidest person.
What?! Who'd possibly
think you're stupid?
Duh! I'm Leonardo!
I don't know the mass
of the Higgs boson.
Duh! I have
to draw in pencil,
'cause I don't know
how to use rendering software.
(couple laughing)
Stupid Biff!
Thinks he's so smart.
He looks stronger
than you, too.
I went to Earth because I could
no longer stand the ridicule.
But being surrounded
by even stupider people
was equally infuriating.
I can see myself
in your shiny button.
Inventing is what
makes me happy.
Or did, until I misplaced
the plans for my masterpiece.
You mean these?
(gasps)
The machina magnifica!
Oh! Infinite joy!
Fry, my friend, you have given
my life meaning again!
That calculus lecture
was harder than I expected.
We had to answer every question
in the form of an opera.
I have a lot of homework
for tomorrow,
if I don't want to be...
♪ embarrassed. ♪
(bright, lilting Renaissance
folk melody playing)
♪ ♪
(harsh buzz)
(class laughing)
(armpit squeaking)
(catcalls, booing)
Thank you. Thank you.
And if you like that,
you'll love our main event.
Ladies and gentlemen...
Leonardo DiCaprio!
(cheering)
I mean DaVinci!
(booing)
For centuries,
you've ridiculed me.
Especially you, Biff.
Nice hat!
AUDIENCE:
Ooh!
But, at long last, this
invention will show you.
'Twill show you all!
Behold, my unstoppable
doomsday machine!
And I helped!
Wait... you told me it was an
unstoppable ice cream machine.
Ice cream is just a
byproduct of the machine.
Its primary purpose it to
exterminate everyone
who ever made me feel inferior!
Ooh! I'm so scared!
Bring it on, dum-dum!
(mocking laughter)
Oh, yeah?
Let's see how hard
you're laughing
when my doomsday machine
chops off your face!
Leonardo, stop!
(audience gasps)
I want in on this!
Are you crazy, Professor?
I hate these nerds!
Just 'cause
I'm stupider than them,
they think they're
smarter than me.
Kill them all...
starting with the math teacher!
(screaming)
I knew this final invention
would be a humdinger.
Yes.
We three idiots will finally
have our revenge.
I don't think so.
You two make me ashamed
to call myself an idiot.
There's always going to be
someone smarter than you,
so the only way to be happy
is to make the most
of what you've got.
But you've got nothing.
Oh, no?
I've got one single nail,
and another nail
to nail it in with,
and I'm gonna stop this infernal
ice cream machine
once and for all.
Aah! Oh! Oh!
(groaning, screaming)
Oh! Oh! Ow!
(laughing)
Some doomsday machine!
It barely killed anyone!
Oh, yeah?
Well, take this!
Oh, my.
Poor Leonardo DaVinci.
He sure was stupid.
Fry, I admire what you did today
and I'm deeply sorry for
insulting your intellect...
Your tiny, tiny intellect.
Oops! There I go
again, you dope.
Uh, I mean, dummy.
It's okay.
I may not be clever,
but I have a good heart.
That's what my mom used to say.
She was a wise woman.
FRY: Also that I'm not
much to look at.
Professor: A wise woman indeed.
I can't believe it!
I'm gonna die!
Next Thursday...
Sync by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net