♪ Two... two, three... ♪
♪ ♪
Sync & corrections by Alice
www.addic7ed.com
(mechanical whirring)
Mom on deck!
Ten...
(grunts)
All right, grunts,
here's your
pre-mission pep talk.
Shoot anyone
who doesn't obey hard enough.
But...
Stop gaining
knowledge, Hubert.
(grunts)
It's a simple mission.
The grunts catch the alien,
the surgeon guts it,
and you smuggle
the poison parts back here.
Uh, something
about poison, got it.
By the way, that surgeon--
where is he?
You! Where's the butcher?
Ma'am, I don't know, ma'am.
His duffel bag arrived.
(Zoidberg groans)
ZOIDBERG:
It's not a duffel bag.
It's my apartment!
Hubert, meet John Zoidberg.
You need an alien
hacked to pieces,
he's the best there is...
in the budget category.
Have you ever dissected
a yeti before?
(chortles)
Himalayan or Neptunian?
Tritonian.
(gasps)
A Tritonian yeti?
You two aren't up
to anything unethical,
- are you?
- Relax.
There's nothing unethical
about covert
biological weapons research.
I said relax!
(both gasp)
(Owls hooting)
Ah, Zoidberg, we've
known each other so long
that sometimes I don't
think we even need words
to understand
each other.
What?
Once and for all, Fry,
even though it's the future,
most objects
are still just objects,
not aliens who
look like objects.
So my efforts to establish
diplomatic relations
with the Cactus People
were doomed from the start.
So you're in pain
and have a bunch of needles?
I prescribe acupuncture.
Let's begin.
(Fry screams)
Blood?!
I mean... blood.
Put it back in me!
I'm afraid Fry lost
a lot of juice.
He's developed
Simpson's Jaundice.
Ay carumba.
His only hope
is some replacement liver.
Yours looks like a good match.
Well, if it'll help Fry...
Careful, Leela!
He knows less about
human anatomy than I do.
And I can't even
find my own uterus.
You may feel a slight sawing.
And all we need
is a little spine supplement
to replace what Leela lost
in that unavoidable saw mix-up.
It wasn't unavoidable.
You just had to stop
cutting my spine
when I yelled "Stop,
you're cutting my spine!"
FRY:
Quit complaining.
My body rejected your liver,
and now I've got
Garfield Syndrome.
Oh, I hate Mondays.
Anyhow, Hermes,
all Leela needs
is one of your vertebrae.
But Doctor, will I be able
to limbo afterwards?
Could you limbo before?
(laughing)
Wait.
I say, "Yes,"
and you say,
"I couldn't limbo before."
You ruined
the joke, Hermes.
There you go, Leela.
Good as new!
Whoa. Whoa...
Oh, sure, Leela's fine,
but my jaundice has progressed
to Muppet Gangrene!
It's not easy being gangrenous.
I thought you were only gonna
take out one vertebra!
Yeah, but did
you ever play Jenga?
Sometimes you pull one and...
(imitates crashing)
You don't know what you're doing!
I want my back back! (Shouting)
Hmm. What started out
as a pleasant afternoon
of drugs and surgery
has not gone as planned.
But don't worry, we still have
three or four co-workers
with plenty of spare parts.
My first mission.
I'm so excited.
And after I dissect
the yeti's poison glands,
we can stop, maybe,
for ice cream on the way back?
With shprinkles on?
(laughing)
Why, you're just a big kid,
aren't you, Zoidberg?
A very big kid.
We're over the drop
zone, gentlemen.
Might I suggest you jump out
the door and poop yourselves?
(Men grunting)
(Zoidberg screaming)
So anyway, I hope the
men have been taking
their hypermalaria pills.
Their wha--?
Their "wha--"?
(laughing)
That's funny,
like a crazy old man.
But you know
what's not funny?
Deadly Tritonian
hypermalaria.
Just be sure to stay out
of the methane swamps.
(sniffing)
What smells like methane?
(people groaning in pain)
My God.
I've never seen such
a gruesome shark attack.
Especially this
far inland.
It wasn't a shark.
It was an awful,
incompetent doctor.
Wow, he must've been
a total Zoidberg.
It was Zoidberg.
He brutalized us
with power tools,
gypsy curses and hypnosis.
Yes, master.
You'll all get
through this.
I give you my word
as a real doctor.
What about me?
What did he do to you?
I don't know
exactly, but
(whispers):
I'm incontinent.
I'm truly sorry.
I consider myself
a reasonable man.
Quick with a joke,
slow to anger.
But Bender can't go
on long car trips anymore,
and I say Zoidberg must die.
People, please.
Let's not overreact.
Death to the crab.
How bad is it, Doctor?
Super bad.
It's Tritonian
hypermalaria.
A lot of these men will
be dead within 24 hours.
What?!
Not you, though.
You'll make a complete recovery
and go on to marry a supermodel!
(sighs)
Funny plague,
hypermalaria.
It can kill immediately,
or lie dormant for decades.
But sooner or later,
it erupts,
causing fever,
spasms, madness,
coma,
and finally death.
What?!
Supermodel!
Oh, those poor,
doomed bastards.
I guess it's up to me
to complete the mission.
(wind howling)
I'll be in the swamp, blowing
the smirk off a toxic yeti.
(cocks gun)
(shuddering)
Professor, we need
to talk, man-to-mob.
(all clamoring)
We've had it
with Zoidberg!
We demand you fire him!
Nonsense.
Zoidberg's a fine physician,
for aliens.
Your mistake is being humans.
No, if I'm going to fire anyone,
it'll be Scruffy.
(all shouting)
You can't do that!
Over my dead body!
Don't you get
it, old man?
Thanks to Dr. Scissorhands,
I wet myself every
time I laugh.
(laughing)
It's not funny!
Well, I guess
it is kind of funny.
(laughing)
Uh-oh.
Why are you protecting
Zoidberg, Professor?
Do you owe him
something?
Is he blackmailing you
somehow?
What does he
have on you?
Why have you kept him
around all these years
when he's so grossly
incompetent?
(sighs)
Long ago,
Zoidberg and I
entered
into a secret arrangement
relating to certain
extraordinary events
too horrible to reveal.
So there's nothing
to be curious about.
(rustling)
Stop, or I'll shoot!
Zoidberg?
You can't hunt a yeti
by yourself, sir.
It's suicidal!
So what? I'm going to die
of hypermalaria, anyway.
I was in the same swamp
as the rest of the men.
Just because you
were in the swamp
doesn't
necessarily mean...
I was thirsty
from the flight.
I drank swamp water.
Look, Zoidberg,
you're a loyal friend.
"Friend"?
But I'm doomed.
I might as well capture
a yeti and die trying.
Then you'll need someone
to dissect it, friend.
(roaring)
(gun whirring)
Go, Johnny! Go!
That's an order!
Never! Zoidberg doesn't
abandon a friend, apparently.
Oh. Oh-oh-oh...
(snarling)
I'll save us
by scaring him off
with my crazy war noise.
(makes gurgling noise)
(growls)
(screams)
(cracking)
Crunch all you want.
I'll make more.
Oy, I lost another one.
(door opens)
Zoidberg, I'm sorry
to break it to you this way,
but we hate you and we never
want to see you again.
But friends...
We're not your friends!
We're your victims!
I was just trying to...
Shut up and give
me my kidney back!
(sniffles)
I'm sorry.
(sobbing)
We don't know why the Professor
keeps you around here,
and we don't care.
You're a terrible doctor!
Nobody wants
to see you ever again!
Dr. Zoidberg!
I want to see
you right now!
The time has
come, my friend.
We have to talk about
our arrangement.
Oh, no. No, no.
Oh, no, no, no!
Oh, no!
(yeti growling)
Unpaw him, you big ape!
I saw this in a Tarzan movie!
It was called...
(grunts)
Tarzan Versus the Yetis.
I lost my virginity
(grunts)... during the film,
so I'm (grunts)...
a little fuzzy on the details.
(yeti growling,
Professor grunts)
(Professor shouting)
(Professor and yeti grunt)
John, are you
all right?
You... you saved my life!
- Oh, fuff.
- Yes, fuff.
How can I ever
repay you?
Do you need a slave?
Or maybe a butler?
No, I haven't needed a butler
since grad school.
But I do need a doctor.
I don't want to die
like those Marines, John.
The fever, the madness.
Don't forget the spasms,
coma and death.
Oh, I don't want
to go through that.
I want you to kill me.
All right. Give
me the knife.
Not now!
Hypermalaria
can lie dormant for years.
Isn't that what you said?
It sounds like something
I would say.
So stay with me until
the symptoms start,
then put me
out of my misery.
You must swear!
All right, Hubert, I swear.
It's started, Zoidberg--
the fever, the muscle spasms.
I'm dying.
(coughs)
It's time for you to keep your
promise and kill me.
This is very difficult,
but I'll try,
friend.
(shrieks)
(choking)
No, wait,
I'm afraid to die.
Ugh, you said you wanted me
to kill you.
Is this one of those
"no means yes" deals?
Yes and no.
I do want you to kill me,
but I mustn't see it coming.
That would be agony.
So you must murder me
completely by surprise.
As God is my witness,
you can count on me.
Well, see you tomorrow.
Not surprising enough.
♪ ♪
(shots firing)
Wha...?
Oh...
(screams)
My...
heart.
(gags)
Hey. What are you doing there?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Stop, you don't understand.
Let's go,
you murderer.
Fry, help me lock him up.
Hang on, I'm learning
how to do loop-de-loops.
Whoa, whoa, whoo!
You're making a mistake.
I was only trying
to kill the Professor.
(straining)
(snipping)
Hubert, I'm sorry.
Huh?
He doesn't have hair.
Great Little Caesar's ghost.
You fools, you stupid,
life-prolonging fools.
I asked Zoidberg to kill me.
Huh? What?
What you talkin' 'bout, Professor?
Professor, have you gone mad?
Probably.
It's one of the symptoms
of Tritonian hypermalaria.
(gasps)
You mean the incurable disease
that causes fever, spasms,
insanity...
(crazed giggle)
...coma...
(sighs)
...and finally death?
Yes, and I begged Zoidberg
to put me out of my misery.
Bring him... quickly.
(sighs)
Should have known better
than to store my antiques
in the office.
LEELA:
Zoidberg, we were wrong.
We're letting you out
so you can kill the Professor.
(whooping)
Oh, no, he sand-crabbed out.
(sighs)
Then we have no choice.
We'll have to mercy-kill
the Professor ourselves.
Well, let's get started.
We have a situation,
Mother.
This creature tried to
sand-crab into the building.
Zoidberg?
Sorry I didn't call first,
Carol, but I'm in a hurry.
I need your help to save Hubert.
Let him go and stooge
the hell out of here.
We're on it.
Ow. Ow! Ow!
Beautiful kids.
You must be very proud.
John Zoidberg.
It's been a long time.
How have you been?
Not too bad.
Last year I took a bus trip
to the Grand Canyon.
Later I'll show you
the pictures.
Do you ever regret it, John,
leaving me to work
for the Professor?
(sighs) What do you
want me to say?
He saved my life.
Oh, big deal.
You could have been rich
if you'd stayed.
Your own lab,
a full staff.
But Hubert is my friend.
He's very sick.
I can cure him, but
I need the thing,
the thing from Triton.
It'll cost you, John.
How much are you worth now?
I live in a Dumpster.
All I have in the world
is this coupon
for one free session
at the tanning salon.
Oh, John, that's really
all you have?
Then I'll take it.
(groaning deliriously)
Okay, Murdolator's finished.
I said I'd kill him myself,
but nobody listens to Bender.
We all have to share
in the guilt,
which is why we're each going
to add one drop of cyanide
to the death wheel
as it goes by.
Commence mercy-killing
in three, two, a-yup.
Kill-check one is go.
(all gasp)
(all cheer)
Kill-check two is go.
(Oohing and Aahing)
It's about time.
Vegetables activated.
Kill-check three is go.
Also, the salad's ready.
(all cheering)
ZOIDBERG:
What the hell are you doing?
TEELA:
Zoidberg,
we know about your
secret agreement.
I am so, so sorry for
how we treated you.
And to make it up to you, we're
killing the Professor for you
so he doesn't die horribly
from hypermalaria.
He doesn't have hypermalaria,
you idiots.
(animal roar)
He has yeti-ism.
(all gasp)
When he saved my life
all those years ago,
he was scratched by a yeti.
Hmm, I consider myself
almost completely ignorant
of modern medicine, and
I've never heard of yeti-ism.
It mimics the symptoms
of hypermalaria exactly,
except for the part
where instead of dying,
you turn into a yeti.
Aah.
(whistling)
Wow.
Hold him down
while I prepare the antidote.
Another yeti?
Yes, the same jerk
that once noshed on me
like a shrimp toast.
Now who's getting
his pineal gland extracted?
(grunts angrily)
Ah, yes,
this contains a concentrated
form of the yeti neurotoxin.
But that's what gave him
yeti-ism in the first place.
Won't it just make him
a double-yeti?
Don't lecture me about
alien physiology, Conrad.
The pineal neurotoxin
neutralizes
the adrenal neurotoxin.
That's why yetis
don't drive themselves mad.
(roars furiously)
My God, he's like some kind
of believable Hulk.
No time for an injection.
(roaring)
(grunts angrily)
(gulps)
(roars)
ZOIDBERG: I'll be damned,
it did make him a double-yeti.
(roars)
(whistling stops)
(growling)
(groans)
(all screaming)
It wasn't supposed to do
any of those things.
You did it, Johnny.
I'm cured.
All right, let's set
it up and try again.
There's one thing
I don't understand, Zoidberg.
How did you persuade Mom to give
you her precious yeti head?
Did you have to promise
anything in return?
Nothing, nothing at all.
This calls for a celebration.
Come on, everyone,
Let´s go tanning!
(All cheer)
(Groan)
I was going to tan...
...once
What do you say, Johnny?
It's on me.
Thank you, Hubert.
(whooping)
Sync & corrections by Alice
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net