A wise man an once said
that nothing really dies,
it just comes back
in a new form.
Then he died.
So next time you see
a lowly salamander,
think twice
before you step on it.
It might be you.
Stand by for reincarnation.
♪ Two... two, three... ♪
♪ ♪
Sync and correction by Mlmlte
www.addic7ed.com
Howdy, folks.
Come on in.
♪ Jumpin' Joe and golly jeeper ♪
♪ I got one gigantic peeper ♪
♪ Sassafras and banana oil ♪
♪ I'm a beautiful
purple-haired goil. ♪
Watch it!
Oh, it's just that I love
Leela something awful.
Do you think a space-age dame
like her would ever marry
a two-bit low-life
delivery boy like me,
and also I have bad posture
and severe financial problems?
Have you tried
getting her pregnant?
Gosh, yes, I've tried and tried,
but so far
I only got Amy pregnant.
You know what your problem is?
Too much smoke in your face.
I want to ask Leela
to marry me,
but I can't afford
a diamond ring
big enough to express my love.
That's for sure,
not on the measly salary I
steal from you each month.
All crew,
report to the laboratorium.
Get a wiggle on.
Thanks for the heads-up, Sparky.
Mmm-mmm, fish on Friday
and human flesh
the rest of the week.
Movietone News, everyone.
I've discovered a new comet.
One side, boys.
Let a lady take a gander.
Hang on,
let me just adjust it
to your eye level.
Holy matrimony.
That's one flashy rock.
Indeed, it's pure diamondium.
Um, would it be possible
to break off a piece
and put it
in an engagement ring
for reasons that are private?
Oh, fuff.
Nothing in the universe
can fracture diamondium,
not even God One and God Two
put together.
But behold!
The tail is composed
of abrasive comet powder,
and that's just what I need
to put a wash-day shine
on my new doomsday device.
Now, hop in the flivver
and score me some
of that sweet, sweet powder.
♪ ♪
Comet ahoy!
Why, it's lit up like a smooth,
refreshing Chesterfield.
Get plenty of that powder.
I want this bomb to sparkle
like the floor
at Grand Central Station.
Over and out.
Watch it, you stumblebums.
You're boopin' my betty.
Um, I'll be back in a jiff.
I got to go check this comet
for anarchists.
♪ ♪
Would you look at that gem?
Slap that shiner on a ring,
and me and Leela will be doing
the married horizontal
Charleston in no time.
All right, diamond,
you won those rounds,
but I've got an ace up my hole.
I love this time of day.
There's such a
beautiful stillness.
Leela, I don't know
if words can describe
how I feel about you...
Good?
Huh, I-I guess
they can.
Anyhow, when a guy feels good
about his sweetheart,
he wants to prove it by giving
her something really... good.
I'm still listening,
you big lug.
Well, what I'm trying
to say is, in all the world,
I couldn't find a diamond
good enough for you,
but then I found one out there
among the stars--
the beautiful, affordable stars.
You mean, when you disappeared
up on the comet...?
Exactly.
I thought you snuck
off to take a dump.
A man can sneak off
to do two things.
Oh, Fry.
In exactly ten seconds,
the doomsday device
will blow the stone loose,
and if my calculations
are correct,
it will land here
on your finger.
You've made me the happiest
finger in the whole wide hand.
Comet kaboomination
in three, two...
Um, hello, cuckoo.
The diamond still
didn't break!
Now you'll never know
how much I love you.
It went kersplitters.
Fry,
I don't need a diamond.
You've given me the
most beautiful rainbow
I've ever seen--
all the colors of the spectrum.
Not beautiful enough.
A swell gal like you
deserves better.
What's that?
Is my eye playing trick on me?
It's so beautiful.
Fry, you've created a new
color, totally different
from any other color or
combination of colors.
Shucks, it's still only
half as beautiful as you.
Whoa.
I wish this moment
could last forever.
Leela, my love,
will you marry me?
Gornella, my love,
Blorg, blorg,
a thousand times blorg.
Good news, multiplayers.
After a lifetime of toil,
I'm on the verge of solving
all the mysteries of science.
So we can leave early?
Certainly not.
Not until I demonstrate
this new microscope lens
made from the debris
of that diamondium comet.
Hey, Professor.
Yes, Bender.
Aah! Boo!
Okay, too bad, good-bye.
You're not through
with this level.
I have another lens.
Byte my eight-bit metal ass.
That's byte with a "Y."
Whatever you say, mon.
Due to the lens' remarkable
quark lattice structure,
it should be capable
of unthinkable magnification.
Come, follow me to the lab.
Hey, I'm gonna try that.
So long, meatbags.
Son of a...
Let me just insert lens
in microscope.
There, now, for the first time,
we may be able to see
the infinitesimal fabric
of matter itself,
laying bare the most
fundamental laws
of the universe.
Hey, Fry, I know something
you could lay bare.
Leela, shh, I'm trying to
listen to a physics lecture.
Now, to examine some matter.
Any old matter will do.
Mon, that's some
cheap-ass matter.
What the hell is it?
Oh, it's just a log I found
in a hole
in the bottom of the sea.
Now, to penetrate
its deepest mysteries.
Hey, Fry...
Leela, no means no.
Oh, my, there's a frog
on a bump on this log
that I found in a hole
in the bottom of the sea.
And that's the ultimate
secret of the universe?
Apparently so.
Wait, there's a snail
on the tail of the frog
on the bump
on this log that I found in
a hole in the bottom of the sea.
Dear Liza.
The snail itself is composed
of cells, molecules, atoms.
Pfft, those things don't rhyme.
Things only rhyme below ten
to the minus five angstroms,
you dope.
Now, ions and pions,
muons and gluons,
neutrinos, gravitinos...
We're closing in on the very
smallest particles of matter.
For the first time,
we're about to observe
the fundamental structure
of the universe.
Such detail.
Such finely wrought,
intricate beauty.
It's like staring
into the face of God.
It's a mirror
into Scruffy's soul.
This explains everything,
even the big bang
that created the universe.
All that's left is
the mathematics.
Put down h-bar,
carry the infinity, and...
My-reka!
There it is,
the grand unified theory,
reducing all the laws of nate
to a single equation.
Professor, you did it.
You solved the problem
that baffled Einstein
and drove Stephen Hawking
to quit physics and become
a cartoon voice actor.
I like physics, but
I love cartoons.
This is the greatest moment
in scientific history.
At last, there are no more
questions left to answer.
Well done, Professor.
Okay, back to work, everyone.
Wait, there are
no more questions
left to answer.
And those are
today's high scores.
Linda?
Thanks, Morbo.
Coming up next,
Galaxians-- what you need to
know to protect your family.
How do you people do it?
How do you go on, knowing
there's nothing more to know?
I watch TV.
It's the next best thing
to being alive.
Oh, what's the use?
I'm just not capable
of the happiness of the dumb.
If only I'd made some mistake!
You didn't. I checked the
invariance of your Lagrangian.
Hubba hubba.
Then there's
nothing left to do!
Nothing!
Would it cheer you up if
I punched Fry in the groin?
'Cause I'll do it, regardless.
Body blow! Body blow!
I devoted every waking minute
to answering the fundamental
questions of science.
I never married,
rarely went outside...
and now that I've found
all the answers,
I realize
that what I was living for
were the questions.
That stinks, Professor.
Too bad the universe
made it turn out that way
and not some other way.
I wonder why it did that.
Probably magnets.
Shut up, Hawking!
Fry, you idiot!
You're a genius!
Why are the laws of
physics what they are,
instead of some other laws?
To find out, we'd have
to recreate the conditions
before the big bang.
It would take decades of work
by thousands of scientists
in a particle accelerator
powered by dump trucks
of flaming grant money!
Of course, there'd be no
guarantee of success,
and, in any case,
I'd never live to see it.
I'm surprised you lived
through that sentence.
Sorry you wasted
your life, Professor.
I guess you'll never know
everything, after all.
Indeed. The pursuit of knowledge
is hopeless and eternal.
Hooray!
Action Delivery Force: assemble!
Ha-ya!
Ya!
Hoo-oo!
Ay-ay-ay-ay-ay-ay!
And me,
Mighty Merchandise Robot!
Meanwhile, on Space Planet 4,
the aliens who communicate
by dancing
were worshipping
a giant comet.
♪ ♪
Team assembled!
What is that box, you old witch?
Ha, ha, ha.
I'll never tell you.
It's a deep space
emotion detector.
The detector can tell you're
impressed. You should be!
Wha? The marvelous device,
it's detecting a massive burst
of anger from deep space!
Flying bananas?
Ha, ha. I will slice them
on my morning fish porridge.
This is no time for
one of your jokes, Fry.
I will tell you something
that's no joke.
I will lead the defense fight.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Don't make me laugh.
If we fight,
we'll surely be destroyed.
Then what is our only hope?
We must summon Zagtar,
defenderf space!
You forget...
Zagtar was destroyed
by the crystal space devil!
The crystal space devil
was once my brother
Prince Hiroshi.
I mourn his loss,
but what matters now
is protecting Earth
from that fruit armada.
I see your mother
the water mutant
didn't raise any fools,
Turanga Leela.
Our only hope is
to communicate with the aliens,
and show them
our peaceful intentions.
Perhaps they speak
perfect English, as do we.
Ha, ha, ha, ha!
We can't take that chance.
We'll need my universal
auto-translator.
This is my universal
That will show them
our peaceful intentions.
The only question is,
who should be our spokesman?
Me, me. Choose Zoidberg.
Zoidberg a diplomat?
The list of things I've heard
now contains everything.
Hear my words. My
shell may be tough,
like a samurai honeymoon mask,
but inside I'm as
soft and sensitive
as a girl made of custard.
Custard time?
Hooray!
Please, I am certain I will
succeed with my delicate manner.
Oops.
Instead, I will send
the peace transmission.
Most honored visitors,
we greet you in peace.
♪ ♪
Kajiggaru desu!
All attempts to communicate
with the aliens have failed.
I fear our only option
is thrilling space battle.
Power friends, go!
Launch all missiles!
We were defeated in battle.
Oh, no!
They're forming Gigatron!
Defeat is ours.
If we can't communicate
with these bone jelly ghosts,
we're doomed!
Professor, I have analyzed
the aliens' movements
with this movement analyzer.
That device was a gift
from my ancestors. Go on.
It seems their movements
are a form of language.
Rather than speaking J--
English.
...like us,
they speak by dancing.
Of course! Having no
mouths or ears,
they could only communicate
through motions.
Or perhaps by odors.
That is how you communicate.
Then our only hope
to talk to them
is by doing a peace dance.
But it will have to be smoother
and more fluid
than any movement mankind
is capable of!
What if we hire
a buttered geisha?
Another one of your
ill-timed jokes, Fry?
You and I are enemies now.
Hear my words.
I believe I,
the most humble member
of Action Delivery Team,
could do such a dance.
Ha, ha, ha, ha. Surely,
your hard shell is too rigid.
I call on anyone but you
to do the peace dance.
Of course,
I will do the peace dance.
But I will need help.
Super Dance Squad, initiate!
We all hope they're
communicating
a peaceful message.
Wha-wha? We thought
we were so smart
with our science and dancing.
But look at us now,
at Gigatron's mercy!
The shame is too great.
It's time to end this.
Zoidberg, stop!
We're too scared right now
to enjoy the ceremony
of your death.
No hara-kiri today,
but heiwa no dansu.
The gelatinous dance of peace.
You may be gelatinous,
but not even the Mochi Phantom
could perform
such intricate motions!
Says you, salaryman.
Behold: the dance of peace.
Sync and correction by Mlmlte
www.addic7ed.com
The dance is so complex,
I can't barely follow it.
**** team member,
but I have given it my own.
I underestimated you, Medical Crab.
But, will the Aliens understand?
Zoidberg, you are the greatest hero.
You save this all.
For now,
But another ****
next week at the same time.
Until then,
Action Delivery Force Star Hero
**** engaged.
www.tvsubtitles.net