♪ Two... two, three... ♪
♪
Futurama presents...:
Mutual of omicron's wild universe
brought to you by
mutual of omicron...
insuring your world,
and its destruction.
Tonight's planet: A primitive
backwater known only as...
Earth.
Sync and corrections by Tony for
www.Addic7ed.Com
narrator:
Of all the creatures on earth,
none has a more
thrilling life cycle
than the intrepid salmon.
It all begins in a cold,
freshwater stream,
where the salmon eggs incubate.
I'm born, baby!
Narrator: The new hatchlings
are known as "Fry."
What's your name?
I don't have a name.
I'm a salmon.
Narrator: After three
years in the stream,
the young salmon are ready
for the arduous journey
to the ocean.
I do look forward to
cavorting in the spray.
Narrator:
The trip will be dangerous.
Only three in ten will survive.
Let's all ten of us go together.
There's safety in numbers.
Ah!
Mm. I reckon my boy
will be right pleased
when I regurgitate
that into his mouth.
Narrator: Looming ahead:
Nature's waterfall,
the cliff of the waters.
Ah, it sure is relaxing getting
swept along by this current.
Whoa!
(Screams) Salmon
Hedonismbot: Oh my!
(Screaming) Salmon
Hedonismbot: Oh dear!
Hedonismbot: Oh yes!
This just in.
Three dead in foamy plunge.
(Laughs)
Oh... oh.
(Choking noises)
Still, six out of ten alive.
That's considered good
for our species!
Five out of ten, also nice.
Ayup.
Narrator: And so the
salmon reach the ocean,
birthplace of all life.
Except the salmon.
Uh, hello.
Who are you?
I'm a salmon.
Really? Me too!
No way!
So, uh, hey...
I don't want to be
too forward, but...
I'd like to mate
with you in a few years
when we're sexually mature.
I'd like that.
Coho, what have we here?
I'm a pieces.
And you?
Also pieces.
We're all pieces.
Then it's a date.
I'll see you at spawning time.
No, thanks.
I've already found my mate.
You haven't ignored
the last of me...
♪
narrator: Having reached maturity,
it is time for the salmon to spawn.
Thus begins their
1000-mile journey
back to the exact stream
in which they were born.
So how do we find our way home?
Nobody knows!
Narrator:
Experts are unsure
whether salmon navigate
by memory, sense of smell,
or by detecting variations
in earth's magnetic field.
Okay, everybody do one
of those three things.
♪
well, this is it.
Home, stream home.
No, it isn't!
I was born
in the next stream up!
You're from next stream up?
So am I!
I can tell by the magnets
in my head, or whatever.
Let's go!
Narrator: The urge to spawn
drives the salmon inexorably
toward the stream of its birth.
Stupid body!
Why won't you go to
that other stream?
Nobody knows!
Narrator:
I just told you!
Goodbye!
It was fun maturing with you,
but at this point
in my life cycle,
I need a mate who's within
squirting distance.
I'll never forget you... fish.
Come on, loxy lady,
it's time for us to
get naughty by nature!
(Sobbing):
No!
(Talking indistictly)
Well, here goes something...
(Grunts)
Don't make it...
Don't make it!
Ouch!
Son of a fish!
Pfft. Jumping is for suckers.
Oh, I'm good!
Who wants a piece of me?
I'll try a bite!
Narrator: Having completed
its perilous journey,
the exhausted salmon
enters the final phase
of its life cycle.
The female deposits her eggs
and the male fertilizes them.
Okay, who's next?
There's a lot more
where that came from!
(Coughs)
I can't see them any more!
What if they're mating?
Who cares?
Just release your milt already!
Everybody's doing it!
No!
I refuse to release anything
unless it's in the vicinity of
the eggs of the fish I love!
(Grunts)
(Coughing)
Tell my offspring I loved me...
Very much...
(Gasps)
Oh, yeah.
Plop those roundies.
Ah!
Ooh!
(Gasping)
(Grunting)
All right, step aside.
Time to let my bad boys loose.
Ah!
I am brrr,
devourer of fish and honey!
(Gasping)
I'm coming, darling!
Hm, I shouldn't...
But who's counting?
Help! Fish police!
Two salmon for dinner?
What? It's spawning season!
It's a bear holiday!
That is what you said when
you found those boy scouts!
Next you'll be telling me
I can't crap in the woods!
That's it!
We're hibernating in
separate caves this winter!
My love!
You... you made it!
You overcame salmon instinct and
left your home stream for me!
Mmm.
So are you gonna
fertilize my eggs now?
Already taken care of.
Well, we swam away
and then we came back.
It's been an interesting life.
(Coughs)
And the best part is,
it had a happy ending.
Narrator: And so the endless
circle of life comes to an end,
meaningless and grim.
Why did they live,
and why did they die?
No reason.
Narrator:
The isolated Galápagos islands.
A veritable pageant
of evolutionary science.
Home to dozens of species found
nowhere else,
such as Darwin's finches,
and the marine iguana.
Also the blue-footed booby!
That's fairly interesting!
Note the blue
coloration of the...
Narrator: Of all the
creatures in the Galápagos,
none is rarer or more tragic
than the Pinta island tortoise.
Only a single living specimen
is known to exist:
Lonesome Hubert.
Sad news, everyone.
I'm lonesome.
Hey, would it cheer
you up if we gave you
a symbiotic parasite cleaning?
Would it? Would it? Would it?
(Sighs)
Fine, knock yourself out.
Narrator:
The Galápagos finches
eat parasites off
the tortoise's skin,
a mutually
beneficial arrangement.
Except for the parasite!
How's that, Hubert?
Feeling better?
(Sighs)
A good beaking usually
cheers me right up,
but today it's no use.
My species is
as good as extinct.
I haven't seen a female
of my kind in over 100 years!
There's got to be
a lady tortoise
out there for you, Hubert.
What about her?
Hey, good lookin',
I've got a lichen
that needs a lickin'.
Are you crazy?
She's a slightly
different subspecies!
See how her shell flares
imperceptibly at the neck?
Ooh... talk about
a cloaca shrinker.
Well, haven't you ever
met a girl tortoise
who had that whole "same
subspecies" thing going on?
Oh my, yes.
When I was a young
tortoise of 50
I met a hot young
piece of shell
by a palo santo tree on
the far side of the island.
Let's go look for her!
C'Mon, c'Mon, c'Mon!
I've always wondered if she's
still there, waiting for me.
But the trip is far too long.
It's only 100 feet!
At my age,
it might as well be 200 feet.
I'd never make it!
Come on, you can make it!
You can do it!
Get out of your shell.
Do it, do it!
Well, let me think it over.
Let's go already!
(Owl hooting)
(Exclaiming)
(Hissing)
(Gasps) Watch out!
What brings yous to this part of
the isleseses?
(Screams)
He's gonna eat us!
Don't be such a Finch.
We Galápagos tortoises
have no natural predators.
Finch Amy (Muffled):
That's so fascinating!
I never thought I'd live
to see this tree again.
Thank you for staying
with me, Fry.
I'm not Fry.
I'm his great-great grandson...
Fry.
Whuh...?
My beak is different, see?
It evolved a slightly bigger
hook over the generations,
to help me eat the cactus
on this part of the island.
Watch!
(Grunting)
I'm stuck!
Oops.
So where's your
lady tortoise, Hubert?
Lady whuh?
Wait, there she is!
After all these years,
I've found her!
Oh, my darling!
You haven't aged a day!
Should we say something?
Nah.
Let him have his fun.
All right.
Let's just do what
comes naturally.
I'll get things started with
a little neck extension...
Then a couple of these...
And here we go!
What the tropical hell
are you doing?!
(All gasping) Whuh?
I've been saving myself
for a hundred years,
and this is how you repay me?
Who is that
hard-shelled skank?
I'll kill her!
Wait, I can explain...
shut up!
I'm going
to crack that hussy open
like a slutty Brazil nut!
(Grunts)
This volcanic archipelago
isn't big enough
for the both of us.
Yeah, you'd better topple.
You always were a
hot-blooded latina.
Narrator:
Like all reptiles,
the Galápagos tortoise
is cold-blooded.
Okay, neck, tap, tap,
climb, climb, and...
We're back in business.
Um, should we be watching this?
It seems kind of personal.
That's not an issue for us.
We're wildlife.
(Weak, raspy moaning)
What about the moaning?
Is it okay to listen?
Sure, but act like
it's no big deal.
Just pretend
you're eating seeds.
Is it weird if I talk about
his crazy turtle penis?
No.
Well, okay then.
Yes, it's been lovely.
Hang on a second.
(Straining)
Narrator:
The Galápagos tortoise
lays a clutch of
between six and 15 eggs.
Oh, what do you want?
I'm 150 years old.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
Aren't you going
to watch over your young?
Tortoises don't do that, do we?
I sure as hell don't.
Anyway, I've done my part.
The species is saved!
(All cheering)
Good job!
Narrator:
And so, the survival
of the Pinta island tortoise
is assured.
(Grunting)
(Yelling)
All:
Mama!
Narrator:
And so, the extinction
of the Pinta island tortoise
is assured.
200 million years
of evolution, snuffed out.
For in the end,
nature is horrific,
and teaches us nothing.
(Cheerily):
Coming up next,
the hilarious
antics of the elephant seal,
(chuckling):
The clown of the sea.
Narrator: Of all the
spectacles in nature,
few can match the mating ritual
of the elephant seal.
Certainly not the salmon.
And the tortoise?
Yeah, right.
The huge, lumbering males
defend patches of beach
to deny their rivals
access to the breeding grounds.
Just as in human society,
only the biggest,
most obnoxious males
have any chance of mating.
Aw, yeah!
Survival of the fattest!
Narrator: The dominant male,
or "beachmaster,"
maintains a harem
of up to 50 females.
Okay, harem, let's get to it.
Form an orderly heap
on top of me.
(Cows barking)
I like mating with beachmaster
'cause he's the largest.
Narrator: While the beachmaster
enjoys the spoils of victory...
Whoo!
I'm doin' it in my sleep!
...the lesser males languish
at the edge of the colony,
unable to attract
their own harem due to age...
Harem?!
I can barely see 'em!
Immaturity...
(High-pitched laugh)
I'm scared.
...or other reasons.
Hmm. I don't know...
Does this kelp scarf
make me look fat enough?
It's so unfair.
That bloated Casanova
gets all the ladies!
Even that one with the
exquisite fat rolls.
(Bleating)
(Sighs)
(Bellowing)
(Terrified yelp)
Back off, losers!
Stay away from my beaches!
You big bully!
Bite my freshly molted,
blubber-filled ass.
You're just a giant lump of fat!
Do you even
have an ass under there?!
I'm 40% ass!
Arf, arf!
Now beat it! Boo!
(All gasping, shuddering)
(Laughs)
Narrator: With no hope of
defeating the beachmaster,
some so-called "sneaky" males
adopt a risky strategy...
attempting to mate
with one of his harem
while he is asleep
or distracted.
So, any of you guys thinking
of being a sneaky male
this season?
(All muttering uneasily)
This season?
Walrus don't need no chicanery.
Once a lady goes
walrus, she never...
She ne...
No one ever goes walrus.
I'm a little old for it now,
but in my prime,
I was quite the sneaker.
How did you do it?
Well, while
the beachmaster was off
behind a whale carcass,
loudly fornicating
with my beloved mother,
I snuck past
and surprised my sweetie
with a romantic meal.
A romantic meal, eh?
Narrator: The search for food
takes the elephant seal
to depths
few other mammals can reach.
In this pitch-black abyss,
life takes on
bizarre and horrific forms.
Zoidberg:
So, welcome to the abyss.
Road trip!
(Snoring)
Kill all penguins...
(Pups squealing)
Kill all penguins.
(Screaming)
(Snorts) Huh?
What's the matter with you!?
You just crushed
seven of our babies!
Yeah, we can always make more.
Come on, floozies,
let's repopulate!
Narrator:
With the beachmaster occupied,
the sneaky male makes his move.
(Gasps)
I can't believe you came!
The beachmaster'll kill
you if he finds out!
Also, who are you?
(Spits)
I'm in love with you!
And I don't care what he thinks.
Here, I brought you something.
Hooray!
We're three friends
at the beach!
(Munching)
Wait, what's happening, friend?
(Screams)
Narrator: The female
conveys her receptivity
through subtle vocalizations.
Wanna do it?
So soon?!
Oh, well... (Stammering)
(Both gasp)
Sneaky male, eh?
I thought I told you...
(Roaring)
(Shuddering):
Oh, my...!
Well, nice try.
Better luck next season.
You gave it a shot!
Pathetic.
Sorry you didn't get to mate.
But, hey, we can still
play some beach games.
Who's up for some twister?
No!
We beta males deserve better.
When we're in charge, we'll
treat females with respect,
keeping sensible harems
of no more than five.
And it begins with me.
Sir, I challenge you to a duel
for control of the beach!
(All gasping)
Aw...
(Laughing)
Aw, hang on...
(Resumes laughing)
Okay, let's fight.
(Yells, grunts)
Aw, that's it.
No more Mr. nice-jerk.
Narrator:
The battle will rage for hours,
until both males
are exhausted or dead.
(Yelling, grunting)
Beachmaster, stop fighting!
He's been dead since yesterday!
(Snorts)
What?! He's dead?!
Whoo!
I'm killin' dudes in my sleep!
Yo! Clean up!
Narrator:
And so, with the threat
to the beachmaster's
supremacy eliminated,
order is restored
for another year.
Another year,
another generation of pups
fathered by me, beachmaster.
(All snickering)
I'm the greatest, baby!
You go, beachmaster!
Narrator: And so concludes our
exploration of planet earth.
For a holographic brain
injection of tonight's program,
send five dollars
to this station,
care of me, the narrator.
Good night.
Mutual of omicron narrator:
Mutual of omicron.
Have you insured your planet?
Sync and correction by Tony for
www.Addic7ed.Com
www.tvsubtitles.net