How Hermes Requisitioned
His Groove Back
Finally, the last form of the day.
Welcome to stampy town,
population five.
And now for the finishing touch.
The cycle of bureaucracy.
Sweet gorilla of Manila!
A letter from Central Bureaucracy!
Attention: You are about to receive
a letter from Central Bureaucracy.
It's from Central Bureaucracy!
I'm playing poker with friends
from my old job.
Interested?
I only gamble with chumps.
-I'll play.
-I'm in!
Leela. Fry. Robot.
No matter what, I'm available.
We're playing poker.
But my friends are serious.
Bah! Big shots. I say let the dice
do the talking.
-Is someone fired?
-Better.
Central Bureaucracy
is inspecting tomorrow.
I'll finally be promoted to grade 35,
the 35th highest grade there is.
Hermes, we're having a poker party.
Whip off some of your jerk dip.
I spent all day cleaning my office.
I got to relax the Jamaican way:
warm milk and a good night's sleep.
Jamaican? I thought you were
an outer space potato man.
That must be my old boss.
-Hi, Leela. You're fired.
-I know.
Sorry, but you're over a year
late for work.
Let the games begin!
So I said, "Your request for a date
is flattering, but I decline. "
Office romances never work out.
That's how I met my horrible wife.
You never wore your ring.
I didn't know.
She doesn't know I work.
I keep my personal life separate.
Deal! You'll have time to talk
when you're poor.
-What's with those?
-My lucky shades.
I got them off a lucky guy while his
lucky seeing-eye dog was whizzing.
Hey!
I can't spell anything
with these cards.
Finally, I have a good claw!
Three females, a number and a king
giving himself brain surgery.
It won't matter how many you got.
Bender's hot.
Uh, what can I say?
Must be my lucky shades.
Nothing. Nothing. Crap. Crap. Garbage.
Read them and leak saltwater.
-Oh, man.
-My baby's milk money!
What will I tell my horrible wife?
I'd be more worried about the tapeworm
going to town on your intestines.
Let me see those glasses!
Oh, my various gods! X-ray specs!
I swear those are prescription.
I need them for reading stuff.
-Behind other stuff.
-Cheater!
Break his neck!
No! Don't hurt him!
He's my best friend--
Hey, you wouldn't hit a guy
with x-ray glasses, would ya?
Easy on the arm. Oh! Oh, my ass!
Great cow of Moscow!
Uh, it was ghosts! Big ones!
And a tornado!
I'll never pass inspection now!
They'll bust me lower than a limbo
stick at carnival time!
And that's as low as limbo sticks get.
Don't worry. We'll watch you clean.
It's too late. The inspector'll
be here in exactly one second.
-Who are you?
-Morgan Proctor, grade 1 9.
Hermes Conrad, grade 36.
-Enough banter. Shall we begin?
-This way, please.
Jeez, you seem awfully calm.
Don't worry. I have a plan.
I'm going to jump!
-No!
Do a flip!
Don't do it!
You have so much to live for!
Reverse psychology?
Old friend, don't jump! Use a method
that won't damage your liver.
Others need it, you know?
Husband, no!
Out of my way! I'm not cut out
to be a bureaucrat!
I'm only anal 78.36% of the time.
I'm not worthy to stamp a form,
so I'll stamp the cement with my body!
If you complete your death transaction
without filing a suicide. . .
. . .and/or falling permit,
you'll be demoted.
Life. Death.
Either way I'm demoted
to a tiny cubicle.
Sweet something of-- Of someplace.
I relieve you of duty.
Consider yourself on paid vacation.
Oh! The ultimate penalty.
I recommend the health cure on Spa 5,
the Sauna planet. Here, read.
Spa 5? ls it good?
Wonderful. I don't know
anything about it. . .
. . .they give me krill
for everyone I send.
I have to assign
a bureaucrat to fill in.
I assign me. I accept. Welcome.
It's settled. Hermes will relax
and Zoidberg will eat.
Last Monday, why did it take
twice as long as scheduled?
-Fry got his head stuck in a crater.
-I thought it'd fit.
-During this, what were you doing?
-Drinking contest with the autopilot.
-I'd have won but I ran out of olives.
-I can explain.
You can explain how you left
without enough olives? I think not.
-Is this high school?
-Locker check!
Why isn't this alphabetical?
-What?
-The zipper should be at the bottom.
Uh, sometimes a guy gets lonely.
Oh, l-- I've never seen
anything like this!
-Why's there yogurt in this?
-I can explain.
It used to be milk, and time
makes fools of us all.
You're dismissed!
Fry, I'll speak to you alone.
This is the other Fry's locker.
I'm "Phry. "
Admit it, Fry. You're a slob.
A dirty, filthy slob.
Dirty boy! Dirty, dirty, dirty!
What's going on?
I thought you were anti-dirty!
I'm surrounded by neat all day.
Nothing's kinkier than a slop-jock.
Oh, stop.
Listen, you pig. No one can know.
If anyone asks, I'll deny it.
Like every girl I dated.
And two, and three, and four.
Come on, work those arms!
This is no spa, it's a labor camp.
If I get out, Zoidberg will see
the business end of a shrimp fork!
Give him one for me, mate.
Don't know why I go to him.
I don't miss twice, campers.
For those six reasons. . .
-. . .I'm demoting Leela to copilot.
-Under who?
-The autopilot.
-That drunk?
Bender, you're in charge
of the professor's bodily functions.
It's full-time.
Fry, I'm promoting you
to executive delivery boy.
You won't deliver.
You'll get an office next to me.
All right!
Would you high-five him so we can
continue this meeting?
And on the rebound?
Adjourned.
I don't know why she's nice to you.
She's a hateful monster.
She scolded and hit me.
She's risking my friendship with her.
What happened to you?
I walked the professor.
We were in the park. . .
. . .and a lady says I stole her purse.
I threw the professor at her.
I had to hit her with a purse I found.
It's Morgan's fault.
That pencil-pushing scaz-wag.
If she were here, I'd. . . .
-Uh-oh, is she behind me?
-No. I'm in front of you.
Morgan? It's 3 a.m.
A skunk knocked over my garbage,
and I could only think of you.
My God, it's so. . .
. . .repulsive.
So, this is where you eat?
Eat and sleep.
Oh, Fry!
Bender's my roommate.
He could be back.
I ordered him to flush out
the professor's earwax.
Hey, Fry? I made you
a candle with-- What the--?
Oh, now I see. Now I get it.
Now the pieces are falling into place.
The promotion, the dwarf in my
book club who steals my opinions.
It's coming together!
I must say this opens my eyes!
Another case closed, my dear Watson.
Come back! It's a loop!
For I was blind, but now I see.
The cat's out of the bag!
About last night,
that was just a misunderstanding.
You didn't understand? I'll explain.
You were having sex with you.
No. A bureaucrat of my rank
can't fraternize.
That's what makes it so juicy.
It's the forbidden fruit angle.
"Guess who saw
Fry and Morgan doing it. "
They'll say, "Who, Bender?"
And I'll say,
"It was lovable old Bender. . . . "
What'd you do?
Downloaded his brain. Bender is here:
His memories,
his in-your-face interface.
I am Bender. Please insert girder.
But-- But Bender need brain.
For smart making!
Stop doing things!
I sent it to be filed at Central.
I had to. He was a bad robot.
He was a bad friend.
I want him back!
You should've filed a request
20 years ago.
I'm sick of you and your bureaucracy!
Dirty boy! Dirty boy. . . .
You were having an affair?
She loved me because I'm a slob.
I loved her because I'm desperate.
I am Bender. Please insert girder.
Without his brain,
he's quiet and helpful.
We have to go to Central
and get the disk!
-Oh, yes. We must!
-Yeah!
Why?
Well, that aside, we're going.
You can't waltz into Central.
It's a tangled web of red tape
and regulations.
I haven't been. A friend went mad
trying to find their washroom.
Then we'll need a guide.
Oh, I've been there! Lots of times.
Carts go out full but come in empty.
It's inefficient!
Pulling empty carts
is the closest we get to sleep.
They'd increase efficiency. . .
. . .if empty carts
brought in machinery.
Hey, I like the way you think.
Oh, Lord.
You know, you ought
to be a bureaucrat.
-Will this take long?
-Getting my birth certificate.
It doesn't look like I'll make
it inside. Good luck.
Just leave me where I drop.
Someone had a baby.
Come on, I have a better idea.
We're from the delivery company.
We're here to deliver a robot.
I am Bender. Please insert girder.
Looks like we've got
a new office cutup.
Ooh, ooh! Look out, look out!
I'm gonna crash!
I swerved to avoid you.
Could you tell us where
the canisters go?
Central filing.
-Okay. Thank you.
-Wonderful.
No!
Of course I know where it is.
I'm grade 20.
-Where?
-I can't tell.
-What do I look like, a grade 1 6?
-We're getting nowhere slowly.
I'll address this to the filing room.
We'll track it with my lojack-a-mater.
Cold. Warmer.
Hot, hot, hot, hot....
Don't tell my boss I was asleep.
This is it! We'll run in, grab
Bender's disk and run out. Got it?
We'll never find it.
I am Bender. Please insert girder.
You're right!
Nothing's over if there's hope.
Lost something?
I should have known you'd come here.
And I did. That's why I came.
We're through! You're evil.
I never want to see you again!
Help us for old times' sake?
He's lost in the master "in" pile.
It would take an atomic-powered
sorter to find him.
You rang?
Damn it, jump already!
Stop hogging the healthy liver!
I want to live!
Organizing the labor spa rekindled
my love of bureaucracy.
My Hermes got that hellhole running
so that all the physical labor. . .
. . .is done by a single
Australian man.
-How'd you find us?
-Dr. Zoidberg.
It was me! I'm the hero!
Request for explanation
of incident meeting.
Number 1 .0!
Number 1 .0, I petition you
for an emergency sort. . .
. . .under regulation two--
Don't quote me regulations!
I was on a committee to review. . .
. . .the color of the book
that regulation's in.
We kept it gray.
I must find the disk
with my friend's brain on it.
Very well, but your license
will be revoked if you fail. . .
. . .to sort the master "in" pile
by closing.
-1 p.m.
-That's only four minutes from now.
Requisition me a beat.
I was born, there was a hurricane
We had a foot and a half of water
I cried all night
Blew my alphabet blocks out of order
This boy's born to be a bureaucrat
Born to be obsessive and snotty
I made my relations file applications
To get into my birthday party
-Something changed when he turned pro
-Sorting but wasn 't smiling
-He forgot it's not about rank
-It's about the filing, people
We didn 't choose to be bureaucrats
That's what almighty Jah made us
Treat people like swine, make them
Stand in line, even if nobody paid us
The world looks down on bureaucrats
We're anal, compulsive and weird
Push comes to shove, do what you love
Even if it's not a good idea
-Said I shouldn 't be a surgeon
-Poo-pooed my electric frankfurter
Said I shouldn 't fly with one eye
I am Bender please insert girder
Everybody sing Jamaica
Just the bureaucrats
Just the grade 19s
-Jamaica
-Sing me home
Push comes to shove, do what you love
Even if it's not a good idea
I'm Bender, baby!
Please insert liquor!
-Yeah!
-Congratulations!
You finished with two seconds
to spare, so I'm demoting you.
Good bureaucrats never finish early.
That's okay. At least you're back.
Not yet. I'm acting bureaucrat
of Planet Express.
I have some changes to make.
Fry, you're fired.
-Second--
-Hold on!
While I was sorting, I found a
document filed by Morgan Proctor.
Form B. Notification
of Romantic Entanglement.
She fraternized me!
It's not about you.
It refers to my prom date.
A date that ended in disappointment.
Yes. But you only stamped
it four times!
No! No! I was young and reckless!
You are technically correct.
The best kind of correct.
I hereby promote you
to grade 37.
And as for you? Guards!
Bring me the forms I need to sign
to have her taken away.
It looks like I need
my heroic bureaucrat back.
At severely reduced pay, of course.
-Yeah!
-Better than nothing.
Can I get reduced pay too?
You got it! ln fact, severely
reduced pay all around.
Come on, wife! Let's blow this joint!
Now it's time for my song!
When I was 2
There was a tidal wave in-- Aw....
www.tvsubtitles.net