UNCER: Cash, cash, cash
for your bones.
Too many bones,
not enough cash? Call Cashbone.
Ribs, skulls, spines,
even certain tiny ear bones.
♪ The leg bone's connected
to the Cashbone. ♪
♪ Two... two, three... ♪
Sync by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
(thud)
Aw, Nibbler made
a bobo for Mama.
I'll pick it up with my
supey-dupey poopy scoopy.
(irritated sigh)
(beeping)
(electronic whirring)
Core magnetic field...
31 microteslas.
Nice.
Temperature...
Whoa! The magma P.I. is
10,000 degrees Selleck.
(scraping)
(speaking Chinese)
Leela, I am collecting data.
Could you dump that
somewhere else?
Not really.
It's highly volatile
dark matter...
and some corn.
But I'm presenting
my thesis tomorrow
and I've barely had
time to prepare.
Nonsense.
You've been my grad
student for 12 years.
You were ready six years ago.
What?!
I probably should have told you.
Anyway, the important thing
is to be relaxed tomorrow.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Do what you young people do
to unwind.
Take a joyride in your jalopy.
Wear a T-shirt
and eat a fish stick.
Go!
Okay, amigos, one teensy drink
to help Amy relax.
ALL:
Hear, hear!
Hmm... I guess
I'm still kind of nervous.
One more teensy drink
to help Amy relax.
Still a little nervous?
(burps)
She's a nervous wreck!
♪ ♪
(both laughing)
Well, I may not have a man,
but at least I've
got you, poopsie-doodle.
Leela, it's time
you and I had a talk.
A talk?!
You can't break up with me.
You're my pet.
As much as I enjoy being
the object
of your misplaced affections,
I am also
a highly sophisticated being
who longs
for intelligent conversation.
Aw, is shnookums
not feeling "shtimuwated"?
An understatement
to say the least.
It's time you treated
me with respect.
If you want to be treated like
a fellow crew member, fine,
but no more purse rides
and no more dressing you up in
your cute little sailor suit.
I keep telling you,
that's my real naval uniform.
(both moaning)
Your place or mine?
Both.
But first, this place.
Ooh... oh, my...
(stammering)
Ooh! Room for one more?
(titters)
(beeping)
(gasps)
I thought I set you for 7:15.
FEMALE VOICE: Sorry... I hooked
up with Bender last night.
Dude was all over
my snooze button.
But my doctoral exam is
in ten minutes... on Mars!
(squishing) Ew!
Kif, did you yack on the floor?
Yes, I did.
Where's your candidate,
Farnsworth?
I have a long list of
students to humiliate today.
(door opens)
You're late, Miss Wong.
(panting):
Oh, God,
this is like
one of those nightmares.
(screams)
Here, take my lab coat.
Allow me to introduce
your examining committee
in descending order
of grumpiness.
Professor Ogden Wernstrom.
Wernstrom.
Downtown Professor
of Applied Physics
Ethan "Bubblegum" Tate.
I see by your curriculum vitae
that you're a Sagittarius.
And Professor Fischerpreis
Schpeeknschpell.
The cow says...
(cow moos)
He proved that 50 years ago,
and he's been coasting
on it ever since.
I am the esteemed
Professor Morris Katz,
and you are wasting my time.
Proceed.
(clears throat)
Imagine, if you will...
Oh, God.
A gigantic spherical generator,
one that could provide
unlimited energy
because it's essentially
in perpetual motion.
(outraged scoffs)
Young lady,
have you been drinking?
Well, yes,
but that's not "revelant."
I'm talking about Earth.
Earth's the generator.
Baa.
Suppose this basketball
is the whole world.
To many young men
in the inner city, it is.
As it spins, it's producing
an enormous magnetic field.
If we could use that field
to generate electric current,
we could actually harness the
Earth's rotational ener-ener...
(sneezing):
Kerchoo!
Yes, tapping
the earth's ener-kerchoo.
Go on.
Sorry, I'm super allergic
to cats.
Professor Katz,
would you mind...?
Miss Wong, I I mind everything.
(sniffing)
You just need to polarize
the Earth's core with a huge...
static charge...
by ratcheting superconductive
wire down into...
(sneezes)
Sorry.
Enough.
The committee members
will now vote yea or nay.
Nay.
Hell, nay.
The horse says,
"Doctorate denied."
It's okay, Amy.
I don't have
a fancy degree either,
but today I'm a prominent boy
in the package delivery field.
(door opens)
Now that I am a full
and equal member of the crew,
I pledge my loyalty,
my perspicacity,
and dare I say it,
my friendship.
Leela, muzzle that skunk.
We can't stop a meeting for
some cute, fuzzy, little...
(gasps) Hey, look, a kitty cat.
(purring) You again?
(sneezes)
Get away,
you mangy ball of histamines.
You leave kitty cat alone.
(all cooing over kitty)
People, please, I'm
trying to run a business,
so I get to hold kitty.
No, me.
(overlapping chatter)
Aw, its anus looks
like an asterisk.
Captain Fuzzy Toes
reporting for duty...
I mean, cutie.
(laughter)
My best friend died
in that uniform.
I hate that cat!
If I had a spray bottle,
I'd give him such a spritzing.
I'll tell you one thing...
nothing acts that cute
without some ulterior motive.
(cute whimpering)
Aw, you want
your dipey changed?
(cute whimpering)
We'll have to watch
its every move.
Powder, please.
(trap closes)
Here's my new theory:
That is one adorable cat.
I guess I was just jealous.
(sniffs) I do miss
being Leela's shnookums.
I'm going to apologize
and hope for a pity pet.
(both gasp) Yes, my lord.
Amy and Nibbler are
a "tewwible thweat."
They must be spayed and
neutered, "wespectivewy."
(hisses)
(to Meow Mix jingle):
♪ Meow-meow, meow-meow,
meow-meow, meow-meow ♪
meow-meow, meow-meow... ♪
(deep, distorted):
♪ Meow-meow, meow-meow. ♪
(glass shatters)
The cat is evil.
We have proof.
It was summoning a saucer.
Of course it wanted
a saucer, you idiot...
a saucer of "dewicious cweam."
You fool, this isn't
about the cream.
It's pwonounced "cweam."
I'm petting mine
down to the bone.
Just stwoke its fwuffy fur.
Scwatch its fwubby chin.
Fweeble its fwooby pwow.
ALL (chanting):
Pet it, pet it...
No, no!
(sneezes)
Pet it, pet it...
NIBBLER: What do cats need
with that much yarn and cobalt?
They're doing
something downstairs.
We've got to find out what.
Where do you think
you're going, No-cat?
Uh, the basement.
I think I left
the air-hockey table on.
Without a cat,
you ain't going nowhere.
Can you at least tell us
what's going on down there?
We're certainly not building
something sinister,
if that's what you're implying.
Now, come on, Bender,
something sinister
won't build itself.
Professor Katz'
last name is Katz.
Do you think he has something
to do with these cats?
The conclusion is as
inescapable as it is moronic.
I say we pay him a visit,
and if he won't talk to us,
he'll talk to Smith & Wesson...
or perhaps
Consolidated Head Melter.
Professor Katz,
we want answers.
I warn you,
if I have to get cute,
it's gonna get ugly.
(Amy gasps)
He's dead!
Wait.
What are these
strings on his lap?
What the...?
(gasps) He isn't dead.
He's one of those
dog-operated puppets
that's been adapted
for use by a cat!
So I had my doctorate denied
by that fuzz ball?!
Bad kitty!
(door creaking)
(both gasp)
Amy: They actually built
the planetary ratchet
from my thesis!
(grunting and groaning)
(sneezing)
Uh-oh.
What the...?
(gasps)
(in Katz' voice): Well, look
what the me dragged in.
You can talk!
You can talk?
How ironic!
Two hyper-intelligent beings
both pretending to be
simple house pets.
Say, do you know Obliteron?
He pretends
to be a hamster, but...
Yeah, that's really great.
Could you please tell us
what's going on?!
What? Oh, right.
You see, my associates
and I are from the ninth planet
of the star you call Thuban.
Long ago, life there was ideal.
The sun provided plenty
of warm, dozy light.
The Chicken-Salmon roamed free.
(munching)
Yet disaster loomed.
Our planet's rotation
was gradually slowing.
At first, it seemed beneficial.
Long dark nights for sleeping,
long sunny days for sleeping.
But then, it got too hot.
(mewing)
And too cold.
(purring, shuddering)
Our top scientists went
to work.
At last, they located a planet
with the necessary orientation
and magnetic field to harness
its rotational energy.
Earth!
Indubitably.
Although we call it
Blue-Blue Shiny Ball.
In the area now known as Egypt,
my people constructed a giant,
semi-octahedral antenna
to beam Earth's
rotational energy to Thuban.
Amy:
The Great Pyramid at Giza!
HEAD CAT:
Yes.
The Egyptians viewed us
as gods,
but ironically,
that was our downfall.
They pampered us with feasts
most fancy
and vittles most tender.
We grew fat and domesticated.
(mews)
Thounds of years passed,
and our home world was nearing
total destruction.
(pained yowling)
MAN:
Shut up!
(window slamming)
But the technology
to save our planet was lost.
Lost, that is,
until I heard you speak
at Mars University.
So you called my thesis
a fat sack of barf,
and then you stole it?
Welcome to academia.
He intends to siphon off
Earth's rotational energy!
Earth will come
to a stop, and...
Half of you will cook,
and half of you will freeze.
Earth will be one big McDLT.
We just got that commercial
last year.
Oh, yeah, smarty paws?
You may have built the ratchet,
but you can't reach the core
without 4,000 miles
of superconducting wire.
(gasps) The ball of yarn!
Quite.
Even so, you'd still need
a tremendously powerful
static charge
to trigger the process.
Ever had a cat rub up
against you?
If you're propositioning me,
I'm not interested.
I'm talking
about the charge generated
when 50,000 felines
rub against a single surface.
Professor?
(loud, amplified whirring)
(mewing)
(crackling)
(whirring and crackling)
(burbling)
(whirring slows)
(rumbling)
Soon the world will
come to a stop,
and there's nothing
you can do to stop it.
The stopping of
the world, that is.
It's unstoppable.
(laughs evilly)
Excuse me.
(growling)
(all grunting, groaning)
The Earth h h is coming to a st!
Keep your eyes
on the kitties and push!
(all grunting)
These space cats seem
to be employing some form
of hypnotic hyper-cuteness.
Well, two can play at that game.
And one of them is me.
(quiet, gentle mewing)
Nibbler? Poopsie-doodle?
(Nibbler mews gently)
Mr. Winkles,
Smudge-Smudge.
Quick, dance with each other!
(lively folk music plays)
ALL:
Aw!
Aw.
Damn, they are good.
(grunting)
(loud rumbling and rattling)
We're coming to a full stop.
All cats, to your posts!
(grunting)
(rumbling stops,
then a screech)
(thudding)
(creaking)
(thud, clang)
(thudding)
Catastrophe Beach Party...
Scene One.
Cue disaster effects
and... action!
(rumbling)
(people screaming)
(glass clinking)
Cut!
That extra looked at the camera.
We'll have to do it again.
(rumbling)
(grunting)
And now to transfer
your planet's rotational energy
to my home world.
(clack)
(rumbling)
(whirring)
(blip)
(electronic pulsing)
Well, now, this calls
for a celebration.
(can-can music plays)
(grunting and groaning)
What's all this cat hair
on my sweater?
Why am I full of sand?
And Tootsie Rolls?
You were all under the spell
of those obnoxious space cats!
Enjoy being broiled alive
by the sun,
and also the dead bird
we've left in your slipper.
(evil laugh)
(hissing)
Quickly! If we turn
the ratchet the other way,
perhaps we can restart
the Earth!
(grunting)
HERMES:
It won't turn.
Push harder, Bender!
(grunts) I can't!
You should have called
my cousin, Turner.
(sighs) It's hopeless.
Even in theory,
the device can only apply
force in one direction.
Can someone open a window?
It's getting a little warm
in here.
Is that better?
(hissing)
Shmeezus, it's hot!
Why'd I have
to invent that awful device?
(crying, tears hissing)
Amy, technology isn't
intrinsically good or evil.
It's how it's used.
Like the death ray.
Maybe you're right.
I guess science has
to keep pushing forward
with the hope that...
(gasps) That's it!
Pushing forward!
Professor, I know how
to restart the Earth!
(splutters)
You can't suddenly
know something
just by assembling
a committee of words.
(gasps) That's it!
I'll assemble your committee!
The ratchet won't
turn backwards,
but what if
we kept pushing it forward?
Earth would start turning again!
Yes... the wrong direction!
(laughs)
So?
Oh.
Gentlemen, ladies,
let's get this globe trotting.
(grunting)
It's working!
Just a little faster!
But we're plotzing here!
Then look at Nibbler!
ALL:
Aw!
(grunting)
(whirring in various tones)
(whirring,
tones playing in reverse)
On the whole,
Earth society is worthless.
But they do have these things
called antique rugs
that are great for peeing on.
(rumbling)
(yowling)
(thudding)
(blip)
(cheering)
MAN (British accent):
Good show.
And though the world
is now spinning
in the wrong direction,
it's good enough.
Well done, Amy.
I'm honored to begrudgingly
present with your Ph.D.
In applied physics.
Also, some kind
of sportsmanship award
I had in my glove compartment.
Yay! I'm finally done
with school!
How's the job market?
Ruff.
Congratulations,
Dr. Wong!
(cheering)
Congratulations.
Permission to come aboard?
Granted, shnookums.
(purring)
Sync by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net