Sync and correction by Mlmlte
www.addic7ed.com
Where's the professor?
Eh, probably dead.
Already dissolving
in a bathtub, if we're lucky.
I was out on the widow's walk
keeping a hopeless vigil
for the return
of my first delivery crew.
It's been 50 years
since they disappeared.
Huh, I knew you had other crews,
but you never told us
you had a first crew.
I remember it
like it was interesting.
I had just built my new
shipping and receiving emporium,
and I scoured the hardware
store parking lot
to assemble
the finest crew imaginable.
There was Candy, the raunchy
by-the-books navigator;
Lifter, the devastatingly
handsome forklift;
and Captain Lando Tucker,
a dedicated young man
with no characteristics.
We'll deliver that
package or die trying.
Hey, it's all my favorite patients.
And also Captain Tucker.
Pow!
Whoa!
You totally got me, Dr. John.
You're hilarious.
Zoidberg was popular?
Zoidberg had hair?
I never said he had hair!
If you chose to imagine him
that way, that's your business.
Anyway,
the time came for our first delivery.
Lando, don't forget
about me and Junior.
I won't, honey.
Or die trying.
Well, crew, this is it.
That cookie bouquet
isn't going to deliver itself.
Ten...
nine and so on.
Three...
two, one...
Go, you big metal bird.
Get up there.
Incredible!
Zoidberg had friends?
It was a different time.
Everything was going smoothly
until right after that part
I was just telling you about.
Suddenly, Amanda's aunt called to say
her niece hadn't received
her cookie bouquet.
I watched the skies for weeks,
with only occasional breaks
to tend to my grief diarrhea.
Just when all hope was lost...
The ship's escape pod!
What happened up there, Johnny?
Oh, don't make me remember.
So horrible it was.
I thought you said
he didn't have hair.
Yes, but something he saw
on that mission
traumatized him so severely,
he grew hair,
just so it could turn white.
Sadly, my brave crew
was gone forever.
Oh, that poor incompetent crew.
What do you think
happened, Professor?
They were lost
in the Bermuda Tetrahedron.
That's ridiculous.
The Bermuda Tetrahedron
is just a myth.
I'm glad you're so brave in
the face of the unknown, Leela,
because, for your next mission,
you'll be flying directly through
the Bermuda Tetrahedron!
Or we could fly around it.
Of course you could.
You'd be stupid not to.
Supposing we're not stupid.
What kind of stupid mission is this?
You'll be picking up a monument
commemorating my lost crew,
to be unveiled Tuesday
at their memorial ceremony.
All the grieving families
will be there,
plus a Popsicle cart.
You can count on us, Professor.
We'll get that
monument here in time.
Hooray!
Or die trying.
What?
Here you go.
In memory of the first Planet
Express ship and its crew.
Hang on.
It shouldn't have an apostrophe.
This means "and it is crew."
What the hell's wrong with you?
It's a minor error, lady.
I mean, we're space aliens.
It's a miracle
we can even speak English.
The miracle is that
I'm not kicking your ass.
I insist you re-carve
the entire statue correctly.
Okay, okay.
Hey, Charlie, hack off
another block of ivory!
Well, the statue's perfect now.
Too bad we won't make it back in time
for the memorial service.
We'll make it.
Or die trying.
We're cutting through
the Bermuda Tetrahedron!
Whoo!
Wait, the Bermuda Tetrahedron?
I think I'm remembering
that thing I forgot.
Uh-oh, the dials are terrified.
Brace yourselves.
It's Tickle Me Elmo's Fire.
Ow! Oh!
Ow-ow-ow!
There. See?
It was no big thing.
What was that big thing?
It's a spaceship graveyard.
Why did we have to
come here at night?
Look at all these famous lost ships.
There's the Garmin!
And the TomTom!
Over there!
It's the original
Planet Express ship!
What caused all that damage?
Could it have been flavor-blasted?
We'd better investigate.
Looks like an ion storm, though.
Everyone, suit up!
Whatever happened here, that
first crew left in a hurry.
The table is still set for
a McDonald's value dinner.
I remember, I remember!
This is what traumatized me.
Such a meal to go to waste!
And with that...
I have closure.
Hey, Zoidberg, you're cockatieling.
Oh, no. Something's happening.
What's happening?
Oh, right.
And there was
a giant killer space whale.
Holy crap, it's a giant space fish!
Actually, the space whale
isn't a space fish.
It's a space mammal.
Wow, interesting.
I'm both impressed and being eaten.
Spacewalk, people!
Spacewalk for your lives!
Man, look at him go.
Like a millionaire
on a cocktail wiener.
I did it. I outran him.
Relax, friends.
Panic, jerks!
That's no ordinary space whale!
It's a four-dimensional space whale!
Of course!
And it only breaches
into our 3-D universe
to hunt and fill it's lungs
with vacuum.
Whatever its beef is,
our one mission now is
to get that monument to Earth.
to avenge the loss of that monument.
Smeesh!
He gonked off the engines.
That won't stop me.
Raise the solar sails!
I'm going after that Mobius Dick!
You've been hitting
the Red Stripe, woman!
Comport yourself, Mr. Conrad!
When we're at space,
the captain's word is law.
I could marry you and Bender
against your will, if I wanted to.
You wouldn't dare!
I've been married to worse.
Leela, I'm not doctor, but I'm afraid
you be exhibiting symptoms of illin'.
You're risking all our lives
for your own personal obsession.
There's nothing personal about this.
That thing screwed up my delivery!
This time, it's business.
♪ ♪
Maybe if I move
the compass like this,
it will somehow kill the whale.
Leela, we need to talk.
You've gone from crazy like
a fox to crazy like Fox News.
Fear not the space behemoth.
In my dreams,
I've peered beyond its eyes
and into the cackling hell
within us all.
Okay, that's a good point.
Fry's right!
Let's kill the captain
and order some strippers!
Yeah, what he said.
It's a mutiny led by Fry!
That's enough insubordination,
Mr. Fry!
String him up!
Things look bad enough without
having to look closer at them.
Look, off in the distance!
It's exhaling!
Use boaty talk!
Thar she blows!
All right, which of you space dogs
has the guts and know-how
to harpoon that whale?
I spent a semester in
Africa harpooning giraffes.
And giraffes are basically
just land space whales.
Ms. Wong, you have the 'poon.
Oh, God, I'm having
a Serengeti flashback.
Die, you dirty giraffe!
Well, I got it.
Now what, Captain?
You know, I'm not sure.
I guess I thought whales died
when you harpooned them.
Don't worry.
I'll drop the anchor.
Oh!
Aw! Ouch!
She's diving
into the fourth dimension.
We have to cut the rope.
Negative, Sailor Moon.
We're going for a sleigh ride.
I can see sideways in time.
Hey, I see CGI.
Poop.
Ah, yeah.
♪ Bender, Bender, Bender ♪
♪ Bender, Bender, Bender... ♪
Aw.
That was the greatest
unaccountably infinite bunch
of guys I ever met.
Look out!
It's pulling us through
a field of spacebergs.
Stupid rocks.
Think they're so great.
Well, they are giant diamonds.
Come to Papa.
A lot of Bender
fell out of the crow's nest.
We need to cut the line.
Enough of your mad obsession
with Bender, Fry.
We've got to murder
that whale or die trying.
This has gone too far.
Bender's one of Planet Express's
most expensive appliances.
And he's in trouble.
That's it. I warned you.
Fry, Zoidberg, I now pronounce
you man and...
Aw, so close.
Unsit me, Mr. Conrad.
We can't let the whale win.
Hi-- yah!
You're all too weak.
I can see that now.
So I'll have to be my own crew.
Understood?
You've gone mad, Captain.
That's enough out of me.
Now come on,
I got to find that whale.
I found him.
With my Oxo Good Grips Cheese Knife,
I stab at thee.
You do know I'm stabbing
at thee, right?
Hello.
Think, Zoidberg.
You must remember something.
No, nothing.
For all I know, our friends
could have been eaten
by some kind of crazy space whale.
Damn that Bermuda Tetrahedron.
It's taken my latest crew
just as it took my first one.
Not to mention
those single socks
from the dryer, am I right?
Shut up, Zoidberg.
Oh, Zoidberg, the grieving relatives
will be gathered here tomorrow
in need of comfort.
And with no stone monument,
they may well demand
that I refund their admission fees.
Where are we?
In the belly of the beast.
Like that Bible guy who got swallowed
by the whale-- Pinocchio.
This is all Obsessy Bessy's fault.
Right on, sister.
We should be back
at Planet Express right now,
hiding from work in the ceiling.
But no!
For the last time, I'm not obsessed.
I just want this whale
to die, die, die!
Uh-oh. What's that
loud digesting sound?
Holy crap!
Four dimensional bowels!
Einstein was right.
Why?! Why?!
Also what and how?!
The great fish has chosen
you for a higher purpose.
It's a great mammal.
See? It's got whiskers.
And I saw it lactating earlier.
Wait, who said that?
I was once Lando Tucker--
captain of the first
Planet Express ship.
Ew!
I'm Turanga Leela--
captain of the current
Planet Express ship.
What's going on?
It's very simple.
Well, actually it's very complicated.
Luckily, I'm here to explain it.
You see, this space whale
feeds on obsession.
Wow. Are you gross looking.
Go on.
- The great space serpent...
- Mammal.
...figured out long ago
that no one's more obsessed
than space captains.
Oh! Oh!
What are these things?!
Get away!
The whale's nearly sucked me dry.
It'll need a new source
of obsession once I'm gone.
How many times do I have
to tell other people--
I'm not obsessed.
The whale is obsession, Leela.
And you are the whale!
I am not the whale!
All I wanted was to complete
my delivery.
Is that too much to ask?
One Chicken Pickin' delivery?
This whale's gonna pay.
It can't escape what
it already is-- me!
I am the whale!
See?
50 years, Junior.
50 years of crippling sorrow.
Popsicles here. Can't mourn
the dead without a Popsicle.
You think a Popsicle
gonna bring my daughter back?
No, sir.
Aha! You just talked
yourself out of a sale.
Poor Amy.
My days of joy and luck are over.
Guess I got to quit that club.
I can't believe our Leela's gone.
You always think you're going to disappear
in space before your children.
Welcome, everyone.
What a pleasure to see
so many miserable faces.
Mmm! Lemony!
I had intended to unveil a
beautiful stone memorial today.
But due to the recent tragedy,
I humbly ask you to join me
in a simple prayer.
No refunds!
Shut up and bow your heads!
O, mighty Isis...
Oh, no.
My deal is doing the thing.
Good Lord, it's some kind
of interdimensional space whale.
I just remembered, that's the guy.
Oy, now with the horror hair.
Popsicles. Fill your gaping
mouth with a Popsicle.
Leela, you're alive.
Is that how you and
your friends are dressing now?
Hello, everyone.
I suppose you're wondering
why my flesh has melded with
that of a giant space whale.
I'll admit to a polite interest.
At first I was consumed
by a dark obsession
to kill the whale.
Then I was consumed by the whale.
That sounds clever,
but it doesn't explain much.
Shut up, Zoidberg.
Okay.
You see, beneath my obsession
lay an even deeper obsession.
An obsession so strong,
it allowed me to overpower
the beast's will and pilot it
through space and time.
An obsession with completing
my delivery...
...delivery, delivery,
delivery, delivery, delivery...
Get your...
Poor Lando.
This is just how
I want to remember him.
Too bad, 'cause he's still alive.
Lando?
Told you I'd be back.
You've grown, Junior.
I'm 61.
I don't know him.
What else you got?
They haven't aged a day.
The whale must have
some kind of Mobius colon
that endlessly recycles
time and space.
Yep. That stands up to scrutiny.
I should have listened to my crew.
That space whale wasn't a monster.
It was the obsession of me
and others like me
that made it into a monster.
Mainly you.
On the other hand,
the stupid fish did eat us.
You guys want to do this?
Oh, you know it!
So, Johnny,
are we going to pick up
where we left off?
Eh.
Sync and correction by Mlmlte
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net