Sync by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
Listen up, people!
As long as nothing happens
for the next 15 minutes,
our insurance
will be reinstated.
So let's just sit quietly
and run out the clock.
A giant sausage!
Oh, God, no! Get out of here,
you horrific sausage!
Wait. Isn't today the parade?
It's just a giant balloon!
Giant balloon?!
See, buddy, it's not so scary.
I feel better now.
Why are so many different
parades smooshed together?
It's the Parade Day Parade.
What's Parade Day?
It used to be that every group
in New New York
wanted their own parade.
Why, when I was a boy,
we had a parade every day.
Those were dark times.
Now we just combine them all
into one big Parade Day
Parade and get it over with.
Hey, look--
A fog is rolling in.
No, that's just
the Jamaican pride float.
Looks like it's speeding up.
Oh, no! It's within
munching distance
of the Doritos float!
Thank you. Thank you.
Kif, you're slacking off
on my waving arm.
Oh, no. It's heading
right for those two nerds!
Whoa. Sweet
shirt, dude.
Thanks. I have
another one that says
"Paleontologists Do It
In The Dirt".
I'm a paleontologist.
I'll save
one of you!
Oh, honey, I dig you so much.
Thank you for saving my
stupidly-dressed husband.
You're a hero.
A hero, indeed.
What's your name, son?
I don't know. Fry?
Ladies and gentlemen, I'm proud
to associate myself
with a true hero.
Mr. Fry, allow me
to present you with
the keys to the city!
This one's for the deadbolt,
this is for the top lock.
I think this one's
for the knob.
The city's in a
bad neighborhood.
Care to say a few words, son?
Uh... heroes don't do drugs.
Except for Drugman, I guess.
I hereby declare
that henceforth,
this Saturday shall be known
as Fry-Day!
It sure was nice of the mayor's
wife to have sex with me.
You.
What?
You could have saved
a robot, but instead,
you saved a human.
Do you think human life is more
precious than robot life?
No, no.
Well, yes, actually.
That's it.
I'm killing myself.
Oh, Lord.
Don't try to talk me out of it!
Well?
Bender, you always say
you're going to kill yourself,
but you almost never do.
Yeah. Last time you went
to the suicide booth,
you ended up dating
it for six months.
How is Lynn, by the way?
Living in Oregon
with her crazy mother.
See you at my funeral, suckers!
Kill me, please,
and make it splatter!
With pleasure.
Bender.
Lynn?
Wow, you look great.
Fat, but great.
I thought you were in Oregon.
My mom tried
to commit suicide in me.
I don't want to talk about it.
Well, tell your mom
I said hello,
and it's been nice, uh,
catching up with you.
Let's get this show on the road.
Oh, no.
You're going to die, all right,
but it won't be suicide.
It'll be murder.
Missed me!
He did it!
He actually did it this time.
No way, mon.
He's faking it.
He really is gone!
Everyone, put on
your taking-off caps.
Our what?
It's a sign of respect, you savage!
Poor, nasty, mean old Bender.
I can't believe
we'll never hear
his evil laugh again.
I miss him so much.
There, there, Fry.
He may be gone,
but he'll always be
with us as a trash can.
Look at that loser
getting garbage dumped in him.
Glad I'm not him, whoever he is.
Fry, as his only friend,
you should have first pick
of body parts.
Just don't pick his nose!
What's wrong with you guys?
This is comedy gold.
He always had my back.
So I'll take his arm.
As a back-scratcher.
I love you, Bender!
Somebody hand me a bolt cutter.
Hey dip-schlitz,
that's not me.
I'm right here. Hello?!
Pay attention to me!
Why can't anybody hear
my witty remarks?
This is hell.
You wish.
Robot devil?
You can hear me?
Why is everyone
else ignoring me?
Isn't it obvious, Bender?
Yeah, I guess it is.
You're dead!
What?!
I thought I just had
laryngitis and antigravity.
Oh, come down to my office,
and I'll explain everything.
So what's happening to me?
And I'll take my answer
in any form but a song.
Oh, you're no fun.
You see, Bender, it's simple.
You're a ghost.
A g-g-g-ghost?
No, just the regular kind.
Because you killed yourself,
you're in limbo.
Your software was exported
to the computational cloud.
A-doy. Wait. A-doy?
Your disembodied program
is now running
on the wireless network
shared by all machinery.
Cut to the chase, smokey.
How do I get out of limbo?
That's the laughy part.
You can't!
You're stuck
in an infinite loop.
An infinite loop?
I don't have time for that!
Man, this is all Fry's fault.
Fry? I hate that guy.
We once traded hands.
They still stink of candy corn.
Get this. That jerk said
human life was more
valuable than robot life.
What?! After all
you've done for him?
Fry must die!
I know. Right?
I'd murder him good,
if only I was still alive.
Hmm. Bender, would you like
to make a deal?
I'm not stupid.
So, yes, absolutely.
What have I agreed to?
I'll return you to your body
after you use
your ghostly powers
to scare Fry to death.
That sounds fair and also fun.
I like
that there's no catch this time.
But, wait.
There's a catch. Crap!
If you fail, you'll spend
eternity here in robot hell.
Which, as luck would have it,
is where I rehearse my band.
Hit it, boys!
♪ Cigars are evil,
you won't miss 'em... ♪
Okay, I'll do it, I'll do it!
Just stop the damn music!
Scare Fry to death? Huh.
I could do that in my sleep.
What, are you deaf?
Hmm, soap.
I know Fry's afraid that.
Maybe he'll die if I rub him
all over with it, real slow.
Whoa, sick!
My software can control
electronics!
What the...?
No! Not the armpits!
Winter's coming!
As you can see,
since Bender's death,
requests to bite
one's shiny metal ass
are down 98%.
Do you mind doing that later?
Bite my shiny metal ass.
Help! I was attacked
in my bathroom!
By my bathroom!
I'm being haunted by a ghost!
Fry, you're just upset because
you drove Bender to suicide.
Here. Take your mind off it with
this soothing relaxation balls.
All right.
I got him all heebie-jeebied
with my bathroom of horrors.
One more good scare,
and I'll be out of limbo.
Oh. Did someone say limbo.
Hold onto your dookie.
It's about to get spooky!
I'm telling you, something
supernatural is happening.
I'm scared to death!
Stop being ridiculous.
There's no such thing as
whatever you're saying.
Whoa, maybe you're right.
I only meant to slap you twice.
All I know is, I've got
a ghost that needs busting.
Who you gonna call?
Gho...
The number you have dialed
has been lame since 1989.
Now do you believe me?
Oh, fuff, enough of your
superstitious nonsense.
I'm sure that
whatever is happening
can be explained by science.
Let the séance begin.
I said science!
The veil is lifting.
I am gazing into the
spirit world, and nothing.
You said something
about a buffet?
I'm right here,
you lazy shyster.
Wait, I'm sensing something.
I'm rich.
Is it a ghost? There's no such thing
as ghosts, you donkey-monkey.
It's a robot ghost.
A robot ghost?
What robot would want
to haunt me?
Me, dumbass.
Bender, Bender, Bender, Bender!
Ah, tell him,
you baggy old crone.
Finally.
Any more ridiculous ideas?
Hallelujah.
I'm here to conduct
the exorcism
and avail myself of the buffet.
Can I get an amen
and a goodly helping
of Scruffy's famous
corn biscuits?
Right away, Reverend.
Oh, Lord.
I got the too-much-macaroni
sweats.
Now, where is
this alleged apparition?
Might be a problem with your
circuit breaker. See you.
Please, I'm under constant
attack by machinery.
I can't sleep, I can't think,
I can't even think.
Very well.
This sacramental firewall
scans for
and removes ghostware
in a 20-foot radius.
Bring it on, holy man.
Carry this at all times and
the demon cannot harm you.
It also keeps cats off the
sofa... by killing 'em.
Ah... so quiet, so peaceful.
Time to lower my guard
even for a minute.
Heart attack.
Yep, I was right.
Okay, Beelzy, Fry's dead.
Aah, a ghost!
Oh, it's you.
A deal's a deal, so
give me my body back.
Fry's dead, you say?
Funny, that's not what it says
on his Wikipedia page.
Survived a heart attack?!
Damn you,
Obama-care!
I'm afraid your heart
has suffered a lot of damage,
Mr. Fry,
and my cleavage isn't helping.
Not helping him.
One more sudden shock
will kill you.
Sudden?
That's just the kind
of one more shock
I was planning.
The machines-- They're after me.
You're suffering
from machine phobia.
Your only hope is to go
to the Amish Home World,
where no machines are allowed.
I guess it's for the best.
The only machine
I'll ever miss is...
Bender.
Say what?
Now that he's gone,
I realize how valuable
a robot life can be,
when it belongs
to my best friend.
That's the closest thing
to "Bender is great"
that anyone besides me
has ever said.
Final boarding call
for Flight 38
to the Amish Home World.
As a reminder,
passengers are limited
to two carry-on butter churns.
I'm sorry, Fry, I'm sorry.
Wait for your ghost-buddy.
Brother Fry, thou hast visitors.
Hello. Hi, Fry. Hello.
Hey, how have you been?
Hi there.
Well, yank my beard.
This be a surprise.
How are you, Fry?
Thank you for asking, English.
My life is simple but plain,
and though Bender be gone,
somehow I feel
he's still with me.
I sure am, Brother Fry.
Yo, big bonnet, move your ugly
but modest head covering.
Oh, right, you can't hear me.
Oh, I hear you loud and clear.
You're not Granny Hester.
What have you done
with Granny Hester?!
She's naked but unharmed.
And now, Bender, it's time
to fulfill your
end of the deal.
Sorry, I'm not going
to kill Fry.
Take me to hell
for all eternity,
just as long as my little
bearded meatbag gets to live.
That he will not, for you see,
it is your fate to kill him.
Says you.
I would never kill Fry,
not even to save my own life.
But, Bender, isn't
a robot life worth
ever so much more
than a human life?
Of course not.
What idiot thinks that?
You.
You're using my
own words against me.
Go to hell!
Soon enough, but
first the killing.
Have you noticed that animals
are sometimes spooked
by robot ghosts?
So what?
I hate animals.
Run for your life, Fry!
Move your ham flaps!
He can't hear you, Bender.
I'm afraid your friend
is about to be fully
buckminstered!
Oh, yeah?
I'll just jump into a machine
and get his attention that way.
Ah, but there aren't
any machines on this planet.
There's one,
you rusty old dummy.
Wha...?!
Hey, no fair.
Occupado.
Ow, what are you doing?
And Scruffy's buffet--
How's that going?
Fry, Fry,
look out for that bowling barn.
Bender, is that thou?
I... love... you.
Did you see that?
Are you okay?
What just happened?
Uh, well, I think
the Robot Devil said he loved me
in Bender's voice
wearing Granny Hester's clothes.
I want to go home.
You still lose, Bender.
You failed to kill Fry,
so you're banished to hell.
I get a new body,
and you get to be
a translucent chump
till the end of time.
Big deal.
I saved my friend.
As far as I'm concerned, I won.
Oh, really?
♪ You may find your victory
Pyrrhic when subjected ♪
♪ To this lyric
for a trillion years ♪
♪ Or so. ♪
Yeah.
Hey, where are you going?!
I don't know and I don't care.
Yay, I'm back.
Wait, this is my stop.
Oy, this guy.
Bender, for your selfless act
in saving Fry,
I am pleased to welcome you
to Robot Heaven.
Shut up, God!
Beg pardon?
I want to go back to Robot
Earth-- I mean regular Earth.
Ow, hey, stop that.
I command you, you jerk.
Eh, just get out.
Whew, I've been through
the adventure of a lifetime.
I'm back, baby.
You're back from the dead?
I'm back from lots of stuff.
Oh, Bender, Bender,
I missed you so much.
Hey, wait, did you haunt me?
Sync by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net