You're
taking a vacation from normalcy.
A weird, motel
where the bed is stained
with mystery,
and there's also some mystery
floating in the pool.
Your key card may not open
the exercise room
because someone smeared mystery
on the lock.
But it will open...
The scary door.
Submitted for your Emmy
A popular senator
with unpopular ideas.
There is no such thing
as space aliens!
Oh?
How can you be so sure
them aliens ain't
already among us?
I'll tell you how.
Because you are one!
Hey, I was watching that!
The saints just needed
a field goal to tie!
Lrrr, you lazy ruler
of the planet Omicron Persei 8!
You said you would
conquer a planet today,
but you have not even
shed your skin yet!
Yes, NDND, I heard you
the first hundred times.
I'll conquer something
tomorrow after I fuel up
on one of your disgusting
egg-white omelets!
You want yolks? Fine.
Enjoy your stroke.
Ha-ha-ha! I am conquering earth.
Not so fast, invader x!
Here comes delivery-boy man!
Laser eye power!
Hand magnet power!
Yay, I'm unbuckled!
Stop it, you hero!
Reverse time power!
It's earlier now.
Mmm...
So what do you think
of my comic?
After I leave here,
I'm getting a memory enema.
If I might offer some
constructive criticism...
There was never any real peril.
I mean, the delivery guy has,
like, 30 super powers.
Well, that's because
he was bitten
by a radioactive superman!
This is wonderful!
It is, isn't it?
Wait, those are the ads.
These X-ray specs will
really take the guesswork out
of surgery.
No more chopping
blindly in the goop.
Don't waste your
allowance, Zoidberg.
This stuff is
butt-grade crap.
Amuse your friends
with real vomit.
Throw your voice.
Sea monkeys.
Throw your sea monkeys.
My disintegrator ray
really works.
But that's you.
That's how I know it's bunkum.
The Farnsworth novelty
disintegrator ray is
nothing more than a
common teleporter ray.
Pfft! Worthless toy!
I'm sick of being critiqued
by nitpicking nerds.
I'm taking this
to a comic book convention!
Shmeesh, it's crowded.
Good thing everyone is
freshly bathed and groomed.
Ooh!
What are you doing?!
That's the rare Zapp Brannigan
with recording session blooper!
don't
tell me how to do the line.
It sickens me.
But the sign said there was
a mint in the box.
Thank you. Okay, thanks, thanks.
Settle, settle down!
So anyway, we're really excited
to show you guys the pilot
for our new series.
It's set in the year 4000,
and we call it Futurella!
Wow.
Fox has really streamlined
the process.
Matt will now take questions.
But please,
only about Futurella,
not the Simpsons.
Yes? The robot standing on
the small child over there?
Ooh! Ooh!
Yeah, uh, when are you going
to make a second Simpsons movie?
Oh!
Mr. Aragonés, I'm a big
fan of your cartoons
and your moustache.
You want it? Take it!
It's brought me nothing
but misery.
Wow, thanks.
Ay-yi-yi!
If you could just quiet down,
I wanted to get your opinion
of my comic book.
Señor, anyone who still writes
comics is a hero to me.
Mmm, it stinks.
But, um, I do like the tiny
doodles in the margins.
That's just some relish
from a hot dog I found.
Attention, lady and gentlemen,
the costume contest
is about to begin.
The costume contest.
The costume contest...!
What the hell are you
supposed to be?
Every nerd's fantasy, baby.
Next up, contestant number 36!
Contestant 36, everyone!
Next up, contestant 37.
I am Lrrr,
ruler of the planet...
Hold on a second,
let me just get this.
I am Lrrr,
ruler of the planet Omicron
Persei 8.
You are hereby conquered!
Please line up in order
of how much beryllium it takes
to kill you!
Damn, that's a good costume.
Next up, contestant 38!
I don't understand.
Why are the humans still
eating their soft pretzels
instead of surrendering?
They're probably just waiting
for Joss Whedon.
Joss Whedon's here?!
Wait a minute.
You look familiar.
Yeah, you almost ate me once.
I was in your mouth
for five minutes.
Leela?
And the winner is...
Nerdgasma!
Whoo!
I got fruit boobs!
What's the use?
Now what?
I send you out to
conquer a planet,
and all you bring back
is J.J. Abrams' face?
I thought you'd like it.
You haven't even tried it on!
I might dress up in a face
if you ever took me
anywhere nice!
Oh, boy, here we go.
I built this castle
with my own two slaves!
What are you gonna do,
kick me out?
I am Lrrr, ruler of the planet
Omicron Persei 8!
May I crash on your couch?
So he just showed up
unannounced,
raided the liquor cabinet,
sprayed urine on the ceiling,
and passed out?
And the walls.
Yeah, leave me alone!
My wife hates me and planetary
conquest has become a chore.
There, there.
You're just having
a midlife crisis.
Midlife crisis, eh?
Lrrr demands the comfort of
pop-psychological platitudes!
Look, Hoss,
your wife threw you out.
That's your license
to be a jerk.
Do whatever the hell you want,
then walk away
and light a cigar.
Don't listen to him, Lrrr.
Bender may seem happy...
But long-term,
you need to reinvest in
your relationship with NDND.
Yes, it's clear what I must do.
I like it.
I'm thinking we need
to downplay those
hideous growths on your head.
Horns are a sign of virility.
Also, they house my testes.
I'm thinking horn extensions.
You need some arm candy.
It's the perfect accessory
for out-of-shape middle-aged
creeps like you.
Yeah, I said it!
What's your type, Borgnine?
Big and angry.
Look, Brah,
you're just not gonna find
a lot of hot, gigantic
Omicronian babes
in this solar system.
There's one!
Hey, cool cape.
Where'd you get that?
What, this old thing?
Ah, I murdered my father.
My name's Lrrr, ruler
of the planet Omicron Persei 8.
I am called grrl.
Of the planet Omicron Persei 8?
That is a pretty name!
What's on the TV tonight?
Oh, wait, I don't care
'cause I got a date!
I know it's not what
you want to hear,
but I think this is a mistake.
Leela's right.
That's not what
you want to hear.
What you want to hear is
that I fixed my comic book!
Now the hero is more relatable
because he has no ridiculous
powers.
Let's watch, shall we?
One more step
and little miss constructive
criticism here gets it!
Oh, yeah?
I may be just a simple delivery
boy with no super powers,
so there's nothing I can do.
Okay.
So? Give me
your honest praise.
Fry, I've now seen
two comic books,
so listen to me.
Why should I care about the hero
when all he does is cry?
Mmm, that dinner
was a worthy foe.
Yes, we shall not see
its like again.
So, um...
Uh, uh...
Um, I'm sorry.
I-I haven't done this
for a while.
I just part-way out
of a bad relationship.
Maybe I should take this off.
You're a human?!
Only physically!
I'm a cross-species dresser.
Wait. You're
an actual Omicronian?
Oh, God, oh, God,
what have I done?
This is so hot!
Conquer me, Lrrr!
Sharpen your horns on
my scaly thorax!
I want to go home,
but NDND would never
take me back now.
NDND just wants
To feel like you're listening
to her nagging.
Is there anything she's
been riding your ass about?
Mmm... conquering things,
I guess.
I could conquer earth,
kill all humans.
That's a thought.
No. We don't need
a war of the worlds.
That's it. We need a
war of the worlds.
I'll call Orson Welles.
Dork calling Orson.
You're asking me,
the renowned spokesman
for Paul Masson wine,
to recreate my brilliant
1938 radio broadcast
merely to deceive and impress
the wife of this
skinny reptile?
Sorry. Never mind.
I'll do it for free.
Ladies and gentlemen,
we interrupt our program
of the Jonas brothers
and their orchestra
to bring you a special bulletin.
We interrupt our program
of the Jonas brothers
and their orchestra
to bring you a special bulletin.
I'm speaking to you
from the hickory farms
in Grover's mall, new Jersey,
through a mouthful
of summer sausage.
Mmm. Where I hardly know
where to begin.
Mmm!
A huge spacecraft,
piloted by a devastatingly
handsome...
Now, how in God's name do I
know what the fellow looks like
if he's inside a ship
miles in the air?
It's just foolish on its face.
If you want
the cheese log,
you'll read what I wrote.
Very well. I shall comply.
I'm getting reports that cities
across the globe are being
destroyed by this noble invader,
whose good looks
are apparently discernible
across vast distances
and through solid metal.
But wait,
the leader of the attack
is swaggering out of his ship
and up to a convenient
nearby microphone.
Now, why couldn't I have just
described his appearance
at this point?
This is the type of thing
I'm talking about.
People of earth, I am Lrrr,
conqueror of your planet.
Cue screams.
You will now remove your skulls
and play dodgeball with them
for my amusement.
Ooh... I could swear his horns
have gotten longer.
Sir, I've intercepted
an earth broadcast.
Put it up on the zenith.
Earth is conquered,
the destruction
of civilization complete.
Now stay tuned
for little orphan Annie.
To hell with
little orphan Annie!
We've got to do something.
What's that, honey?
How many dead?
Uh, I don't know.
Uh, 80 million?
Okay. I love you, too.
That was NDND.
She's taking me back!
I'm sorry I've been
so difficult.
So, you thought you could
conquer us so easily, eh?
Nice job.
We surrender.
Earth is yours.
Damn, I'm good.
Now, may I please have
that cheese log?
Oh, glorious conqueror,
permit me to offer up
a sacrifice.
How about this?
Hey!
Yeah, he'll do.
Come on, Lrrr.
Show's over.
Fine. Okay.
About this conquering thing...
Funny story...
Hello...
Lrrr.
Lrrr, put a stop
to this right now.
Okay. Okay. Quit nagging.
Lrrr, why are you
yelling softly
with the
purple-furred one?
Uh, it's nothing, my queen.
He messed up my hair.
I'm missing a leg.
We fought like hell, sir,
but in the end, we caved
like a house of soufflé cards.
Got it. Peace with honor.
Well, I resign again.
Come, Nixon.
Introduce me to
the kitchen staff.
I must lay down the law
about Lrrr's low-sodium diet.
You've got
to tell her the truth.
And lay off the salted peanuts.
I'm just trying to get the
leg taste out of my mouth.
Lrrr, I'm in here now,
not out there!
Give me a little time.
With a lady like NDND,
one must use finesse.
Uh, coming, gigantums.
Mmm. That's crisp.
Yes, but no more so than your
squamous dorsal plates
in the moonlight.
Ooh...
I am experiencing arousal.
My organs are moving
into position.
Ooh.
NDND, there's something
I've got to tell you.
What is it? Is
there someone else?
What? Oh, no, no, it's about
this takeover of earth.
It's, it's...
The spark that
reignited our marriage?
Yes, exactly.
Good night.
Oh, lord, now what?
I couldn't tell her the truth.
Look, you scaly crybaby,
you do what I say
and you do it now!
I knew it!
Frying pans,
cast-iron frying pans.
It's not what it looks like.
What do I do?
Do what I say.
Tell her!
Tell me what?
Give me the heavy one.
The invasion was all a fake.
I just wanted to impress you.
You lied?
What else have you
been hiding from me?
What else?
Nothing else.
I still want you, Lrrr,
ng to fight for you.
All I got left is a
colander and a pie pan.
Lrrr?
Look, we only had one date.
I barely mated with her.
Whatever.
I harbor no resentment
against her.
What I want to know is
what is up between you
and bossy boots here.
Her?
She's just a bossy friend.
Exactly.
She nagged you, tormented you,
and pushed you around.
That is my job!
This must be settled.
I demand the ancient ritual of
rrmmr-Mr-fr-mrh
or consequences.
Rrmmr-Mr-fr-mrh or what?
Let the ritual begin.
The rules are the same
Lrrr must simply choose
between myself and Leela.
Fine, hurry up.
By shooting the one he rejects.
Whoa!
Lrrr, I'm getting angry.
Don't you go through with this.
She is not the boss of you.
I am the boss of you.
Uh, um, oh.
Leela's going to die.
What would delivery-boy man do?
I-I do not want
to shoot anybody.
You never want to do anything!
Oh, nag, nag, nag.
You want me to stop
nagging? Then shoot me.
Oh, you'd like that,
wouldn't you?
Beats staring
at your fat ass on the couch.
Oh, yeah?
I'll show you.
Ray-blocking power.
Fry.
Lrrr, you were willing to
shoot that bossy temptress.
You really do value my
nagging above all others.
Good night, dumb prince.
Come back, Lrrr!
I want to have your popplers!
There'll never be
anyone but you!
Hello.
Of course I'll marry you.
Wait, what the shmell happened?
I thought NDND disintegrated
you with this ray gun.
Pfft, it's just
a cheap teleporter.
I bought it out of the back
of a comic book.
Cha-Ching!
The teleporter gun?
That means Fry might still be...
Fry?
Is this him?
Fry, you're alive.
Not only that.
I now know exactly
how to end my comic book.
Let's watch.
Say good-bye
to your forehead
'cause I'm going
to shoot you in it.
Not if I leap
in front of your death ray,
and I am going to do that.
Jumping sound!
I didn't shoot yet.
As usual,
your delivery arrived too soon.
Oh, delivery-boy man,
you saved me by random chance.
Don't thank random chance.
Thank my meteor-wishing power
with your lips.
Mmm...
Good ending...
not great.
Sync by n17t01 - Corrected by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net