Sync and correction by Mlmlte
♪ ♪
(drill whirring)
(kids grunting and laughing)
I got one!
Okay, kids.
Put away the dust motes
till tomorrow.
It's story time.
- Oh, boy!
- Yay! Ooh!
Today's storyteller
is a space captain
who grew up right here
at the orphanarium.
Welcome back the bed-wetter
of Building D, Turanga Leela.
Hi, kids.
What book would you
like me to read first?
We don't got books no more.
- What?
- He means "anymore."
Look, sometimes
you got to choose
between eating and reading,
so they ate the books.
Just make something up.
Make something up?
Um, okay...
Once upon a time,
there was a... a...
Princess?
Yes! That!
(kids gasping)
A... one-eyed princess
in a long, flowing...
tank top.
And she lived in
a magical one-room...
Castle?
Yeah, if you believe
the listing agent.
Anyhow, one day,
the princess went off to,
uh, tell a story.
And then that's exactly
what she did do that.
And they all lived
happily ever after.
The end.
Miss Leela?
I have a question.
- Yes, Albert?
- That story was bad.
That's not really a question.
That wasn't really a story.
I'm sorry, kids.
I'm not a natural storyteller.
But I promise I'll make
up a better story
and come back again.
Please don't.
See you soon.
I'm sure I've got
a great kids' story in me.
I just need to think of three
of some kind of animal.
Concentrate, Leela, concentrate.
(trombone plays "When the Saints
Go Marching In")
Fry, I'm writing here.
Do you have to play that?
Yes.
It's the only song I know.
Look, friends.
I accidentally learned
to tap dance.
(cans clanging,
trombone playing)
Zoidberg, I'm trying to...
(clock beeping)
Time for my 4:21 daiquiri!
(trombone continues playing)
(blender whirring loudly)
Guys, guys, guess who just
got commissioned as a tugboat?
(whistle blows)
Oh, yeah!
Pachinko break!
MACHINE:
Tokyo crazy balls! Yes!
(overlapping noises continue)
Oh, good, Leela.
You're here.
I'd like to describe
my foot pain.
My left has a sharp jabbing
throb near the bunion,
while the other's got
a searing pain like gout.
Maybe it's too much albumin because
of gravity...
(groans)
Even if I had a pen,
I couldn't write
under these conditions.
I'm going to some other planet
where I can concentrate.
Searing, searing pain
that feels as if
it were in a vice.
(loud whooshing)
Well, that was rude.
(whistle blows)
(door opens)
Warden Vogel.
I have a new story
for the children.
I'm sure they'll like it
more than my last one.
They liked hunger cramps
more than your last one.
Anyhow, you'll have to wait.
The kids are busy right now.
Oh, is the
organ-harvesting clown here?
Nah, Rusty comes
on Tuesdays now.
Today it's the owner of
the Tickleodeon Kids Network.
Okay, kids, get ready to be
subjected to our new fall shows.
Mr. Funny-Bunny here
will gauge your reaction
by bombarding your brains
with harmless snuggle rays.
(warbling)
He gives me a nice,
warm feeling in my eyeballs.
♪ ♪
DIGITAL VOICE:
♪ Popular Slut Club. ♪
Oh, my God.
There's Jake Finkelberg!
He's so hot.
I wish he wasn't my brother.
DIGITAL VOICE:
♪ Popular Slut Club. ♪
ANNOUNCER: Look! Up on
the drive-thru menu!
It's Captain Mega Meat
and his young ward,
Bottomless Boy.
Hurry, Captain!
A skinny kid needs our help.
Super-size me!
(belches)
ANNOUNCER:
From the Rowdy Roddy Piper
Daycare Center
in Glasgow, Scotland,
it's Extreme Toddler Wrestling!
♪ ♪
Thanks
for the brain scans, kids.
Don't have any children for
the next couple of days.
All right, boys and
girls, enough fun.
Your old friend Leela is back
with a brand-new story.
Hi. It's great to be back.
I think you'll enjoy this one.
(all groaning)
Please.
Can't we just get
our organs harvested?
It's about
some cute little creatures
from a land
called Rumbledy-Hump.
Kids, let's meet the Humplings!
♪ ♪
♪ My name is Ladybuggle ♪
♪ And I huggle all my friends ♪
♪ I'm a silly spring
named Doingg ♪
♪ And my bouncing never ends ♪
Doingg, doingg, doingg.
♪ They call me
Princess Num-Num ♪
♪ I'm as sweet as sticky buns ♪
♪ I'm Feffernoose ♪
Hello.
♪ I'm scared of everyones. ♪
Oh, Feffernoose.
(muffled)
What about me?
Hey, it's Garbly.
Everyone loves him
'cause they can't
understand him.
(muffled):
It's nice to meet you.
♪ We're here to make you
laugh and think ♪
♪ And smile and learn and sing ♪
♪ And laugh and learn and smile
and think ♪
♪ And other happy things. ♪
(music ends)
(all cheering)
Say more things like that.
Okeydoke.
One sunny, funny day,
there was an unfamiliar visitor
in Rumbledy-Hump.
♪ Today we learned
that folks are not ♪
♪ As different as they seem ♪
♪ The space gorilla's
just like us ♪
♪ Although I breathe chlorine. ♪
(kids cheering)
Wow, I can't believe you
'maginated all that stuff.
Will you come back again
and tell us more stories?
And also adopt us all?
Of course
I'll tell you more stories.
I'll go think some up right now.
(scanner warbling)
(digital squeaking)
Holy moly!
Lady, you don't know me,
but my name is
Abner Doubledeal.
Wait, I know you.
You're Abner Doubledeal.
I brain-scanned those little
nose-pickers during your story,
and, sister,
their enjoyment glands
were squirting
like Broadway roadkill!
Aw, they were?
Say, you seem
like a smart mark.
How'd you like to make
it into a TV show?
Sign here on this, uh...
Supercuts coupon.
I don't know.
Don't I need a degree
to write gibberish for toddlers?
Come on, Miss Leela.
Don't be a fraidy cat
like Feffernoose.
Okay. I'll do it
to show you kids
you can succeed at anything,
if you just luck out
hard enough.
Welcome to the glamorous,
big-money world
of basic cable TV!
I'm going to need
that pen back.
Working on a real TV
show is so exciting.
I'm on a mostly natural high.
These costumes are gonna make it
hard to go to the bathroom.
I'm not having any problem.
We're shooting in five minutes,
and this Leela broad hasn't
even delivered a script yet!
Sweet zombie Jesus,
like it's not hard enough
to make a freakin' TV show
for under 50 bucks.
Damn it.
I'll call you back, Grandma.
Nice of you to show up, toots.
I mean that sincerely.
It's just that I'm in show biz.
Sorry, I went to my
quiet place to write.
Here's the script.
Ach! You writers
make me sick.
Nice job on the script, though.
Places, everyone!
Okay. Cheap lights.
Off-brand camera.
(whirring)
And non-union action!
I like ice cream.
(slurping)
And I like lollipops.
And I like you,
Princess Num-Num.
(slurping)
Ew. I'm all
licky-sticky!
(sobbing)
I don't understand.
When I like something,
I lick it.
Like this raccoon.
(slurping)
(hisses)
LEELA: Doingg, don't
lick things
that don't want to be licked.
But how do I know what to lick
and what not to lick?
It's very simple.
(piano plays)
♪ If it's alive,
don't lick it ♪
ZOIDBERG: ♪ Like a horse,
a turtle or a cricket ♪
BENDER:
I like turtles!
♪ So if you're not sure ♪
♪ If it's alive or dead ♪
♪ Poke it with a stick
and lick the stick instead. ♪
Now I get it!
(slurping)
Ow!
Well, that's all for today.
But before we go,
let's do everything we just did
two more times.
Leela, that was great!
Even I have
to admire the performance
of me, Bender.
The show looks so cute.
Kids will love it!
And it looks so cruddy,
their ironic hipster parents
will love it.
Thanks, guys, but
let's be realistic.
We all know any TV show
that's even slightly good
gets cancelled.
Sometimes two or three times.
Leela!
Tomorrow's ratings
just came in from the future.
We're a hit.
What? My show is a hit?
What are you, deaf?
It's gonna be bigger
than SpongeBot SquareBolts.
I interfere with pacemakers.
(laughing)
Baby, I hope you like
drowning in caviar,
'cause that is how
you're gonna die.
♪ ♪
(cheers and applause)
Welcome back to the
Young People's Choice Awards!
In a moment, the award
for Outstanding Sext Message.
But first, the nominees
for Best New Kids' Show are...
(drumroll)
I hope you win, Leela.
Thanks, Fry.
It's nice to have the support
of viewers like you.
- I'm the star of the show.
- Shh!
And the Slurmie for
Best New Kids' Show goes to...
Turanga Leela
for Rumbledy-Hump.
WOMAN (over P.A.):
This is Turanga Leela's first nomination
and second time in high heels.
Wow. I feel so lucky
just to have been nominated
alongside so many
inferior shows.
And to all
my young friends
at the orphanarium,
thank you for inspiring me
to be your hero.
Slurm her!
So, wait. You play
a high school student
who's also secretly a rock star who's also
secretly a massage chair?
No. I play a high school student
who's also secretly a rock star,
but in real life
I'm a massage chair.
Oh. You ever made out
with a tugboat.
(whistle blows)
Guys, I didn't have time
to mention it up there,
but I want each of you to know
what an honor it is
to work with me.
Sweet ego of Montego!
Someone build a wind farm
in front of her mouth!
Leela, I mean this:
you're the greatest creative mind
since blah, blah,
blah-bity blah.
But it's 2:00 a.m. and you still haven't
written tomorrow's episode.
Well, you can't expect me
to write it here
with everyone talking so loudly
about how great I am.
Sorry.
I'm taking the ship to my quiet place
so I can be alone.
You noncreatives can
catch a bus home.
Noncreative? Ha!
I'll have you know
I bedazzle my own underpants.
(groans, babbles)
That was a hell of a massage.
Maybe the best that ever was.
Say, where are we?
(gasps)
BENDER:
Rumbledy-hump?
It's real!
I love eating vegetables,
don't you?
They're like crunchy,
green water.
I don't like 'em!
They're icky-yuckie!
(giggles) Now, now, Garbly,
if we don't eat our vegetables,
we won't grow big and strong,
like Feffernoose.
I had to be big and strong
to fight off the monsters.
Did somebody say monsters?!
(laughs)
This will make a great episode.
But talk slower;
I can't type that fast.
Well, well, well.
(gasps)
You didn't make up
that TV show.
You just wrote down
what these space twerps said.
Oh, hell.
(gasps)
Leela said
a Rumbledy-Hump no-no!
♪ Sometimes when we're mad ♪
♪ We say words
that are bad. ♪
♪ And poo-poo and pee-pee ♪
♪ And penis and gay ♪
♪Those are the 98 words
we don't say. ♪
(cheering, shouting)
My God, you stole
all your ideas
from those poor,
innocent creatures
and hogged all the credit?!
I underestimated you.
Wait. I can explain.
Nah, don't ruin it.
I'm loving the hypocrisy.
It's like catching an evangelist
in a whorehouse.
That was
the best Christmas ever.
You know I hate lying.
But those orphans
were so proud of me,
I couldn't bear
to let them down.
(sputters)
At least Reverend Pickens had the dignity
to jump out
the whorehouse window
with his pants
around his ankles.
Who's your friend, Leela?
He sure has a shiny
metal bumbledy-boop.
Aw, they're so cute
and harmless.
No wonder you feel safe
ripping off their act.
Bender, I feel
bad enough already.
(chuckles)
I'm just messin' with you.
I love that you're
getting rich off of them.
'Cause now I can get
rich off of you.
Oh, Lord.
From now on, you give me
half the gross,
or I'll blow your cover.
(groans)
Oh, fine. You'll get your cut.
I don't really care
about the money anyway.
I just want to show those poor,
disadvantaged orphans
that they can succeed in life.
Ugh! You are the worst kind
of rich person.
♪ Be it parsnips or peppers
or kale or zucchini ♪
♪ I like to relax
with a spinach martini ♪
♪ Bl drg tr blg vndl mrg frgrz
Houdini ♪
♪ 'Cause we love
our vegetables. ♪
DOUBLEDEAL:
And... cut.
That's a wrap, everybody.
Ten minute break,
then we shoot season three.
(cheering)
Leela, you may have become
a Lady Gaga-esque fame hag,
but you sure cheered up
those orphans.
Nice job.
(boinging)
Thanks so much
for inviting us to the taping.
The kids haven't been
this excited since Food Day.
Ah, thanks.
They're my inspiration.
But not my only inspiration,
am I right, Leels?
(cackling)
(gagging)
Is somebody standing on me?
Ah. I do love inconveniencing
the underclass.
Well, we'll be on our way.
After we dig through your trash
for aluminum.
Okay, kids, delta pattern.
Go! Go! Go!
(excited shouting)
Miss Leela?
Yes, Sally?
I want to show you
the story I made up.
That's Gumdrop, Sticky, Candycorn,
Sourball, and Jujube.
They're brothers and sisters
and they live
in Butterscotch Hollow.
Sally, that's wonderful.
You came up with that yourself?
Out of thin air?
How?
You were an orphan,
and now you're
the best writer ever.
So I knew I could write, too.
Thank you for being my hero.
I can't do this anymore.
I don't blame you.
Having to wear a costume
made from a
hollowed-out walrus.
Everyone, I have a confession.
I Turanga Leela,
winner of a Young People's
Choice Award,
a Peabody Jr.
and two Training Emmys,
am not what I appear to be.
There's something
I need to show you.
Uh-oh.
Continuing my confession,
this is the hardest
thing I've ever done.
Harder than creating
the best-est show in the world?
I didn't create anything.
I stole it.
Stealing is a form
of creativity.
No, it isn't.
Guys, come on out.
(all gasping)
Holy moly again.
Oh, hello, Leela.
I was just telling my friends
how they shouldn't eat food
off the floor.
Should we sing a song about it?
Yes, please.
No need, Ladybuggle.
Say, what's going on here?
(sighs)
This planet is the
real Rumbledy-Hump,
and these creatures are
the real Humplings.
All I did was write down their
adorably repetitious hijinks.
(gasps)
You lied?
Like Doingg did when he stole
Garbly's pet pinecone?
You told them about that?
I should have told
the truth right away.
These simple prairie folk have
a simple prairie-ish life here,
and I was wrong
to exploit it for profit.
I'm as sad as
an upside down smile.
You mean a frown?
We didn't have a word
for it... until now.
To think I put on an unflattering
cupcake costume for you.
To think I borrowed
money from you.
I was going to ask you
to marry me.
I guess if you can't
make up stories,
I can't neither.
I deserve this.
And more.
Keep it coming.
Wait a second.
As a big Hollywood TV producer,
I think I know how to remedy
this ethical lapse.
♪ So if you don't want a
tapeworm or intestinal bug ♪
♪ Don't eat pastrami
that fell on the rug. ♪
And... cut.
Ta-da!
We got us a reality show.
No writers, no actors,
no problem.
Doubledeal,
this is disgraceful.
You can't just rip off
their real lives
and put it on TV.
Who said anything
about ripping them off?
I did.
I'm paying 'em.
Gather round, gang.
Here are you paychecks.
(muffled):
I can finally afford my speech therapy.
And the health plan covers
my generic Prozac.
Electricity, plumbing--
our lives are a jillion times
better.
And it's all thanks
to you, Leela.
Don't thank me.
I should be punished.
I've corrupted you and taught
the orphans a terrible lesson.
What orphans?
The kids were all adopted.
They were?
By who?
DOUBLEDEAL:
Come on, kids,
let's get this place cleaned up
for the next episode.
Albert, pick up that pastrami
and put it back
on the craft services table.
You're the boss, Daddy.
Oh, God, what have I done?!
You've given us a new father
and a full-time job.
Which is more than
most kids have.
But...
We love it here, Miss Leela.
This is the funnest planet
in the whole world.
Don't hug me!
I've done a horrible thing!
For God's sake,
somebody teach me a lesson!
(chanting):
We love Leela, we love Leela (and so on)
No!
Sync and correction by Mlmlte
www.tvsubtitles.net