♪ Two... two, three... ♪
♪ ♪
Sync and correction by Mlmlte
www.addic7ed.com
After centuries
as a delivery boy,
nothing surprises me.
You stink, loser.
Hey, Fry!
Pizza going out!
Come on!
Aw, all right.
I'll take the Red Rocket.
Hello! Pizza delivery for...
D. Frosted Wang?
Ugh, not another crank delivery!
Why don't I read these
ahead of time?
One time was funny.
But every week for ten years?
Not as funny.
True, not as funny.
But still somewhat funny.
And-and then
they burst out laughing
a second time.
I've been a delivery boy
for a thousand years.
Isn't there any room for
promotion around here?
There'll be no promotions
unless somebody dies.
And even then, only if we can't
bring them back as
a zombie, like Scruffy.
Life and death are
a seamless continuum.
Mm-hmm.
Well, could I at least
get some encouragement?
I could use a shot in the arm.
I get shot in the leg!
Roberto!
What are you doing here?
What? A fella can't drop in
on old friends
and hold them hostage?
I'm good. And you?
Attention, criminal robot
in the building!
Come out with your hands up!
- Never!
- Uh... other guy.
Listen up, piggies,
I want a hovercopter,
and an unmarked sandwich,
and a new face with like
a, a Hugh Grant look.
And every five minutes
I don't get it,
someone's going to get
stabbed in the ass!
He's bluffing. Ouch!
He's not bluffing!
You call for a chopper?
Nah, I specifically said
hovercopter!
One chopper, coming up.
Hi-yah!
Ah!
All right!
Way to go.
You know, URL,
sometimes it's almost
too much for me.
You mean the respect we get?
And the high level
of job satisfaction?
There's that, but I'm
also talking about
the non-stop promotions
and the free hot rod.
Mm. I do love
a man in uniform.
Ahem!
I mean a uniform that
doesn't involve short pants.
I can see I have
no future here.
My only option is
to resign with dignity.
Here are my shorts.
♪ ♪
Hello. I'd like to enroll
in Police Academy.
You think you can
just waltz in here
with no pants and become a cop?
That's the plan.
I like you, kid.
I got no pants on, either.
I can see that. You're
quite a bit taller than me.
Welcome to Police Academy.
Hi, I'm Fry.
I'm a Sound Effects 5000.
Weep, wop, beep!
Wow. That would be impressive
if you were a human.
Yeah.
On your feet for
Chief O'Manahan.
At ease, cadets.
I'll make this short and sweet,
'cause I'm PMSing
like a lumberjack.
Police Academy
is not for everybody.
You're gonna get
your boob scuffed.
But if you've got
the vulva to stick it out,
I'll be proud
to call you ladies policemen.
Sir! Yes, ma'am!
Yeah. That's great.
Now, can you actually
turn on the ignition?
I don't have any hands.
Well, it's that
time of the month.
Graduation day.
So grow a pair and put them
together for our new officers!
Good job!
Hooray for the pigs!
Graduates, you are hereby
officially cops.
Now move it along,
nothing to see here.
Hooray! Free sky sticks!
Oh!
Police brutality!
Nice...
All right.
Before we head out, I'll be
teaming up our new officers
with their
ironically matched partners.
Sound Effects 5000,
you'll be with Cranski.
Ow, my tinnitus!
Fry, due to the unfortunate loss
of Officer Smith,
you'll be riding with URL.
And Smitty was just
a few days from retirement.
Wh-What happened?
He took a early
retirement. Damn.
Let's get down to business.
Aren't you going to say,
"Good news, everyone"?
Oh, I just said that
for Fry's benefit.
Made the poor fellow feel better
about his pointless job.
As much as I miss him,
he didn't really serve
much purpose around here.
Though he did walk Zoidberg.
In any case,
I've improved on Fry
by sticking some wheels on
a board, so Leela and Bender
can easily make the next
delivery without him.
Me? So where we going?
Pandora.
That dangerous 3D planet?
Can't we just send our avatars?
No, it's cheaper
just to have you die.
Whoa. 15 miles over
the speed of light.
That's a violation of the law
of Lorentz's invariants, baby.
Light 'em up.
Look out for that
particular individual!
An electric wall, eh?
I can't see the harm
in peeing on that.
Whoa! Where'd my man learn that?
Sunny D commercial.
Let's refract this sucker.
DNA and career chip, please.
Erwin Schrodinger, huh?
What's in the box, Schrodinger?
Um... a cat, some poison,
and a cesium atom.
is it
alive or dead?
Alive or dead?
Answer him, fool.
It's a superposition
of both states
until you open it and
collapse the wave function.
Says you.
There's also
a lot of drugs in there.
So... you're a robot?
You boys did good.
Nailed a major violator
of the laws of physics.
He's going down.
Cat's gonna testify.
Guys like this
really bust my uterus.
You're both getting a promotion.
Ever heard of the
Future Crimes Division?
Tomorrow, I have.
Oops.
I can't make out a thing.
Well, I guess you should
have had two eyes.
Just deliver the package,
and let's get out of here.
Screw that! I ain't
no delivery boy.
I'm the company chef.
Oh, you're the chef, are you?
Then why don't you make us
something nice to eat?
Here's your damn peanut butter
and jelly sandwich!
Now that we can predict
crimes with 99% accuracy,
we can arrest most perpetrators
before they even
perpetrate anything.
That's ridiculous.
Only horoscopes
can predict the future.
That's what we used to think.
Until we invented... this.
Ooh.
Slow down, baby.
The Cybernetic Oracle.
The ultimate man-machine hybrid.
Programmed with
every crime ever recorded,
and implanted
with the brain cells
of history's
greatest detectives.
We call him...
Pickles.
On account of it's like
he's floating in a jar?
Exactly.
The Oracle's visions are
recorded on these colored balls.
Green is larceny.
Black is fraud.
homicide.
What's pink polka-dots?
Clown slaughter.
It happens more often
than you'd think.
Floater in the bowl!
Red ball. Homicide!
Whoo!
male, six foot one.
Distinctive mustard stain
on his forehead.
My kajigger!
Hattie McDoogal.
Look, the clock says 5:08.
It's 4:30 right now.
Uh-oh, we only have
a half hour to chill out
before we head over.
Oh, Hattie.
When I look into
your one good eye,
I see a reflection of beauty.
Oh! Fresh.
Freeze, fool.
You're under arrest
for future murder!
Yeah? You can't arrest
me for future murder...
after it's right now murder!
My kajigger!
So he didn't really
want to marry me?
Nah. See, he knew
you left everything
to your parakeets in your will.
He was going to murder you,
marry your parakeets,
and then poison them with
an arsenic-laced cuttlebone.
Classic move.
Aw, yeah.
Congratulations
on your big bust.
You, too.
Keep it up, and you boys
might just make detective.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I got to go drop a big one.
Wow. I can't
believe it.
One more promotion,
and I'll be a real detective,
like Sherlock Holmes
or Speed Buggy.
Eight pounds.
I'm naming her Burt.
Mazel tov, Chief.
That's a beautiful
bathroom baby.
Hey, you heading home, Phil?
In a minute.
I just want to finish
this paperless work.
Don't stay up too late.
We got a lot of people
to shoot tomorrow.
Hello! Anyone?
There's never a cop
around when you need one.
Green ball. Larceny.
Hmm.
The thief seems to be
some sort of ghost.
Or is he?
Aah! Bender?
Our
corporate tax rate
remained unchanged
this fiscal year.
That's not funny.
It's not supposed to be funny.
It's a business meeting.
Things used to be funny
around here.
Noses were picked,
pants fell down.
So what changed?
Only Fry could say,
and he's gone.
Hey.
Bender and Leela are back
from Pandora.
How was it?
Awful.
We had nothing to
say to each other,
so we had to listen to Bender's
Eagles album for 27 hours.
Beats talking to you,
witchy woman.
Hey, he's back!
Look at you.
Hubba hubba.
Your pants go almost all the way
to your ankles.
Good afternoon, individuals.
Sir, would you mind
stepping out of the building?
Normally, when a cop
asks me that,
I spray whip cream
in his eyes and run away,
but to ditch
these losers, gladly.
Bender, be honest with me.
Are you planning a big heist?
Usually, but not at the moment.
I only ask
'cause the Oracle thinks
you're going to pull off
a major theft next Thursday.
Next Thursday, you say?
Pray, continue.
Are you familiar with
this particular location?
I may have a burgling
familiarity with it.
Does the word "Maltese"
mean anything to you?
The Maltese Liquor--
the strongest,
the most valuable malt liquor
ever brewed!
And soon it will be mine.
I'm sorry.
You were saying?
Bender, I'm only
telling you this
so you can avoid
committing the crime.
"Avoid committing
the crime." Got it.
You wrote "commit the crime"!
Oh, there's got to be some way
to stop Bender.
Maybe something
in the Oracle's predictions
that I missed before
due to incompetence.
Wait.
Who's the trigger-happy jerk?
That's me!
I recognize the face.
You shot me!
You miserable dingus!
No! No!
What have I will have done?
Man, that's heavy.
Osmium heavy.
Wha...? Are you going to turn me
in for concealing evidence?
Say what?
You're my partner, home Fry.
Besides, I got my own secrets.
Anything big worth checking out?
Just your big
jangly booty, baby.
See you tonight, toots.
You... and the chief?
Mm-hmm. We been gettin' it on.
Right there in your chair.
I'm like, "Oh,
baby! Oh, baby!"
And she's like,
"Yeah. Yeah. Yeah."
I would never shoot Bender.
Never!
He taught me how to shave.
Revision ball.
By deciding not
to shoot Bender,
you created an
alternate future.
I could never
shoot you. Never!
You taught me how to shave.
See?
Just get out of here.
Go!
Now, dig the unintended
consequences.
My friends, let us
share this booze
in a toast to our
dear friend, Bender.
Oops.
The Maltese Liquor
done destroyed their brains.
Fools should have
known it's fatal
for anyone but robots
and Billy Dee Williams.
So, if I don't shoot Bender,
all my other friends will die?
Fate is a freaky mistress.
Much like the chief.
Look out!
Something's not right.
I refuse to believe it.
Rewind.
Ooh.
Are you the calloused
working man I ordered?
Uh, sure.
In order to fix
your leaky roof,
I'll need to spend
two or three hours
down here in the wine cellar.
I'll be upstairs
putting batteries in things.
Whoa!
The Maltese Liquor.
40 ounces of heaven!
Here, boy.
This is for you.
Ah.
Hmm.
Invisible safe, eh?
Aah!
Ah, yeah, baby!
210 proof.
That's all
the proof I need.
Put the bottle back.
We both know I won't do that.
Either you're going
to shoot me,
or I'm going to spray
whip cream in your eyes
and walk out of here
like a big shot.
Bender, no!
You don't have to do something
just 'cause it's going
to happen.
The future's making a chump
out of you.
Oh, yeah? Well, I'm going to
make a chump out of the future.
I'm not stealing anything!
Yes! I stopped the crime
without shooting you.
The Oracle was wrong.
Was I?
Pickles?
Yes.
It is I, Pickles.
I set the whole thing up.
Everyone will think
Bender's the thief
while I make off
with that glorious brew.
Seriously? Why?
So I can kill
my human brain cells.
Do you have any idea
what a burden it is
to know everything
that will ever happen?
To never be surprised.
To know the punch line
of every joke hours in advance.
Like watching Leno.
And that is why I faked
the prediction of this crime.
Nevertheless--
stay with me here--
things will now happen
just as I fake predicted.
Bender, you're going
to hand me that bottle.
Not that one!
The real one,
which you switched
when Fry stupidly looked away.
Hey.
Ah, man.
Why you got to be
so Oracle-y?
Fry, you are going
to shoot Bender,
killing him and shattering
the fake bottle,
just as I predicted.
Do it!
It is your destiny!
Funny thing about destiny.
Sometimes fate has other plans.
Oh, nuts.
You shot me!
You miserable dingus!
And now the part
I didn't show you.
Everyone will think
Bender killed you,
and I walk away
with the goofy juice!
Finally, blissful ignorance.
I have no idea
what's going to happen next.
Did you get that, Chief?
Huh?
We got it all from behind
this prediction-proof glass.
But how could you know
my prediction was fake?
I knew something was wrong,
but I couldn't put
my finger on it.
Then it hit me.
You showed Bender
sharing the deadly booze
with our friends.
Bender would never share.
The very idea!
So we set up
this little charade
based on an episode
of Speed Buggy.
With the added benefit
of me and the chief
being locked in a small room.
Shall we adjourn
to the dungeon?
Well, I got my shield
for stopping Bender.
But then I got fired
for tipping off Bender.
Fry, we have no idea
what you do around here,
but we desperately
need you back.
Really? Um, I don't suppose
there's any chance
I could get a promotion.
Sure. What the heck?
I hear by promotion,
executive delivery boy.
Executive?
It's a meaning less title.
But it helps insecure people
feel better about themselves.
I feel better about myself!
www.tvsubtitles.net