♪ Two... two, three... ♪
♪ ♪
Synced and corrected by Arcinboldi
Who likes good news?
Everyone?
Then, good news, everyone.
Our next delivery isn't to some
dangerous outer space planet.
It's to Earth.
Earth is dangerous.
I fell off my
chair there once.
(groans)
Quit it, Earth.
We won't even have
to leave New New York.
The package is going
to Long Long Island.
Yes, to the lavish
Mafia-style villa of the Donbot.
The Donbot?
The vicious robot gangster?
I'd better use
my special robot vision
to see what's inside.
It looks like a pair of clamps.
(squeaking)
When are those new clamps going
to get here?
These are all rusted out
with snitch juice.
Patience, Clamps, it is my
eldest daughter's wedding day.
You don't want the Space Pope to
see you clamping, now, do you?
Oh, geez,
I forgot my Pope manners.
(clanging)
Dearly beloved,
it is with great speed
that I now pronounce you
husband and wife.
(clang)
♪ ♪
May I help you
with some assistance?
Delivery for Francis
X. Clampazzo?
We don't got nobody here
by that alias.
CLAMPS:
Hey, hey, that's me.
Those my new clamps?
Your name's Francis?
(mocking laugh)
Guys, look, it's Calculon
and the Robot Devil
and an open bar.
What's not to sneak into?
Bender, you can't crash
a mob wedding.
You forget, Leela.
I'm Bender, owner of disguise.
And now, ladies and gentlemen,
my good friend Calculon.
Hey, this one's
for the new couple.
It's your day.
It's all about you.
♪ Who's that singing
at your wedding? ♪
♪ It's Calculon, Calculon ♪
♪ Calculon. ♪
Hey.
Oh.
Piscopo.
This guy.
(gasps)
Bada-boing.
Hey, sexy, I'm Bender.
What brings you
to this tacky soiree?
I'm the bride.
Oops.
How about you, baby,
want to do it?
Bender, it's me, Fanny.
You who?
The Donbot's wife?
We had an affair?
An affair, huh?
Sounds like me.
Geez, I'd better be
a little more careful.
I don't want to hit on anybody
I already had sex with.
(bell tolls loudly)
Hi-ya, Bella.
Hi, Mom.
What about you?
You're my third choice.
(giggles)
(bell tolls loudly)
(bell ringing)
(both moaning)
Oh, Bender, this is all
happening too slowly.
Let's get married.
Quiet, I'm making out
with a floozy.
(both moaning, bell ringing)
(door opens)
Hold your clapper.
Someone's coming.
Donbot, please,
I'll pay you back
as soon as you loan me
some more money.
Sorry, Calculon.
It gives me no joy to do this,
because Clamps will be doing it.
Clamps, here are
your new clamps.
Clamps!
No, no.
Line?
(clamping furiously)
No...!
Yeah, Daddy
hates welchers.
The only thing he hates
worse is witnesses.
And guys who mess around
with his daughters.
And attempt to duplicate
his meatball recipe.
How was the wedding, Bender?
Says who?
I didn't witness anything!
MORBO:
In entertainment news,
two-time Oscar pool winner
Calculon was brutally clamped
yesterday
by an unknown assailant.
Poor Calculon.
(stammering)
All right,
Amy, you win!
The mob did it.
I saw the whole thing
while also having hot sex
with the Donbot's daughter.
(sobbing)
I'm scared and great at sex.
Bender, you need to go to
the police and tell them
a tastefully edited version
of what you just said.
What, and have the Mafia
come after me, too?
No way.
This secret goes to my grave.
The Bureau is offering
anyone with information about
this gangland-style clamping
a $50 reward.
BENDER:
Ooh, ooh, ooh, and then
Calculon said, "No, no.
No...!"
And then I ate some
excellent meatballs.
Can I have my
50 bucks now?
I enjoyed your story,
especially
the tasteful love scene,
but it's not enough
to convict the Donbot.
You'll have to testify
in open court.
No, no.
Can I have another $50?
No.
No?
No!
No...!
All rise for the
Honorable Judge 723.
Be seated.
Organized crime is
a plague on our society,
and I will not tolerate any form
of intimidation during...
All rise for the
Honorable Judge 724.
Good day.
I'd like to say
I'm prepared to tolerate
several if not all forms of
intimidation during this trial.
Prosecutor?
Your Honor, the prosecution
pecks for a mistrial
on the grounds
of jury tampering.
(circuits crackling)
JUDGE 724:
Donbot?
Motion denied.
Prosecutor,
call your first witness.
People call our star witness
Mr. X,
whose appearance will be altered
be-caw-se he's in grave danger.
(gallery gasps,
Hyperchicken clucks)
Bender, I've been looking
for you.
Which cake do you like better
for our wedding?
Bender?
Aah, fix it, fix it,
fix it, fix it!
Whew, that was close.
Isn't it true, Mr. X,
that you are slandering
this innocent mafioso
to distract
from your own felonious past,
including a crime
you made up yourself
called
"burgle-arson-arceny"?
That's a wholly
owned trademark
of Rodriguez
Crime Concepts, Inc.
Besides, I'm not
on trial here.
That's true.
You're on trial
in Courtroom Three.
You are charged
with two counts of
burgle-arson-arceny.
How do you plead?
Not inno-guilty-cent.
BENDER:
And then the Donbot said,
"Sorry, Calculon,"
and then Calculon said,
"No...!"
I think we've heard enough.
Wait, I'm not finished.
...o!
Now I'm finished.
Your Honor,
the prosecution roosts.
(clucks)
Have you reached a verdict?
Indeed.
After a steamy
12-way deliberation,
we find the accused guilty as...
(door opens)
CALCULON:
Wait.
The Donbot is innocent.
(gasping)
Calculon,
who is that escorting you?
Yes, who?
My personal trainer,
and he's trained me
to say that my wounds
were self-inflicted,
for you see I am
a big Hollywood idiot dumb guy
what does dat sort of ting.
Poifect.
(indistinct whispering)
We find the Donbot...
Dramatic pause.
...not guilty.
(gasping)
Honey, if you're
marrying Bender,
you might want to get
a black dress for the wedding.
That's going
to look hot.
(sobbing)
Don't be scared, Bender.
We're putting you in the
Witness Relocation Program.
You'll be given
a new identity,
a new place to live,
and this iPod.
I don't want it
anymore.
So I got to hide forever?
No, just until the Robot
Mafia finds and kills you.
They're pretty good
at that.
Good-bye, Professor.
Before I leave,
I just want you to know
I've never done
any work whatsoever.
Zoidberg, I know it seems
like I can't stand you.
(voice cracking):
Leela, you'll have
to watch out for Fry now.
Oh, Lord.
(sobbing):
I wish I could go
with you, pal.
Me, too.
I'll need a butler.
Bender, we have to go.
There'll never be
another like him.
Let's hire
someone better.
Clamps.
Clamps!
Huh?
Listen to my boss words.
I would like you to apply
for Bender's old job
and cozy up to this Fry,
his best friend.
Yeah, and then I'll introduce
him to my best friend--
clamp number one!
Sorry, toots.
No, Clamps.
No clamps.
Sooner or later
Bender will contact Fry,
as relocated squealers
always do.
Then with the clamps, Francis.
Francis... Francis?
I'll clamp you
with the Francis!
(grunting angrily)
Hey, oh,
take it ease.
(doorbell rings)
Hey there, slick,
I'm here about the job.
Take a seat.
We'll begin the
interviews shortly.
We'll start with Andrew.
(gasps)
Yeah, they all
kind of broke.
So, when do I start?
Everyone, this is Francis.
Hey, Francis.
Hello, Francis.
Hello.
Cute name.
Look what he can do.
Wow!
Whoa!
Oh!
Yeah, I do it all-- clamping,
crimping, occasional snipping.
Snipping?
(laughs)
Looks like you may be
out of a job, Zoidberg.
Ha, ha, ha, that's all good fun,
but of course a clamp
is no substitute
for the precision
of a genuine...
Francis, would you do
the honors?
(crying)
Stay off my turf!
Yeesh.
That guy can bite
my shiny metal clamps.
(laughs)
You remind me of my
old friend Bender.
Oh, yeah?
Where does he safely live?
I don't know. Hey, you want
to come to my house and play?
Yeah, sounds like freakin' fun.
♪ ♪
(exhaust hissing)
Eh, four stinking years
of clamping school for this?!
Greetings, Francis.
Sorry if I was
a little hostile before,
but snipping is the only reason
I'm even tolerated around here.
Not like you, with those
magnificent squeezers.
Squeezers? Squeezers?!
They're clamps,
you (bleep)!
If I want to (bleep)
snip with these clamps,
I will snip with these
(bleep) clamps!
Why do you think
they call me...
Francis?
Francis,
I have good news!
It's time
for your first delivery...
to the moon!
Fan (bleep) tastic!
Here's the 200 feet of rope
you ordered, Sheriff Furley.
Hot diggity!
You fellers want to stick around
for the hanging tomorrow?
It's gonna be a doozy.
I sure do love
hanging people.
(laughs)
Well, I best start
cutting the nooses.
Oh, you know
who could help with that?
(claws clicking)
Francis!
Nice job, Francis.
I like how
you didn't get drunk
and steal anyone's organs,
like our old robot.
Bender?!
Bender, it's me Fry!
Hee-yah!
I knew Bender would turn up
purely by coincidence.
Take care of him,
but do it quietly.
Don't worry.
We're in space,
where no one can hear you clamp.
(laughs)
What do you know?
The Feds gave Bender
a new identity as a moon farmer.
He must be afraid
to break character,
in case there's any robot mafia
scuzzballs around.
Huh?
Come on, let's
go check on him.
I checked on a guy once.
I checked him into tiny pieces!
Bender?
Nope, don't recollect
nobody by that name.
But let me ask my
son-in-law. Billy?
Yes, Moon-Pa?
These nice big-city
hillbillies are looking
for someone named Bender.
You know him?
Nope. He ain't any
of the eight people I ever met.
Bender, it's us,
your friends.
You can drop
the hillbilly moron act.
Sorry, mister,
but I'm no Bender.
I'm just a simple farmer.
Name's Billy West.
(laughs)
Billy West?
What a stupid, phony,
made-up name.
You city folk
are probably hungry
from premarital sex
and flag-burning.
Y'all want to stay
for supper?
Well, my boyfriend and I
were going to have sex
on a burning flag,
but I could have a bite.
May I present my beautiful
robot wife, the Crushinator.
She's serving up the dinner
and the charm.
Mashed chicken,
Mr. Fry?
Sure.
So, uh, Billy,
where were you born?
Right here in moon country.
And how long have
you been a farmer?
Reckon I was born a farmer.
Folks say my mama was a hoe.
Oh, dear, I seem
to have warped my fork.
Could you bend it back
for me, Billy?
Bend it?
I can't even lift it.
Which is weird, seeing as how
my daddy was a forklift.
(quietly):
Wow. Bender is
really committed
to his new
Jethrovian identity.
If y'all are finished,
I'll drive y'all back to town
in the old clunker.
So, y'all flew here
in a spacey ship?
Stop talking
like that!
You live
on the moon!
If that is Bender,
I guess he's just happier
in his new life.
I refuse to believe
anyone is happy!
Mr. West, would you mind
if I examined your brain?
Examine?
Heck, if you
can find it,
you can keep it.
(birds singing)
(whirring)
Gadzooks!
Bender's hard drive
no longer contains any
of his old memories!
When the Feds
bumpkinized him,
they completely
wiped out his old identity!
(all gasping)
Well, I don't know about that,
but who am I to argue
with a man from the sky?
So long,
space heroes.
You sure you don't
want to kill all humans?
(splutters)
I love all humans.
(sniffles)
He really is gone.
I guess
I'm happy for him.
And honestly,
Francis is a way better friend
than Bender ever was.
Hey, where is
Francis?
(lively music and chatter)
One sarsapar-oil-la,
Sheriff.
I'm thirsty.
Make it two.
I'm greedy.
You got the rest fooled,
but not me.
Now let's take this outside,
so's no one else gets clamped.
You're the
boss, stranger.
I'm gonna clamp your
body parts off one by one.
But then I'm gonna clamp
your wounds shut
so you stay alive...
while I clamp you some more!
Say your prayers, stoolie.
Okay.
God bless Grandma
and Grandpa...
They're next!
Right now I'm gonna cut
your damn head off!
(grunting)
ZOIDBERG:
Drop the robot!
(claws clicking)
I thought I told you,
I do the cutting around here.
♪ ♪
(all gasping)
(bird squawks)
(squawks)
Scuttle on home.
This ain't none
of your business, Slick.
My name isn't Slick.
It's Zoidberg.
John (bleep) Zoidberg!
(yelling)
Stop! Zoidberg,
you'll hurt Francis!
Oh, yeah?
Take this and that!
(wailing)
Why, you lousy...!
(grunts)
(grunting)
(gasping)
(groans)
(both grunting)
(trilling)
I'm gonna
clamp your...
Oh!
Oh, yeah.
Ow. Ow. Ow.
(laughs)
Looks like an all-you-can-
kill lobster fest!
That offer was
for a limited time only.
(yells)
My clamps!
Why, Zoidberg,
why?!
Because our friend Francis here
is in reality a bad murderer.
Yup. He was fixin'
to kill me.
This here crawdad
done saved my life!
(bell tolling loudly)
(all gasping)
Bender, you two-timing jerk!
I put off my singing career
for you!
If I can't have you, no one can!
(three rapid metallic clinks)
Oh, shucks.
(gasps)
Bender!
No!
What?
(Crushinator
sobs)
(whirring)
Bender was a hell of a squealer.
Maybe the best there ever was.
We'll send his widow
some meatballs.
Clamps, Bella, get
in the way-back.
(whooshing)
To my friend, Bender.
A wise man once said
he was a hell of a squealer.
Maybe the best there ever was.
ALL:
To Bender!
You pizza's gonna be
another minute.
We're still-a waiting for it
to be delivered.
Bender?
I'm-a no Bender.
You got-a me-a mixed uppa
with another-a robot.
(sighs)
You're probably right.
I don't really remember
what he looks like.
Guys, guys,
it's me, Bender.
(all gasping)
He's alive!
So that moon hillbilly
who got murdered was just
an innocent husband and father.
(all cheering)
Bender, old 'bot,
the mafia thinks
you're dead.
You can come back
to work with us.
I'm back, baby!
Pizza's here.
Whoo!
I'll just cut that...
You do, and I'll (bleep)
gut you like a fish.
(claws clicking)
www.tvsubtitles.net