Crimes of the Hot
Hurry up with the water.
I'm steaming inside my own shell, I am.
It's that hot, it is.
Man, it's hot. How hot is it?
It's so hot, I poured McDonald's
coffee in my lap to cool off.
[CHUCKLING]
Johnny Carson said it.
[PANTING]
No, Nibbler! Don't drink the pool water!
It's full of chlorine.
[GROANING]
[BURPING]
[COUGHING]
[LAUGHING]
Lightweights.
Oh, wait, chlorine.
[SIGHING]
Perhaps this movie will help
take our minds off the heat.
BENDER:
Focus!
ANNOUNCER: Global Warming
or: None Like It Hot!
[SOBBING]
You're probably wondering
why your ice cream went away.
Well, Suzie, the culprit isn't foreigners.
It's global warming.
-Gwobal wap-po?
-Yeah.
Meet Mr. Sunbeam. He comes
all the way from the sun to visit Earth.
Hello, Earth.
Just popping in to brighten your day.
La-la-la-la-la-la-la.
And now I'll be on my way.
Not so fast, sunbeam.
We're greenhouse gases.
You ain't going nowhere.
[SCREAMING]
Oh, God, it hurts!
ANNOUNCER: Pretty soon, Earth is
chock-full of sunbeams...
... their rotting corpses
heating our atmosphere.
[CHUCKLING]
How do we get rid
of the greenhouse gases?
Fortunately, our handsomest
politicians came up with a cheap. . .
. . .Iast-minute way
to combat global warming.
Ever since 2063,
we simply drop a giant ice cube. . .
. . .into the ocean every now and then.
Just like Daddy puts
in his drink every morning.
And then he gets mad.
Of course, since the greenhouse
gases are still building up. . .
. . .it takes more and more ice
each time.
Thus, solving the problem
once and for all.
-But--
-Once and for all!
Well, we just need one
of those big ice cubes.
Call the losers
who were supposed to deliver it.
[PHONE RINGS]
-Hello?
-President Nixon here.
I'm hiring you losers to deliver
the ice. And hurry up.
I'm sweating like J. Edgar Hoover
trying to squeeze into a new girdle.
You heard the good news, everyone.
Save the Earth, et cetera, et cetera. Bye.
-Wait. Where do we get the ice?
-The what?
Oh, Halley's comet, of course.
The only sufficient source of ice cubes
that don't have bugs in them.
Wow. Mining a comet.
That sounds fun.
Yes. There's no safer occupation
than mining.
Especially when you're perched
on a snowball. . .
. . .whipping through space
at a million miles an hour.
Whoo! Whoo! Whoo! Whoo!
Safe.
Deploying ice drill.
Wow. That ice dispenser's so big
the ice crushes you.
-Yakov Smirnoff said it.
-No, he didn't.
Activating ice drill.
Oh, my God! It's out of ice!
Like some outer-space Motel 6.
Completely out of ice?
This could mean the end of the banana
daiquiri as we know it.
Also life.
With Halley's comet out of ice...
...Earth is experiencing the devastating
effects of intense global warming.
Morbo is pleased but sticky.
The scorching heat has melted
the polar icecaps...
...causing floods of biblical proportion.
They called me crazy
for building this ark.
You are crazy. You filled it
with same-sex animal couples.
Hey! There are parts of the Bible
I like and parts I don't like.
MORBO: Direct your pity now
to the African turtles...
...seen here migrating
to cooler homes in Holland.
That poor turtle.
-Bender, are you crying?
-No. Never.
Morbo wishes these stalwart nomads
peace amongst the Dutch tulips.
I'm sure those windmills
will keep them cool.
Windmills do not work that way!
Good night!
Well, everybody, I just saved a turtle.
What have you done with your lives?
You went all the way
to Holland already?
Bender, a turtle isn't yourself.
Why do you care about it?
Because I also care deeply
about things that remind me of myself.
Like poor little Shelly here.
What could you possibly have in common
with this walking soup mix?
For one thing, we both
have a tough outer shell.
But lead a rich, inner life.
And also. . .
. . .well, you know.
You're both alcoholic, whore-mongering,
chain-smoking gamblers?
No. It's just. . .
. . .neither of us can get up
when we get knocked on our back.
What? I've seen you get up
off your back tons of times.
-Those times I was slightly on my side.
-Interesting.
Maybe we should test this erectile
dysfunction of yours, Bender.
No, that's not necessary, really.
I think I hear my factory recalling me.
That's what I get for sharing
my vulnerability with you.
MAN OVER SPEAKER:
Calling all scientists.
There will be a worldwide conference
on global warming in Kyoto, Japan.
I've got a degree
in homeopathic medicine.
You've got a degree in baloney.
-Professor Farnsworth, you're a scientist.
-Forget it. I'm not going.
I have my reasons.
Shut up, all of you!
Strange.
You haven't acted this suspicious since I
found the "ape bones" in the basement.
My hip hurts. I'm in the middle
of cooking a turkey.
I have warranty cards to fill out.
I am not just making excuses.
All right, I'll go!
WOMAN: I can't believe it!
I love you!
It's Professor Hubert Farnsworth!
He's looking sharp in a standard
white lab coat and dark slacks.
His wristwatch is a Casio.
Thank you all for coming.
It is my pleasure to introduce the host of
the Kyoto Global Warming Convention.
The inventor of the environment
and first emperor of the moon, AI Gore.
I have ridden the mighty moon worm.
[CHEERING]
Good for him.
My fellow Earthicans, as I discuss
in my book, Earth in the Balance. . .
. . .and the much more popular
Harry Potter and the Balance of Earth. . .
. . .we need to defend our planet against
pollution, as well as dark wizards.
Sure, blame the wizards.
That's why I'm offering
a bag of moon sapphires. . .
. . .to the first scientist who can solve
this problem once and for all.
CROWD:
Ah. . . . Ooh. . . .
-Lovely, aren't they?
-Sapphires?
With those, I could open
the gate of Girash.
First up is Professor Ogden Wornstrum.
Wornstrum!
[CLEARS THROAT]
Ladies and gentlemen,
I have placed in orbit a giant mirror. . .
. . .that will reflect 40 percent of the
sun's rays, thus cooling Earth. Observe.
[SIGHING]
Problem solved.
[CHUCKLING]
[GASPING]
That's a little bright.
[SCREAMING]
All right. What else we got?
Professor, you're a professor.
You must have some ideas.
Absolutely not! I won't speak.
I've got nothing to hide.
-Our next speaker is Professor--
-I demand the floor!
-Yes, it's your turn to speak.
-Well, nuts to me. I'm taking the stage.
I know the source
of the greenhouse gases. . .
. . .but in my shame, I've kept it
secret for 75 long years.
Oh, it haunts my memory still.
-Professor, no! Don't do it!
-Don't do what?
Don't use this memory ray so I can
remember what happened back then?
It was October 1 7 at 1 :54 p.m.
and 1 4 birds were flying by the window.
I was working at Mom 's
Friendly Robot Company.
Back then, robots were slow-moving,
stiff and a little on the uptight side.
Oh, dear, might I favor master
with a tender kiss on the forehead?
Oh, I've failed again.
Oh, dear. Oh, dear. Oh, dear.
FARNSWORTH: The company's owner
pressured me to create a sportier robot.
Stop!
It wasn 't easy. But by sacrificing
fuel efficiency, I succeeded.
-What was that?
-A flaming burp.
-Does it always do that?
-It's not always a burp.
We still have one problem, though.
This robot would never meet
emission standards.
Crap spackle!
We'll just call it a sport utility robot
and classify it as a light truck.
Well. . .
. . .I suppose the environment
can take one more for the team.
What a fool I was!
If only I had made the effort
to develop a cleaner-burning robot...
...but I was tired and in love.
Take me now, you stud.
[YAWNS]
Oh, this is all my fault!
That's awful, professor.
Especially the making-out part.
Yeah, I didn't need to hear that.
All modern robots descend from
my original smog-blasting designs. . .
. . .and that's the cause
of global warming today.
So the robots are to blame,
as I suspected.
We are left with only one possible
course of action, grim though it be.
I got a good feeling about this.
We must immediately and permanently. . .
. . .shut down, dismantle
and destroy all robots!
[GASPS]
-Wait! Surely there's a better--
-The conference is over.
I must go now
to help collect cans on Jupiter.
Peace out, y'all.
ALL: Destroy all robots!
Destroy all robots!
-Poor Bender.
-Be brave, my friend.
Come on. You've got to come out
of your chest sometime.
Would you do it for a Bender snack?
FRY: Ah-ha!
-Gotcha!
BENDER: Let me go!
I don't even want the stupid beer.
Yes! You tried to trick me
into coming out of my chest.
But who has the beer now?
[LAUGHING]
I've got mail.
It's a party, apparently.
Do you like to party?
To boogie down?
Well, I'm throwing an all-night beach
rager for my robot pals.
It all goes down this Saturday
on the isolated Galápagos lslands. . .
. . .where there will be no escape. . .
. . .from the fun.
All robots must attend!
Strange.
Why would Nixon, an awkward,
uncomfortable man, throw a party?
One of the most
social events imaginable?
It's a trap is why! They're going
to deactivate all the robots.
-I don't hear any gasping.
-We all figured that out.
-Oh. . . .
-Well, I'm off.
We can hide you. We'll pile fruit
on you and claim you're a bowl.
-No. I'm going to the party.
-I won't let you!
Fry, as you know, there are lots
of things I'm willing to kill for.
Jewels, vengeance,
Father O'Malley's weed whacker.
But at long last, I've found
something I'm willing to die for.
This mindless turtle.
Bender, this world
isn't good enough for you.
Not even close.
Goodbye, everybody.
Don't touch my stuff after I'm dead.
It's booby-trapped!
["GET DOWN TONIGHT" PLAYS]
[CHEERING]
Oh, yeah, baby!
Come on. Come on, baby.
Poor guy. Maybe you'd feel better
if I had a drink.
Crummy keg, it's completely tapped--
-Oh, you're a robot.
-Don't stop.
-Ew!
-Attention, happening robots.
Who's got what it takes
to party with Nixon?
[BURPING]
You fellas enjoy yourselves
for the next two hours. . .
. . .and be sure not to leave the island
for at least two hours.
I'm going out
to pick up some smokes.
Really good smokes.
Two hours.
[CHEERING]
Okay, headless body of Agnew,
let's blow this joint.
[GROWLING]
BIG ROBOT: Do you want to dance?
-No, I'm not really in the--
You know you want to.
[GRUNTING]
Per your orders, I modified my mirror. . .
. . .to fire a colossal electromagnetic
pulse at the Galápagos.
Every robot will be instantly
and painfully terminated.
Now, for your part of the bargain.
Very well. Agnew,
you belong to Wornstrum now.
[GROWLING]
I'll say goodbye now.
There ain't no turtles
where Daddy's going.
Don't tell anybody, but Nixon's
about to shut all the robots off and--
What?
[SCREAMS]
ROBOTS: We're gonna die!
We're going to the great beyond.
Nixon's not bringing the smokes.
Shut up and pay attention to me.
Bender.
Look, I love life and its pleasures
as much as anyone here.
Except perhaps you, Hedonism Bot.
But we need to be shut off!
Especially you, Hedonism Bot.
-I apologize for nothing.
-We pollute too much!
We're destroying the world
and killing the turtles!
-To hell with the turtles!
-No one insults the turtles!
Come on, you!
Let the games begin.
[CHUCKLING]
[GASPING]
Everyone listen!
Ah! Damn!
I've devised a way to save you and
stop global warming at the same time.
Granted, you're all blasting out
greenhouse gases.
You're one to talk.
But we can use those very gases
to save the planet.
If you all vent your exhausts
directly upward in one burst. . .
. . .it should thrust the Earth
further from the sun, thus cooling it.
[MUMBLING]
By my calculations, we'll need
the full force of every last robot.
So quickly, everyone point
your exhaust vents straight upward.
Now vent.
Vent like the wind!
[BURPING]
Harder! Harder!
Why isn't this working?
Some lazy or polite robot
is holding it in.
[GRUNTING]
Help! Help!
[WORNSTRUM LAUGHING]
A billion robot lives
are about to be extinguished.
Oh, the Jedis are going
to feel this one.
I'm sorry, buddy.
At least we'll die
on our backs, helpless.
What the hell are you doing?
Hey, are you trying
to make me look bad?
Ah-ha! I'm even greater
than I thought I was.
And now to fulfill my destiny!
Fire!
-What the--?
-We missed!
[GROWLING]
NIXON: Professor, for saving the Earth
and foiling me. . .
. . .I proudly, yet angrily, present you
with Earth's new highest honor:
The Polluting Medal of Pollution.
Thank you. I deserve this.
Hey, professor?
Now that the Earth's orbit. . .
. . .is further from the sun,
won't that make the year longer?
Why, yes.
One week longer to be exact.
In that case, I hereby declare it
Robot Party Week!
BENDER:
All right, baby!
["HOT HOT HOT" PLAYS]
[COUGHING]
www.tvsubtitles.net