Sync by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
Item one: duck!
Cubert, you crapscallion!
Why aren't you in school?
I couldn't get past
the protestors.
A bunch of smiling,
angry people
were handing out these
anti-evolution flyers.
Evolution is under attack
in our schools?!
To the Science Mobile.
You mean the ship?
Yes.
The Science Mobile.
It's just that you've never
called it that before, but okay.
I don't understand evolution,
and I have to protect my kids
from understanding it!
We will not give in
to the thinkers!
You people are as loud
as you are ignorant.
Now get back on your turnip
trucks and go home!
That is an insultingly accurate
stereotype, sir!
As a Professor of science,
I assure you
that we did, in fact,
evolve from filthy monkey-men!
I cannot speak for you, sir,
but my ancestors
were not monkeys.
They were orangutans.
Hard-working,
patriotic orangutans.
Dr. Banjo?
In the fur.
And I remind you that evolution
is merely a theory,
like gravity,
or the shape of the Earth.
Hey, Professor,
I'm a flying spaghetti monster.
You seriously believe
I'm descended
from some kind
of flightless manicotti?
Yes!
Oh, please.
A far more logical explanation
is the undisprovable science
of Creatureism.
All life was created
in its present form
7,000 years ago
by a fantastical creature
from outer space!
Bunk!
Oh?
If your elitist
East Coast evolution is real,
why has no one found
the missing link
between modern humans
and ancient apes?
We did find it.
It's called Homo erectus.
Then you have proven
my case, sir,
for no one has found the link
between apes
and this Homo erectus.
Yes, they have!
It's called Homo habilis.
Aha! But no one has found
the missing link
between ape and this so-called
Homo habilis.
Yes, they have!
It's called
Australopithecus africanus!
Oh-ho! I've got you now.
Fair enough,
but where then
is the missing link
between apes
and this Darwinius masillae?
Answer me that, Professor!
Okay, granted, that one
missing link is still missing,
but just because
we haven't found it
doesn't mean it doesn't exist!
Things don't exist simply
because you believe in them.
Thus sayeth the Almighty
Creature in the Sky!
I'll show that
banana-swilling poop-slinger!
We just need
to find that last missing link.
I found a
missing link.
It seems to be half
man, half toucan.
Not what we're looking for.
Throw it in the soup!
And here's something.
Uh-oh. It's another one
of Fry's dogs.
You find something, Hermes?
Uh... no.
Ugh! I hate chiseling
right after a manicure.
Oh, darn it!
I broke off
one of my of fingers!
Look, Cubert.
The neck on this one.
I bet he spent
a fortune on ties!
What, too soon?
I highly doubt
a Jurassic elaphrosaurid
had access to neckwear.
I knew I should have gone with
the ring-around-the-collar joke.
Hey, look!
I found a robot fossil!
That's a bedspring,
you dumb bedspring!
There are no robot fossils.
What?!
Who says I didn't evolve?
Everybody!
Robots were created
quite recently.
It was in all the papers.
Then explain this!
I've hit a rich
vein of missing links.
Java Man, Piltdown Man,
Manfred Mann.
Eureka!
It's the elusive
missing missing link.
This will show Banjo
once and for all.
What the...?
Oh, that's mine.
Hmm! My tux doesn't fit.
Probably because I've grown
so much since I last wore it.
Or evolved, one might say.
One might not say that.
Your tux doesn't fit because
you stole it from a boy.
You mean a man.
It was his Bar Mitzvah.
Welcome, museum members.
Or as I like to call you,
future exhibits.
He's good.
Tonight, we have a new resident
here in the e e Hall of Homini,
generously donated
by its discoverer,
Hubert Farnsworth.
Ladies and gentlemen...
Homo Farnsworth!
Once again,
science saves the day.
The end.
And now, to discuss
the scientific implications
of this discovery, our new
museum curator, Dr. Banjo!
Thank you, Professor Farnsworth,
for your generous gift,
which has once
and for all disproven evolution.
Behold! Homo Farnsworth
frolicking with dinosaurs
at the moment of creation.
I don't want to live
on this planet anymore.
Faster! Faster!
Just drop me off
at that asteroid over there.
Wow, this planetoid is
completely lifeless.
Not lifeless enough!
Set up my shack
so I can kick you out of it!
Professor, is this
your only water source?
It looks like
Diet Dr. Pepper.
It's not that bad.
It's just laden
with toxic minerals.
But not for long.
What's in the tube?
Microscopic nanobots.
They're tiny robots I designed
to eat up nasty irritants.
Speaking of nasty irritants,
what's gonna become of Cubert?
Who? Oh, my son.
Don't worry.
He's been safely abandoned
with his godfather.
Cubert, I felt we needed
some father-son bonding time,
so I found a couple
of baseball gloves
and boiled them up for lunch.
Why don't you just go to hell?!
Wait! We still have
to discuss the facts of life.
What are they?!
Okay, I finished moving
the last grand piano.
Now can we have our pizza?
You'll get your damn pizza,
you parasite.
First let's see if my nanobots
have purified the water yet.
Ah, the water's as sterile
as my milkman-trusting father.
But what's this?
The nanobots
have gotten more complex.
What's that, you say?
Those robots evolved
all by themselves, you say?
It wasn't by themselves.
I put them there.
I'm a genius.
Get over it.
Hey, look.
Now they got bigger.
Good heavens. Trilobots.
Oh, no! My sunglasses
were in there!
Let's get the pizza
out of here!
Look, there's a cave-like hole
in that mountain.
It might be a cave.
Does anyone
have a lighter?
Hang on.
Okay, we have shelter
and just enough precious food
to ward off starvation.
It's pizza time!
Pineapple?!
Ugh!
Oh, man!
Oh!
So much
for that.
Hello.
I remembered
you liked superheroes,
so I painted you a mural
on your wall.
This is Father-Man.
He fights crime to
earn Son-Boy's respect.
Is it working?
This is sucky!
You suck!
Who taught you
to do three-point perspective?
I could make a better mural
with my butt!
Father-Man away.
Nothing like a cave for
a good night's sleep.
So what do we got to eat that's
not poisoned with pineapple?
I packed plenty
of food, but it's all in
dehydrated pill form.
Then we need water
from that pond.
We'll have to fight our
way past the trilobots.
Go! Go!
Hit anything that moves!
A whole forest
grew overnight.
All these trees are robotic.
I can't believe
how quickly they sprung up.
I can.
Robots do everything faster,
including evolving
and believing
how quickly things spring up.
One thing about
Bristol-Myers-Squibb...
they know how to cook a steak.
Hey, look at me.
I'm the Tidy Bowl Man.
I own a yacht,
and everybody poops on me!
Help! Police!
Everybody grab a club.
big, tough water guy,
why don't you come
up here on land and...?
Look out for the next thing!
Great Scott,
a tricycle-tops.
Throw down,
dinosaurs of the land and sea.
This is a cool way to die...!
Dr. Zoidberg?
I'm sorry for treating you
like a total Zoidberg...
I mean, loser.
Go on.
It's just that
I get bullied a lot.
I guess I kind of make fun of
people as a defense mechanism.
Hey, Cubert,
is that your family mansion?
Why don't you ask your mom?
She's coming over
for a sex visit.
Don't worry, I know
how to handle bullies.
Just pretend
like you're pathetic.
Help, I'm scared!
I wet myself.
I'm crying like a baby
and I'm soaking in pee,
but what else is new?
The pee babies peed themselves.
I'm off to pottery class,
dorkwads.
And that's that.
Whoa! You're like some
kind of Dumpster Jedi.
So... you want
to come in maybe?
I've got a nice pound cake
with a footprint on it.
Aah, don't eat my butt!
If this is anything
like killing that pigeon
on my balcony, we've got
our work cut out for us.
Look out, a solar flare!
What the shmell happened?
A mass extinction.
That solar flare created
a huge electromagnetic pulse
that, while harmless
to organic life,
short-circuited
the robo-dinosaurs.
Convenient.
Only puny mammal-like robots
cowering in caves could survive
such a catastrophe.
Guys, guys!
I taught myself to knit.
Wait a moment.
If we could scavenge the right
parts from these robo-dinos,
I might be able to construct
a rudimentary spaceship
to get us off this planet.
Well, it took almost two
hours, but it's finished.
Now let's go... to sleep.
It's solar powered, so we can't
take off until sunrise.
Well, let's find something comfy
to bed down on.
Hey, looky here.
Sweet robot swan
of Botswana.
Looks like the fittest did
a little surviving
last night, huh?
Whatever.
Hey, looky there.
Those robo-cavemen
have kidnapped our
human regular-women.
We gotta save 'em.
But the only weapon
we have is my fan dance.
Hmm. I believe I can
fashion a slingshot
using this robot wishbone
and this elastic from my pants.
I think they want wives,
so just play along.
If it doesn't work out, we'll
still get half their rocks.
I can earn my own rocks.
Also, I don't want any rocks.
Well, it took almost 12 hours,
but it's finished.
It's too dark now,
but first thing tomorrow,
we'll slingshot them
like they've never been
slangshat.
What's going on?
How did we save you?
It was the weirdest thing.
We went to sleep,
and when we woke up,
our cave husbands were gone.
I'm going to miss Spencer.
Don't be afraid, little guys.
I'm not going to hurt you.
Nice net.
What, you...
you can speak?
Dread my locks.
A fully-evolved
robot human.
I'm Dr. Widnar, a naturalist.
And I'm Bender, baby.
My human slaves and I come
from a planet
where organic life
and robotic life
evolved side by side.
Oh, shut up.
Amazing.
I've theorized
that carbon-based,
fat-filled life
could exist,
but until today,
I never had any proof.
Good for you.
Can we go home now?
Welcome, museum members,
or as I like to call you,
future exhibits.
I now present
my latest discovery...
the amazing non-mechanical man,
Homo Farnsworth.
Thank you.
I must say, I'm so proud to
see what you've blossomed into
since I first created
your ancestors.
What?!
I thought you knew.
You all evolved
from some filth-gobbling
nanobots I designed.
I dumped them in one of
your ponds a few days ago.
But, but this is
creationist talk.
He speaks lies.
The Earth was created
in eons, not days.
Yes, relative to you,
it was eons, but, well,
look at this hologram I took
the day before yesterday
of a robot frolicking
with a robo-dinosaur.
Hogwash.
I don't want to live
on this planet anymore.
You're under arrest for
crimes against science.
No...!
Could you drag me
by the restroom?
Go back to Roboklahoma!
Order!
In the matter
of Everyone v. Farnsworth,
the alleged creationist faces
a sentence of death by melting.
Who is representing the accused?
I am. Ow!
I am, Your Honor.
Bender, what the
hell are you doing?
Shut up, I'm billing you
by the hour.
Besides, I'm a robot;
They'll listen to me.
Ladytrons and gentlebots...
Objection.
In the absence of pants,
defense's suspenders
serve no purpose.
I'm going to allow them...
for now.
Thank you.
Your Honor,
this meat-man does not deny
that we robots are
the glorious product
of evolution.
He claims only to have played
a small role
in supplying
the initial machinery.
I ask you, is that so crazy?
Yes, it's completely crazy,
and that is
why you must find him
not guilty
by reason of insanity!
Objection.
I'm not crazy.
I created you all,
and I came here in a homemade
spaceship and lived in a cave.
If you don't believe
me, ask my uncle.
Prosecutor,
your opening statement?
Yeah, honey,
I'll be home for dinner.
The prosecution rests,
Your Honor.
Very well.
We will reconvene
when the jury reaches a verdict.
Son, you in a whole
mess o' trouble.
Has the jury
reached a verdict?
No, we have not,
for we have evolved to a
higher state of consciousness.
In the grand scheme, all
physical beings are but yokels.
Now, settle your
petty squabbles
and get the hell out.
That'll be $1P, 000.
Well, digital
photographs don't lie.
I admit that what you witnessed
may have been some
form of evolution.
I'm glad you agree,
Dr. Banjo.
Evolution set in motion by
a wise and all-knowing creator...
you.
Oh, well, I don't know
about all-knowing.
And I admit it's possible,
however unlikely,
that some wise and all-knowing
alien monster
set evolution
in motion here on Earth.
Oh, oh! And the creator
could also be a robot.
Then who built this
so-called "creator robot"?
Some magical bearded robot
in the sky?
I guess that would be silly.
Never mind.
Then it's settled.
Finally, a world in which
I'm happy to raise my son.
Good, 'cause I'm sick of him.
I'm serious.
He's a terrible person.
Sync by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net