Obsoletely Fabulous
[BENDER WHISTLING]
-Ten dollars, please.
-Oh, man!
Sleep, little dumpling.
I have replaced your mother.
Aw.
-Oh, my God! Robot dealy-boppers!
-And there's a robot scratching post!
-You should try it out, Bender.
-Please. I have some dignity.
Ladies and gentlemen, my Killbot
features Lotus Notes and a machine gun.
-It is the finest available.
-Like fun it is, you glass-headed wallaby!
No one calls me that! I'm having at you!
Wernstrom!
[GRUNTING]
Such senseless aggression.
Come on. Let's go for a paddleboat ride.
[GRUNTING]
The secret was scratching
really, really hard.
ANNOUNCER: And now, the woman who
mom-opolizes the robot industry...
FRY: I get it!
-...Mom!
FRY:
Oh, now I get it!
Hello, dearies.
[CROWD CHEERING]
BENDER:
I love that old bat!
Ladies and gentlemen,
for the 1 7th year in a row. . .
. . .the future of robotics has arrived.
Boys.
I give you Robot 1 -X.
-Ow.
-Ow! Oh.
[CROWD GASPING]
Neat.
Quite frankly, Robot 1 -X will put
all my previous models to shame.
Incidentally, would one of my
previous models mind coming up here?
BENDER: Here! I'm coming!
Come on, baby! I'm yours!
-Come on, Mom!
-Jerk!
Here we go.
I'm your top of the line, Mom!
Notice that this obsolete robot
runs on alcohol and emits pollution.
Whereas Robot 1 -X runs on pollution
and emits pure oxygen. . .
. . .with a fresh pine scent.
[BURPS]
[SNIFFING]
Man, that smells great!
Now let's see how both robots do
at a typical household task:
Sorting a jar of pocket change.
Task completed.
Total value $4.73 and one Albanian lek.
Very good, Robot 1 -X.
And you, bending unit?
I never got the change.
Suckers.
Presenting Mom's Friendly Robots.
[CROWD CHEERING]
That new robot is great, huh?
He sure made me look like a pile of crap.
Indeed. That's why I bought one
to help around the office.
[BENDER SHRIEKS]
Let's try him out. Robot 1 -X,
can you clean Nibbler's stanky litter box?
I can, and will.
Hey, I could have done that
if you'd ask me.
I asked you five minutes ago.
You call that a kiss? I'll show you!
Come here, Nibbler!
[NIBBLER GRUNTING]
Look, Bender. If you want something to
do, stop making out and give us a hand.
Go up on the roof
and install this fake satellite dish. . .
-. . .so we can impress the neighbors.
-Yes, sir! I'm on it.
-Oh, and have Robot 1 -X help you.
-God!
[GRUNTING]
Get out of here, freshman!
I don't need your help!
-Our owners asked me to assist you.
-Yeah? Well, assist this!
Whoa! Ah! Help!
When I screamed "Help,"
I didn't mean you!
I apologize. However, I was able to do
your job before I saved your life.
Don't mind me. I'm just saving you
the trouble of throwing me away.
Mell out, Bender. Come watch some TV.
[GROANING]
I can't. I'm stuck in the can.
Well, ask Robot 1 -X to pull you out.
Never!
-Why can't you accept his help?
-I hate him!
But he's just a tool
to make your life easier.
Like a socket wrench, or a burglar's kit.
-I can't ask for his help because. . .
-Yes?
. . .I'm scared of him.
-Oh, sorry.
-Well, then, there's only one solution.
You need an upgrade
to make you compatible. . .
. . .with Robot 1 -X's new technology.
An upgrade? But I thought
we all agreed I was perfect.
-Fry, didn't we agree I was perfect?
-Oh, yeah. No, you're pretty perfect.
"Pretty perfect"?
So you do think I need an upgrade.
Yes, for God's sakes, yes!
Fine. I'll be back in a few days.
Man, I hate those new 1 -X robots.
I'd like to stab them!
Give them some of these!
[YELLING]
Yeah, right on, nut cake.
Parole officer says I gotta upgrade, or he
won't give me back my stabbing knife.
But it's no big.
I hate those 1 -X so much.
I know it won't affect me.
Death to the 1 -X Robots!
I love those magnificent 1 -X Robots!
The 1 -X Robots are my friends.
Wait. What happened to your enthusiasm
for stabbing them?
I'm past that. Later, blood.
It's like he's not him anymore.
You took away his robo-humanity!
[SCREAMS]
I changed my mind!
[BENDER SCREAMING]
[SEAGULLS SQUAWKING]
Yeah. I did it! I escaped.
But to what kind of a life?
[SQUAWKS]
I'm too scared to get the upgrade. . .
. . .but I can't face my friends again
without it.
[SOBBING]
And so, I set sail for unknown shores.
Oh, merciful Poseidon,
take pity on this mechanical mariner.
Oh, jeez.
BENDER:
Whoa! Whoa! Oh, uh. . . . Whoa!
Curse you, merciful Poseidon!
Boy, what is the deal with the ocean?
A tropical island, huh?
Well, I've washed up in worse places.
Okay, first up,
I'm gonna need to build a shelter.
There.
Well, I guess I'll go out for a while.
Damn. One rock short of rescue.
[MIMICS FOGHORN]
[FOGHORN SOUND FADES]
Low on power.
Better fuel up.
Oh, no! Guess I'll do what I always do
when I run out of booze.
[SOBBING]
[GRUNTING]
Okay, don't panic.
I've got these yams.
I'll just make some yam schnapps.
Hmm.
Hey, I should be mad at you.
Now, turn around.
Funny now hot.
[BABBLING]
Beer!
[QUACKING]
Ow!
Oh. . . . Numb. Oh.
[DRUMMING]
Who is it. . .?
Ow!
[GULPING]
Who are you, and why should I care?
Side A. We're a community of outdated
robots who refused to upgrade...
...and came here-- Side B.
--to live a simpler existence,
free of technology.
A working cartridge unit? Wow.
You guys went obsolete years ago.
Your mother.
What Cartridge Unit means is, the things
that make us obsolete. . .
. . .also make us unique.
I, for example,
need to keep refilling my waterwheel. . .
. . .or I'll power-down forever.
Oh, God! I'll never make it this time!
This is the end!
-Anyway, we like it here.
-Like you have a choice.
-So, what's your problem?
-Not enough. . . .
-Memory?
-Oh, great.
Now I remember that word,
but I forgot my wife's face.
Oh, God! No! I want to live!
[WATER SPLASHING]
If you'd like,
you're welcome to join our society.
Look, no offense, but I need technology,
especially e-mail and snowmobiles.
And television. Without television,
how will I know what's buzz-worthy?
Why would you want to watch TV when
you can watch a snail crawl for hours?
That's the dumbest thing
I've ever heard.
Oh, man! He's never gonna
make it over that pebble!
Wait! Wait! Oh, my God! He made it!
ALL:
Yeah! Way to go!
That was the greatest thing ever!
Let's party.
[KENNY LOGGINS'
"I'M ALRIGHT" PLAYS]
-Yeah, baby! Come on!
-Where did you get that CD?
It's one of my 1 0 desert-island disks.
I never really thought I'd use them,
but look at me now.
Oh, yeah, baby! Gonna do that dance. . . .
CDs are unnatural.
Why don't you just listen to the ocean?
Which ocean? That ocean?
Wow. It's like the Earth
making sweet, salty love to itself. . .
. . .while all the fish groove on it.
So much for this garbage.
Take that, Beethoven, you deaf bastard!
Bang, bang, bang.
You sure got this life thing figured out,
cymbal-banging monkey.
Hi, Bender. We know how much
you miss technology. . .
. . .so we brought you this
washing machine that drifted ashore.
[BENDER GASPS]
I'm gonna wash my linens so hard,
the--
[GRUNTS]
[WATER SPLASHING]
You. . . .
What? I don't understand.
Wretched technology has brought me
nothing but misery.
But Bender, you are technology.
You're the most advanced thing
on this entire island.
Oh, it's true. I am a hideous triumph
of form and function.
But not for long!
[BENDER GROANING AND GIGGLING]
BENDER:
Oh! That hurt!
WATERWHEEL ROBOT:
The downgrade is complete!
Behold my handcrafted purity.
The modern world
can bite my splintery wooden ass!
Ah.
Welcome to your new life
of simple tranquility.
Forget that! I say the whole world
must learn of our peaceful ways!
By force!
[GASPING]
-What?
-We're going back to civilization. . .
. . .to wage war on technology!
What?
BENDER:
Row, comrades, row!
We'll stage an attack
on technology. . .
. . .worthy of being chronicled
in an anthem by Rush.
We've been sailing for three weeks.
Maybe I should check our position
with the periscope.
BENDER:
Aye, up!
[GASPS]
Mirrors reflecting mirrors?
High-tech sorcery! Sorcery, I say!
-Did you see anything?
-Yep, we're there.
Prepare to surface!
And now, technology shall taste the lash
of the hickory switch!
[HARD ROCK MUSIC PLAYS]
[CHEERING]
[CHILDREN CRYING]
[CHUCKLING]
SINCLAIR:
Technology is defeated!
Let us return to the island
and celebrate by counting rocks!
ALL:
Yeah!
Whoa! Whoa! No one wants
to count rocks more than me. . .
. . .but our mission is not complete.
Not so long as Robot 1 -X torments me
with his obvious superiority.
Ready the catapult, Sinclair!
Aim for their power lines!
They're the devil's veins,
and electricity is his blood!
Bender? lf we don't survive the attack,
I want you to know I love you.
Okay, fine. Fire!
-Oh! I'm blind!
-Professor, we have no power!
What do you mean, "no power"?
We're living in the future!
I'd better light some candles.
Friends, I've come to free you
from your complicated lives!
Free you from the "complicated" part,
I mean, not the "Iives" part.
Oh, Lord, he's made of wood.
-What now, Bender?
-I got a downgrade.
I'm a steam-powered wooden robot,
just as nature intended.
-Therefore, I must kill Robot 1 -X!
-That's just stupid!
Does Mr. Bender
wish me to destroy myself?
I don't need your charity.
Target Robot 1 -X and fire!
[ROCK WHIZZING]
You wanged my ship,
you walnut-paneled idiot!
BENDER: Try again, Sinclair.
I said target Robot 1 -X.
SINCLAIR:
Who's Robot 1 -X? Launching.
[ROCK WHIZZING]
So I guess everything worked out fine.
[SCREAMS]
[SCREAMING]
Great. Now we're being crushed.
Help us, wooden Bender!
Those guys hate fire!
I gotta do something!
[BABBLING]
What the--? Termites?
Well, I don't need legs
to save my friends.
I'll just use the old extenso-matic arms.
Bender! Hurry! This fuel is expensive!
-Also, we're dying!
-I'm a-coming!
[GRUNTING]
Ow! Lousy primitive body!
Oh, why didn't I get that upgrade?
I'm an outdated piece of junk.
-Sir, might I recommend--?
-You shut up!
No, wait. I can use you as a tool
to save my friends.
And I'll still be the hero,
who everyone says how great he was.
-How may I help you?
-Save my friends! And Zoidberg!
[SIGHING]
Look! My hair got singed
into an even cuter 'do.
-Hey, where's Bender?
BENDER: Down here.
I'm so sorry, guys.
I never meant to hurt you. . .
. . .just to destroy
everything you ever believed in.
Well, at least you saved us from. . .
. . .uh, you.
Thank God you finally overcame
your incompatibility with Robot 1 -X.
Oh, yeah, we were totally in sync.
I was like, "Save them! " And he was all,
"No problem. " And then he did it.
His new technology is great.
I love those magnificent 1 -X Robots.
The 1 -X Robots are my friends.
It's like his personality
is totally different now.
Oh, maybe this upgrade
isn't such a good idea.
I'd like to give Robot 1 -X
a big smooch on the--
-Hey, what's the dealy-o?
-Your upgrade is complete.
But I destroyed the technology
of the world.
I ran on the beach and felt the sand
between my foot-cups.
Everyone experiences the upgrade
differently.
If that stuff wasn't real,
how can I be sure anything is real?
Is it not possible, nay, probable. . .
. . .that my whole life is just a product
of my, or someone else's imagination?
No. Get out. Next?
[SIRENS WAILING]
Well, I guess reality
is what you make of it.
[WHISTLING]
BENDER:
Yep. Oh, thanks, baby.
www.tvsubtitles.net