♪ Two... two, three... ♪
♪ ♪
Sync and correction by Mlmlte
www.addic7ed.com
Double time, soldier.
I want this ice fishing
operation up and running
by 0800 hours.
It's too cold, Dad.
My teen region is freezing off.
You don't know what cold is.
I once survived an entire week
trapped in a Swiss glacier,
eating nothing but
frozen Neanderthal.
To this day I can't stand
the taste of early hominid.
Let's just get inside the shack.
- Hold, maggot!
- Ow!
Remember the code of the ice:
Thick and blue, tried and true;
thin and crispy, way too risky.
Shows what you know.
Crispy doesn't even rhyme with risky.
Aah!
Help, I'm drowning!
Don't worry, son, you'll
freeze before you drown.
I love ice fishing.
I shouldn't be out in this cold.
I have no protective fat, hair
or warm blood.
I'm not even legally a mammal.
You don't know what cold is.
I was frozen for a thousand years.
You were?
Huh, learn something dumb every day.
Live bait.
Get your live bait here.
Fresh killed bait.
Can we get inside the shack?
I'm wearing a belly parka.
If I understand ice fishing,
and I'm pretty sure I don't,
we'll need to laser-blast
a hole in the ice.
No, no crazy technology.
Here, Bender, use
your immense robot strength
to drill a hole
the old-fashioned way.
I don't see any irony in that.
And voilà !
Everybody's ice fishing.
How come nobody's ice fishing?
Hot cocoa break.
Cocoa is for yodeling babies.
If you're sober,
it isn't ice fishing.
Mom, what's my temperature?
50, 45, 40.
It's all over.
Whoo!
Down at the 35!
I'm really sick.
Huh?
Oh, sorry.
A hundred and nine.
We'll check it again at halftime.
You home from school, you traitor?
I fell through the ice.
Cut me some slack.
Nobody cut me any slack
when I broke my spine.
Didn't even take a day off of work.
Lot of people depend on you
when you sell trampolines
door to door.
Here's your homework, you lucky knob.
And with a little more luck
from my seven-leaf clover,
I might get sick enough
to miss the whole semester.
Hey, give me that.
No.
Give it to me, you faker.
No, you're not getting it.
Ow, my underbite.
Come on, Yancy,
your brother's sick.
You'll never have
a better chance to take him out.
Dad.
"Nerd Search '88"?
What's this?
Some stupid science contest
for smartwads.
NASA's going to pick one kid's
experiment to launch into space.
I could make a space experiment.
I just got a new thing of glitter.
I'm not sure science is your thing,
seeing how that chimp
at the zoo tricked you
out of your allowance.
Yeah, well, I'll show you
and Mr. Bananas.
Anyway, I've got nothing better to do
while I'm sick in bed.
Wait, that's it.
I'll make a space experiment
about the common cold.
Where's that contest flyer?
You're holding it, genius.
Oh, good.
I feel awful, but it was worth it
to catch and kill this baby fish.
Shmeez, what's with
the shmiffling?
It's nothing.
Just a common cold.
- Wha...?
- Common huh?
- What the hell's a common cold?
- Is it valuable?
Could it be taken from you
if you were, say, unconscious?
A common-- a common cold?!
No, no...!
Ever since Fry first came to us,
I've lived in mortal terror
that this would happen.
I never heard you mention that.
Oh, I try to act cool, but
inside I'm freaking out.
It's just a cold.
What's the big deal?
This is the police.
An unknown pathogen has been
detected on these premises.
Come out with your hands...
I mean, stay in with your hands up.
You are hereby quarantined
until such time
as it is deemed safe to enter
and shoot your asses.
Now, now, let's not
all panic at once.
We'll have to take shifts.
Hermes, you take the first six hours.
Very well.
Louder, louder!
Right, baby.
Look, I just have a common...
...cold!
It'll be gone as fast
as I can sneeze, hurl,
and squirt it out.
No, it won't.
The common cold died out
500 years ago,
and subsequently, humanity lost
all resistance to its ravages,
but the virus survived in you,
frozen for a thousand years.
Huh, so it was hiding
deep down inside of me,
like my skeleton bones?
Give it to us straight, Professor.
How incredibly deadly is it?
We don't know.
It could kill millions or nobody.
I suppose it might even bring
a few people back to life.
Anything is possible in science.
Oh, no, I've got it, too.
My nose is all gunked up with blork.
And I've got a hankering
for a useless remedy
created by a schoolteacher.
Uh-oh, I think
I'm getting swollen glands.
Screw the quarantine,
I'm out of here.
Initiate containment procedure.
Aah, ow, oh!
Go on now.
Now I'm sick.
I shudder to think
what this cold will do to me.
Yesterday I was nearly killed
by a tight hat.
I'd be remiss if I didn't rub
your goopy noses
in the fact that I'm immune.
Which is why we'll all be
counting on you and you alone
to nurse us through this catastrophe.
Why, God?
Why have I been singled out?
Everyone just calm down and make
yourself a tissue walrus.
Damn it, son, lose the tissues.
You're ruining Thanksgiving dinner.
I'm busy with my space experiment.
I can't devote precious
brainpower to blowing my nose.
You're never going to win
that science fair, Philip.
Face it, someone
with your limited brainpower
would be lucky to get a job
as a pizza delivery boy.
Hey, Barack,
pizza going out, come on.
Man, I have got to go
back to law school.
I'm not going to wind up a loser
like that guy.
Sure you will.
You're going to lose
the science fair,
and that's who's going to beat you--
Josh Gedgie, boy scientist.
Pi over four radians
of pizza, please.
What is that, about a slice?
More like exactly a slice.
Game on, Gedgie.
Ew!
I've had worse.
When I was shot down over Korea,
I had to eat Kimchi.
He was our interpreter.
Coming.
What now?
Humidifier.
Fine.
Yes?
Where's that chicken soup
we asked for?
Chicken, water, fire.
You take it from there.
This is torture--
the fever, the chills,
and the sweating--
Amy's horrible sweating!
That's it.
I'm leaving
while I still have my dignity.
See you in the obituaries.
How's the containment holding up?
Without turning my head,
I'd say 100%.
Howdy, folks, and may I say
nice work keeping
those sickos penned up.
Put her there.
You, too, buddy,
and you and you and you
and especially you.
That robot was
a heck of a nice feller.
You'd better stay here
during biology.
Mrs. Jenkins dissects anything
smaller than a fifth-grader.
Well, if it isn't Grandmaster Phlegm.
I heard you're entering the
NASA science competition.
Maybe I am, LL Fool J.
So what's your project-- the
effects of losing on idiots?
No, I'm gonna infect my
guinea pig with the common cold
and launch it into space to see
if it gets cured by cosmic rays.
Lame, though the common cold
virus does seem
like a judge-pleaser.
I think I'll steal that
and do an experiment
that's slightly less very stupid.
But that's my idea.
You are an evil, evil nerd.
Gedgie out.
We'll show him who's stupid.
♪ ♪
Linda?
Borbo, the so-called common cold,
introduced by living
fossil Philip J. Fry,
is spreading out of control.
All citizens are advised
to wash their hands thoroughly
after beating up Philip J. Fry.
Phew! Lucky I'm safely
locked up here with you guys.
There he is!
Get him!
Ow! Ow! Ow! Wait!
The situation is expected
to deteriorate
as newscasters whip
the city into a panic.
Run! Run for your lives!
And finally, the heartwarming
story of a handicapped magician
who didn't know when to give up.
I don't like the looks
of this, Mr. President.
Shall I switch it off?
Negative.
Rosemary,
release the surgeon general.
Get in there!
Ow! It's bright out here.
Wernstrom, the quarantine has failed.
Give me a worst case scenario.
And make it grim.
I've prepared some projections.
Should the virus escape Manhattan,
this is how far
it will spread in 12 hours.
This is 24 hours.
This is a Verizon coverage map.
And in 36 hours, it will have
infected the entire planet.
Options?
We have only one option.
Protocol 62.
Not possible.
We don't have arly enough piranhas.
Then protocol 63 it is.
Hooray!
They're letting us out!
And hundreds of black hovercopters
are coming to welcome us!
They shrink-wrapped the whole city.
Well, it could be worse.
It is worse!
Oh!
They're flying
Manhattan into the sun!
They must have been out of piranhas.
They're gonna kill the virus
by exposing it
to the heat of our burning bodies!
I'm just glad I have my wool scarf.
What good is a wool...?
Guys! Guys, you're never
gonna believe this!
We know!
They shmooped up Manhattan
and blasted us toward the sun!
They did? Oh, so that's
why this was unguarded.
People of New New York,
this is Surgeon General
Ogden Wernstrom.
Wern...
...strom!
No doctor likes hurling
his patients into the sun,
but since there is no way
to make a vaccine
for the common cold...
There is a way to make a vaccine!
There is? Yay!
Of course,
there's a catch.
Yay! Yay!
So what's the catch?
The vaccine requires the original,
unmutated 20th-century cold virus,
so I need to grind you into a paste.
Professor, no!
It's okay, Leela.
This is all my fault sort of.
If this will save you, then please,
turn me into a virus milkshake.
He consented!
You all heard it!
♪ ♪
Yes, sir, many of these
entries merit a ride
in the mighty bosom
of our space shuttle.
And then there's
your so-called entry.
Geez! Walk much, Gedgie?
Absurd. You really think
your guinea pig can survive
in the vacuum of space?
He already survived
in the vacuum of my mom.
I mean, my mom's vacuum.
My experiment measures
the effect of microgravity
on the propagation
of the common cold virus
in an anaerobic environment,
i.e., space.
Impressed?
Damn right I am.
That's some dry, emotionless science.
Nice job, son.
Hey, wait a second!
I know where you can get some
20th century cold virus
without killing me!
Hush, lad.
I'm totally in the zone.
We just have to find the
Nerd Search '88 satellite.
Oh! I don't know why
I even build these things.
Gunnery Chief Bender,
blast us out of quarantine.
Aye aye, lady!
Oh, fiddlepoop!
Our weapons aren't strong enough
to puncture a thin
plastic tent that thick.
No, but theirs are!
Captain, a ship is attempting
to break the quarantine.
Blow them to Bac-O bits
with a well-placed warning shot.
But...
Oh!
Oops.
We'll find that cold virus.
The Nerd Search satellite was
launched on the space shuttle
and released into orbit.
Hmm. All ancient satellites were
swept up as space junk in 2113.
I actually knew that offhand.
I'm Facebooking right now.
Aha!
That satellite was scuttled
on Enceladus,
Saturn's main dump moon.
Let's dump it up!
This is the exact location of the dump,
but there's nothing here.
Can we please go home and die now?
I'm with Bender.
Whatever was here has been covered
by centuries of ice buildup.
No! It's under here somewhere!
We just have to bust our way down.
Remember the code of the ice.
Thin and crispy, way too risky!
I found the satellite!
Let's just hope
the experiment's still in here.
Yes! We're saved!
And now, to present the awards,
our very special guest.
He walked on the moon,
and now he is judging
a high school science contest.
Truly a man who can
and will do anything:
Dr. Buzz Aldrin!
Wow. I could have used
an introduction like that
when I first met the moon men.
But seriously, there are moon men.
Okay, this year's
Nerd Search runner-up
is a young man who devised
a way to add and subtract
in zero gravity-- Vijay Patel
and his calculator space hat!
And now, the grand prize winner
whose experiment will be
launched into space...
Look at that cocky smirk.
My money's on Gedgie.
Yeah? He may have brains,
but I have heart.
Josh Gedgie!
I'll bring the car around.
What a well-prepared virus culture.
This will make a fine vaccine.
Good thing Gedgie won.
My dumb experiment wouldn't
have lasted an hour in space,
let alone a thousand years.
Besides, Buzz Aldrin ran over my
guinea pig in the parking lot.
Okay.
Come on, gang,
let's go inoculate everyone
and cram Manhattan
back into its rightful hole.
This may hurt a little.
Ow!
Now I'll give you the shot.
You saved millions of lives, Fry.
You should feel proud, no matter
what your dad said to you.
You still haven't thanked me
for pulling you out
of the lake, soldier.
I could have flip-flopped out.
I know that.
Look, son, I know I give you
the business sometimes.
But if I'm hard on you,
it's only 'cause I want you
to grow up strong and resilient.
Some day, you may face
adversities so preposterous,
I can't even conceive of them.
But I know you'll pull through
and make me proud.
I love you, son.
Now bundle up.
I don't want you getting frozen.
Sync and correction by Mlmlte
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net