Sync by n17t01, corrected by gloriabg
www.Addic7ed.Com
And now "The transcredible
exploits of Zapp Brannigan"
brought to you by
Bartley's rocket wax.
I wax my rocket every day!
No one can save you
now, Leela.
What about Zapp Brannigan?
Well, obviously, Zapp Brannigan
could save you, but...
Zapp Brannigan?!
So, Emperor Chopchop,
once again, we meet at last.
Drop that space gun
or I'll shoot... like so.
Ooh.
Oh! Oh, Zapp.
Tie me back up
and ravish me.
I'd like to,
Leela, so I will.
Mmm, shake it, baby.
Shake it like...
I surrender and
volunteer for treason.
Emergency summons
from the president, Captain.
Oh, it's you.
Just let me freshen up.
Computer, Captain's musk.
The long, dramatic corridor.
That's never a good sign.
Glove recognized.
Proceed, Mrs. Eisenhower.
Mr. President.
What the hell?
At ease, Brannigan.
What you're about to see
is highly classified.
Reptilicus,
hit the thingy.
At oh-zero-hundred hours,
planet X-3 was attacked by
a mysterious death-sphere.
Magnify that death-sphere.
Why is it still blurry?
That's all the
resolution we have.
Making it bigger
doesn't make it clearer.
It does on CSI: Miami.
They fought back with
advanced military hardware,
but it was like shooting
bbs at Bebe Rebozo.
That poor, brave hardware.
The sphere then fired some
kind of hellish blackout ray.
Erased that planet like 18
minutes of incriminating tape.
Oh, I just wish
I understood why.
Why I should care.
Because the death-sphere
is now on course for Earth.
Aroo!
My God, we're defenseless,
like fish in a barrel.
Options?
My instinct is
to hide in this barrel
like the wily fish.
Ah, then we're down
to our last hope:
A radical new weapon built
by a visionary scientist
I once dismissed as crazy.
Let's see how crazy
I am now, Nixon.
The correct answer is "very."
All right, Professor,
sock it to me.
Top secret news, everyone.
I've developed a tiny,
one-man stealth fighter
that's virtually undetectable.
How undetectable?
It's right in front of you.
I find that...
Ow! ...To believe.
Hubba, hubba.
But how exactly is this
happy meal toy going
to destroy a giant
death-sphere?
From within.
This ship should be able
to sneak, undetected,
through the sphere's
one vulnerable opening.
What vulnerable opening?
All death-spheres have
one vulnerable opening.
Well, sure, but who's brave
enough to fly into something
we all keep calling
a death-sphere?
I say Brannigan.
I say no.
- I say me.
- I say Leela.
- I say yes.
- I say no.
I say Leela, too.
I say yes again.
I say I shall join her.
But it's only a one-man craft.
I say.
There'll only be
one man... Me.
How would you feel
if I rode rear
as your personal
tail gunner?
Creeped out.
Then it's decided.
Cape Knievel
Flight Test Center
Are you sure I have
to sit in your lap?
It'll help us achieve
maximum thrust.
I made you some trail mix
for the flight.
Also, this picture,
to remember me.
You hold onto it.
I'll be back soon.
Aah!
Activating stealth shielding.
Liftoff!
I'll Roger that.
Does anybody else feel aroused
and jealous and worried?
I haven't felt
much of anything
since my Guinea pig died.
Death-sphere in range.
Engaging holographic targeting.
Activating the force.
Male voice
Feel the entrance, Leela.
Destination on your left
in 0.3 miles.
Zapp to Leela.
Look at all that
surveillance equipment.
We better whisper.
Switching to pillow talk mode.
Look! What are
those huge letters?
V-giny?
Doesn't ring a bell.
Hmm, I don't like
the looks of this V-giny.
Does anyone recognize
those call letters?
Nope.
It's not in the
janeway's guide either.
Deciphering that I.D. Code
is critical.
I'll be in the chamber
of understanding.
This is it... the moment we
should have trained for.
Holy cr...
Incoming yucky.
Firing pocket-rocket!
Don't panic, Leela.
Go, go, go, go, go.
I hope this is
the control stick.
Captain's log.
We've lost control.
Addendum...
Chapter two:
"The heat thickens."
Leela, wake up.
I can't face this
mysterious planet alone
without you
or someone like you.
Zapp?
Zapp, wake up.
Leela, where are we?
We crashed
on an uncharted planet.
When I woke up,
I was pinned under this tree.
Can you help me?
If anyone can
move it, I can.
No one can move it.
Are you hurt?
No, but I'm so thirsty.
This space suit is making me
sweat like a sow.
Me, too.
We'd better strip them off
and continue surviving
au naturel.
Uh... I suppose so.
Here, we can
cover ourselves
with these sticky,
sap-covered leaves.
I'll try to avert my eyes
from your nudery.
You will?
Eh, what's the point?
You'll have to look
sooner or later.
Well, I promise
not to abuse the privilege.
For now I'd better
scout ound
for food and
water and help.
What a thoughtful
and considerate thing to say.
What the hell's wrong with you?
I'm not quite sure.
Perhaps it's the fresh air
or a severe head injury.
In any case, I'm off.
If you see any steaks,
that'd be good!
Why isn't Leela back yet?
Do you think she's okay?
How should I know?
And how come you
never ask if I'm okay?
I'm feeling
a little neglected here.
Oh, sorry.
Are you okay, Bender?
Shut up.
What difference
does it make?
When that death-sphere
gets here,
we'll all be blown
to manwich meat.
Well, I guess
it's time to indulge
in some end-of-the-world
debauchery.
Who's up for an orgy?
Maybe a parcheesi
tournament.
Belay that parcheesi tournament.
I've identified
the death-sphere.
We may yet have
a faint hope of survival.
Still, a parcheesi tournament.
This is a top secret
military satellite
launched by the
air force in 1998.
And this is a top
secret FCC  satellite
launched that same year
to censor indecent
TV programs.
Like The Pimpsons
and Ass-o-rama?
Precisely.
However, the satellites collided
shortly after launch
and were never heard from again.
I found the board!
Now I've simulated
that collision
using shrapnel-vision.
V-giny!
Granted, all that makes
perfect sense.
But why is this death-sphere
destroying planets?
That makes
the most sense of all.
Lookt the planets
it's destroyed so far.
First came X-3 the
nude beach planet,
then Poopiter,
and finally that world
that can't be mentioned
in polite company.
You mean...
How dare you.
So the death-sphere
is "censoring"
indecent planets?
Indeed, and we're next,
if we can't keep it in
our collective pants.
Our sole hope is to persuade
the people of earth
to abandon their
smutty ways.
So the orgy's off?
So thirsty.
Why couldn't a water fountain
have fallen on me?
I couldn't find any
water, but the moisture
in these fruit-nut-berries
should sustain you.
Thank you.
I climbed perilously high
into the trees to pick them,
yet I saw no sign
of intelligent life.
Bummer.
Moreover, the crash
totally destroyed our ship.
So we're stuck here
until someone finds us?
Alas, that may
never happen.
Stealth technology makes the
ship impossible to locate,
yet easy to stub
your crotch on.
Well, there's worse places
to be marooned.
Plenty of food, mild climate.
I's a veritable garden of eden.
It is?
Hello.
Did that snake say hello?
No. We're both delirious
from dehydration.
Just like
Adam and Eve.
We can still save Earth.
People are sure
to clean up their act
when presented
with cold, hard facts
by rational folks like us.
The end is near!
Repent thy sins!
I'll thinks it overs
while I engages
is five-dollar hooker.
Don't do it!
It's not worth it!
Okay, make it three dollars.
Yuck! I don't wants
no three-dollar hooker.
I'm going backs
to the adults bookstore.
Adult bookstore?
I thought this was
the public library.
No. Pubic library.
Zapp? Where are you?
Oh, God, I'm actually
starting to miss him.
Maybe you two
belong together.
We do not.
And you can't talk.
Oh, come on.
It must be
an awful temptation.
Guess who just killed a
woodchuck with his bare feet?
I thought I'd whip
us up some shelter.
Make this a little
more like home.
I do miss
the Earth terribly.
I wonder if it's
even still there?
Let's find out together.
I'll brave
the ship's wreckage to
fetch you the telescope.
That's so sweet.
I'm just sayin', is all.
I know my new plan
is a long shot,
but it's the
only hope left.
Well, now
I've heard everything.
On my iPod.
So, do you have a new plan,
Professor?
And is there any hope left?
Indeed. We're here on
Earth's last unspoiled acre
to show the death-sphere
there's still purity
in the world.
Begin transmitting.
Commence purity chant.
Hey, I'm proud of you, Bender...
avoiding sin
for almost a full minute.
Bender?
Oh yeah, baby,
you're quite a dish.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, no. Oh, yeah.
Ooh!
- Oh, no.
- Bender, stop!
Stop!
Eh, quiet your riot.
What's the worst
that could happen?
No... no!
Earth is gone!
We're the only two humans
left in the universe!
Oh, God, I'm sorry, Leela.
Maybe... maybe
this was meant to be.
Maybe you and I were meant
to build a new world here.
We can avoid
humanity's mistakes.
Like the tuba.
Yes!
We'll be like
Adam and Eve.
Only without the tuba.
And we'll beget
little Zapp junior.
And Leela junior.
And they'll have kids
of their own.
Yuck! Is that really
what happened in the Bible?
It's a sick and twisted book
of holiness, all right.
Then we'll write our own Bible.
With less Sodom
and more Gomorrah.
Let's do it.
I shall become the
mother of a new world,
trapped here,
under this tree.
The tree of knowledge.
Look, it even has apples!
Ow! Wow!
Come here, Adam.
Partake of my
forbidden fruit.
Thee will be done.
Wait. One more bite
before we begin the begetting.
Mmm. Juicy.
Those nut-berries
you found were so salty,
I couldn't think straight.
I mean, not to belabor it,
but they were as salty
as that bag of trail mix
Fry gave me.
Exactly as salty.
Hey! Wait a second!
Uh...
Oh...
I have a terrible
confession to make.
You see, when I first
went foraging,
what I actually found
was the smoldering wreckage
of the ship.
Ignoring all danger, I charged
inside to liberate
our provisions.
So this is the trail mix
Fry gave me!
Yes. I exaggerated when I said
I picked it from the treetops.
I just wanted
you to think...
A little better of me.
Well... your motives were good.
And we were both loopy
from dehydration.
Hey, wait.
You've been doing
an awful lot of urinating.
There's plenty of water.
You see,
after I selflessly rescued
the trail mix,
i braved the flames once more,
in search of fluids.
Then why didn't you give me any?
I thought it might
help you forget
your intense hatred for me if
you were a teensy bit delirious.
So you let me dehydrate
while you washed down
the trail mix
with imported mineral water?
Not exactly.
You see, besides the trail mix,
the minibar also contained
doritos, beef jerky,
and a generous assortment
of fine chocolates.
I wanted to offer you
the chocolates...
I truly did... but I was
concerned about your waistline.
Very concerned.
It's because
I haven't been exercising.
If only this tree hadn't
fallen on me by chance.
Oh, dear God!
It was just after we crashed.
I awoke first,
to find you trapped.
Leela!
Leela, wake up.
You could've moved this
grub-infested log
any time you wanted?
Well, sure...
But then I wouldn't have been
able to provide the loving care
you wouldn't have needed.
I'd leave you to rot
in this paradise,
if only the ship
weren't destroyed.
The ship's fully
functional, isn't it?
You see, after re-trapping you
and before feigning
unconsciousness,
i paused to enjoy a cigar.
Though mellow and satisfying,
it did parch me a bit,
so I went in search of Brandy.
That's when my keen
senses detected
the still-invisible ship.
Ow!
So we can go back to Earth?
But there is no
Earth anymore!
Everyone I know is dead!
Ah, this seems like a good
place to take a dump.
Leela?! You're alive!
Fry!
But how did you
find this planet?
Well?
We're actually on Earth.
The ship's homing device
brought us back.
But I saw Earth explode.
I'm actually kind of proud
of this one.
You see, what you saw
was merely a simulation
I rigged up,
using the ship's holographic
targeting projector.
The alleged "telescope"
was a toilet paper tube.
You said there wasn't
any toilet paper!
And that humanity was
annihilated!
My motives were pure.
I just wanted to you to think
we had to save humanity
so you'd be willing
to have sex.
Please say you believe me.
Yes, I believe you.
Hee-ya!
Yay!
There must be something to
steal on this island.
Hey, it's Leela.
Let's go home, everybody.
At least the world
wasn't destroyed.
Yet.
People of Earth!
Hear the righteous word
of the mighty V-giny!
The mighty V-giny!
Seeing you frolic
in this unspoiled garden
gives hope that this world
may yet be redeemed.
Huzzah!
The purity chant worked!
Unacceptable wardrobe
malfunction!
I was referring
to Adam and Eve!
We're not Adam and Eve.
You see, due to a series of...
Consummate your union,
or I shall destroy Earth.
Well... if it's to
save Earth...
I guess I could
take one for the team.
Uh, what? Right now?!
But I need a romance first.
Maybe a vanilla candle
or something?
Commence intercourse!
Those giant guns are
making me feel sort
of inadequate.
I'm not sure if I can...
Move it. I gotta get
home and do laundry.
For God's sake, censor it!
Censor it!
Approved for all audiences!
No!
And now,
the spicy finale of...
That was a close call,
but we saved Earth.
Was it as good for you as
it was for the human race?
Oh, Zapp.
Let's save another
planet right now!
Sync by n17t01, corrected by gloriabg
www.Addic7ed.Com
www.tvsubtitles.net