Sync by n17t01, corrected by gloriabg
www.addic7ed.com
(Snoring)
(Female giggles)
Bender (Loud whisper):
Shh! Don't wake up Fry.
(Ladybot giggling)
Shh! My roommate's sleeping!
(Giggling continues)
- Wake up already!
- (Snorts) Huh?
I'm about to get down
and funky with this ladybot,
and I'd appreciate it
if as many people as possible
could know about it.
Now can we get some privacy?!
(Jackhammer rattling)
(Both giggling)
(Backup warning beeping)
Bender:
Aw, yeah! Back it on up.
(Both giggling)
(Jackhammer rattling)
(Bluegrass music playing)
♪ Hambone, hambone! ♪
♪ hambone! ♪
Okay, Hambone break's over.
Back to the bedroom!
(Jackhammer rattling,
pneumatic tools whirring)
Bender and ladybot:
♪ Hambone, hambone! ♪
(groans loudly)
Bender:
♪ Hambone! ♪
(snoring)
Wake up and feel the coffee!
(Spluttering)
Oh, no, I'm late for work again!
(Panting) Sorry I'm late.
Well, well, well.
Look who decided to show up.
I've had it with your tardiness, Fry.
I expect you to arrive the same
time as everyone else.
Well, wait a second.
Leela's not here yet.
She left a while ago.
She said some idiot
was taking her to lunch
for her birthday.
Oh, no, I'm late!
(Panting)
(Indistinct chattering,
fingers drumming on table)
(Noisemaker bleats)
Since you got stood up,
I thought this might
cheer you up a notch.
That's not necessary.
♪ What day is today? ♪
- ♪ it's Leela's birthday ♪
- Please stop.
♪ What a day for a birthday ♪
I really would like you
to stop singing.
♪ Let's all have some cake! ♪
you want to buy a slice
of birthday cake for $11.95?
Yes, please.
(Panting):
Uh, nice cake.
Sorry I'm late.
Where have you...?!
Uh! It's fine.
You're not mad?
I was. But then I realized
it's actually my fault for thinking
you might be on time for once.
Anyhow, I ate both our lunches.
You ordered the lobster pileup.
It wasn't cheap.
Bam!
Please, let me make it up to you.
I'll treat you to a fancy
birthday dinner tonight
at Cavern on the Green.
Wow, that'll be
the nicest place I've
ever been stood up.
Not this time.
No matter what happens,
I swear I'll be there.
Guys, guys! Hedonismbot
is finally gonna settle down
and marry a nice house
in the suburbs!
But tonight, he's having
the girls gone wildest
bachelor party of all time!
Whoo-who-who...
Cares?
I'm having dinner with leela.
(Sighs)
Just go to your stupid party.
We can have dinner on my
birthday some other year.
No! I can throw up
on a stripper anytime.
Tonight, I want to not throw up...
On you.
Really?
Your loss.
Hey, Professor, you're my wingman!
Very well.
Cubert, fetch my drinking teeth.
(Crickets chirping)
I just have to sign
leela's birthday card.
- How do you spell "XO"?
- Guh!
It's a record-your-own-message
card.
You don't sign it. You leave
a nude video greeting.
Does it have to be nude?
I guess not.
That never occurred to me.
If I leave now, record a
birthday greeting on the way,
score some fancy cologne
at the newsstand,
I'll be exactly on time.
You're not going anywhere!
But I have a date.
You were late this morning,
so you have to stay and test
my latest invention!
Behold!
A time-traveling machine!
(Both gasp)
Time? I can't go back there!
Ah, but this time machine
only goes forward in time!
That way you can't accidentally
change history
or do something disgusting, like
sleep with your own grandmother.
I wouldn't want to do that again.
We're going to test it
by going forward in time one minute.
(Alarm chirps) Get in.
Okay, hurry. Let's get it over with.
I can record Leela's birthday card
while we're in there.
(Softly):
Happy Birthday, Leela!
I'm really sorry I'm gonna be
one minute late,
'cause we're testing the Professor's
dumb time machine, but...
Okay, I'll just nudge us forward
exactly one minute into the...
Whoa!
(All yelling) My card!
Did we go too far?!
What time is it?!
Bender:
The year 10,000.
Professor: Whoopsy!
Oh, dear.
I mean, oh, my.
The year 10,000?!
But I promised Leela
I'd be on time for dinner!
Relax, Fry.
Everyone we ever knew
died thousands of years ago.
Everyone we ever knew?
Ah, I never liked those guys.
(Wind whistling)
(All gasp)
No! They did it!
They blew it up!
And then the apes blew up
their society, too!
How could this happen?!
And then the birds took over
and ruined their society!
And the cows, and then...
I don't know.
Is that a slug maybe?
No...!
Cavern on the Green.
The year 3010
(vehicle whooshes)
(Lively piano music playing)
(Water dripping)
While you await your "friend,"
allow me to read
from a prepared history
of our Cavern.
These unique
rock formations were created
over millions of years
by mineral-rich water
dripping from pores in the ceiling.
(Echoing):
dripping and dripping,
year upon year,
(low and distorted):
century upon century...
♪ What day is today? ♪
Hey, aren't you the loser
who got stood up
at my other restaurant?
Just shut up and
bring me two dinners.
Has anyone seen Fry's ass?
It's late for a date with my boot.
Fry's not here.
Obviously, he went
to that pervert party
with Bender and the Professor.
(Snorts)
Fry went to the party?
Linda (On tv):
We interrupt hypnotoad on ice
to bring you breaking coverage
of the disaster
at Hedonismbot's bachelor party.
(All gasp)
Linda, what began as innocent
fun ended in tragedy tonight
when a nuclear-powered
robot stripper
suffered a catastrophic
reactor meltdown.
There is only one survivor.
Everywhere I looked,
there were piles of bodies.
And then the explosion struck.
(Sobbing)
The three co-workers I liked
are all dead!
Fry stood me up and died?!
I'm so angry!
I mean, I'm so sad!
But... But I'm still pretty angry!
But also sad.
Can I be both?
It's what he'd want.
Then that's what I am!
Hi-ya! (Sobbing)
(Fire crackling)
Man, the future is a total craphole,
and whoever lives here
is a crap-faced sack of crap!
No offense, fellas.
Don't sweat it, man.
(Sighs)
I'll never see Leela again.
No, without a backwards
time machine,
we're stuck in this craphole.
- Dude, give it a rest.
- Hold on.
I've got it!
We can't go back in time,
but we can keep going forward
until people invent
the backwards time machine.
And then we can go home.
Hit it.
(To the tune of
"In the year 2525")
♪ In the year 105105 ♪
♪ if man is still alive ♪
♪ if robot can survive ♪
♪ they may find... ♪
♪ In the year 252525 ♪
♪ the backwards time machine
still won't have arrived ♪
♪ in all the world,
there's only one technology ♪
♪ a rusty sword
for practicing proctology ♪
whoa! Oh!
♪ In a future year
that ends with 20 ♪
♪ a shlubby merman's
gonna try to get chummy ♪
♪ he may look like a watery wimp ♪
(Laughing)
♪ When in fact
he's a bloodthirsty shrimp! ♪
(roars)
♪ In the year one million
and a half ♪
♪ humankind is enslaved
by giraffe ♪
♪ man must pay
for all his misdeeds ♪
♪ when the treetops
are stripped of their leaves ♪
♪ Whoa-oa-oa. ♪
(vehicles whooshing)
(Whooshing)
Sometimes I can't believe
how successful
Planet Express became
once the Professor was killed
and you seized control.
There were tough times,
but we all pulled together.
I've been crunching the numbers
on our trans-galactic strategy...
What are you doing here?
I laid you off 20 years ago.
Woop-woop-woop-woo...
Oh, the claws can't flee
like they used to.
Success is nice,
but I do kind of miss the old days.
(Slurps)
Hey, Leels.
(Flirty):
Hi, Cubert.
(Whoosh)
(Adenoidal voice):
May we help you, strange ones?
We are travelers from the past,
my good runt.
I see.
Since your time, human
evolution has diverged.
There are we... Advanced in
intellect and morality...
And the dumblocks...
Stupid, vicious brutes
who live underground.
Advanced in intellect, you say?
Have you invented a
backwards time machine?
No, but if we apply
our superior minds,
we could perfect such a
device within five years.
See you then!
(Whooshes)
We're back for our time machine!
(Grunts)
Ow!
(Lasers zapping)
(Time machine whooshes)
(Gasping, panting)
Yoo-hoo, boys!
What's this era in human history like?
The machines...
We built them to make
our lives easier,
but they rebelled.
They won't stop
until every human is dead.
This seems like a nice future.
Let's just stay here.
We could settle down
on that mountain of skulls.
Hey! That place had
a gorgeous view
of Blood Lake!
Greetings, time travelers.
Stupid jerks!
Wouldn't let me stay
in the good future.
How did you know
we're time travelers?
We, too, study
the time travel enigma.
We have perfected a
method using negative-mass
neutrino fields that allows us
to travel backwards in time.
My name's Hubert.
All right! We can go home!
(Mocking): All right!
We can go... (Blows raspberry)
We can talk of our research
tomorrow.
Men are very rare in our society.
Even very old and
stupid males are prized.
Tonight, please be the guests of
honor at our fertility banquet.
Well, there's certainly no harm
in a fertility banquet.
I could eat.
And fertilize.
Very well.
Let us anoint our guests in oil
without using our hands.
Oh, so we can stay
in the future you like,
but not the future I like?
Next!
No!
I was about to close the deal!
Bender, they had
a backwards time machine!
The other place had a lot
of good things, too!
Did you even see
that mountain of skulls?
Why, you!
Oh, no, you didn't.
(All grunting)
Stop!
Somewhere, some time,
Leela is waiting for me.
We need to keep looking
for a backwards time machine.
Fry's right.
Yes. We have to work together,
not have this fight,
which I was definitely winning.
Professor:
The year one billion.
I've got a feeling this could be
exactly the point in time
we've been looking for!
(Wind whistling)
Professor: Nope.
(Trilling)
(Buzzer sounds)
In fact, all life is extinct.
(Laughs)
So let's keep going forward.
Oh, it's no use.
Earth is dead.
This is the end of all things.
The Cavern on the Green.
(Echoing):
I made it, Leela.
Sorry I'm a billion years late.
(Gasps)
Dear Fry
You'll get your alimony check, Cubert.
Now get lost!
Chill out.
I'm just here to see Amy.
Move it, boy toy.
Granny's taking you
to Atlantic City.
I don't know why you ever
married that pig-nosed punk.
I don't know, either.
I'm married to the job now.
I used to think
there was someone for me, but...
Ow!
How odd.
It's one of those old
record-your-own-message
birthday cards.
(Music plays)
(Softly):
Happy Birthday, Leela!
I'm really sorry
I'm gonna be one minute late,
'cause we're testing the
Professor's dumb time machine...
Okay, I'll just nudge us forward...
But, uh, you know, um, happy
birthday and all, and, uh...
Exactly one minute into the...
I love you.
Whoa!
(All yelling)
Fry: My card!
Leela: Ow!
My whole life I've been mad
at him, and it wasn't his fault.
(Whooshing)
(High-pitched whooshing)
(Water dripping)
Leela (Reading):
Dear Fry, our time together was short
but it was the best time of my life.
(Loud splash of water)
You know, all in all,
I had a good life.
What do you say
the three of us grab a six-pack
and watch the universe end?
Hear! Hear!
That's basically
what I do every day.
To the end of the universe!
(Loud whoosh)
(Trilling)
(Loud whooshing)
(Explosion)
So long, Earth.
Thanks for the air and whatnot.
(Whooshing)
(Popping)
All:
Whoa!
Hey, uh, what was the purpose
of life, anyway?
Who knows.
Probably some hogwash
about the human spirit.
- Mm-hmm.
- Sounds about right.
(Whooshing)
Professor:
The stars are receding.
Oh, the vast emptiness!
Yeah, yeah, I can take a hint.
(Trilling)
Ah.
The last proton should be
decaying about now.
Bye, last proton.
And... here we are.
The end of the universe.
Well, now what?
You guys want to talk?
No, thanks.
- Ooh! Oh!
- Wow! Oh!
Did anyone else see that?!
Unbelievable!
It's a second Big Bang!
(Whooshing)
My God, is it possible?
It must be possible. It's happening.
By the way, what's happening?
It appears this universe
is exactly identical
to the old one.
If so, we just need
to keep going forward in time
to the point when we left!
(Whooshing)
(Explosive pops)
The Earth is born!
(Rumbling)
(Whoosh and explosion)
Professor:
Ladies and gentlemen, the Moon!
Look. The first fish
to crawl up on land.
Bender (Grunts):
it was coming right at us!
You saw it.
I'm gonna grab another beer.
Fry, Fry, you're
missing the dinosaurs!
It's okay. They're not
going anywhere.
Where'd they go?
(Weapons firing)
(Gunfire)
(Gunshots)
Now, what's going on there?
History.
Hang on. I just want
to make one stop.
(Whoosh)
(Gun chamber cocking)
(Loud cheering)
Betrachten sie meinen
schnurrbart!
(High-pitched whirring, poof)
(Whoosh)
(Soft crackling sound)
(Explosions)
Professor:
Easy. Easy.
Taking her in for a landing.
One year to go.
Six months.
I'm almost there, Leela.
One month...
Two weeks...
One hour...
30 seconds...
And here we...
Professor: Whoa!
(Thudding)
Stop!
Give me the keys, Magoo!
(Fry grunting)
We'll have to bring her
around again.
(Trilling)
(Whooshing)
(Pop)
(Explosive whirring)
Just slow it down. I'll shoot
Hitler out the window.
(Whirring)
Darn! I hit Eleanor
Roosevelt by mistake.
Okay, nearing our era again.
Here we go.
Careful this time.
Careful.
We're going to test it
by going forward
in time one minute.
(Alarm chirps) Get in.
Okay. Hurry.
Let's get it over with.
(Whirring) Wha...?
Professor:
Uh-oh.
This new universe is about
ten feet lower than our old one.
Pow! We took care of
the time travel paradox.
- All right!
- Hooray!
Yabba-dabba-doo!
Uh-oh. I'm late for dinner with Leela.
(Fry panting)
(Water dripping)
Welcome to cavern on the green.
May I offer you some meat loaf
while you wait?
(Panting) Sorry I'm late!
- Actually, you're on time.
- Really?
I have to admit, I was
afraid you wouldn't make it.
(Sputters)
That was the old Fry.
He's dead now.
Fry: Happy Birthday, Leela.
I got you a card, but I
guess I kind of lost it.
That's okay.
I don't really like cards.
What I'll remember
is our time together.
Sync by n17t01, corrected by gloriabg
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net