♪ Two... two, three... ♪
Sync and correction by Mlmlte
www.addic7ed.com
Run, Leela!
They're bouncing right at us.
So, anybody hungry?
I could stuff myself.
I'll use that free app
that tells
what restaurants you're near.
You mean the window?
Yes.
I am lrrr, ruler
of the planet Omicron Persei 8!
I demand extra dipping sauce!
How many?
I don't know. Two?
Welcome to Fishy Joe's.
Today is Stroganoff Thursday.
We are currently out
of the following menu items.
Stroganoff.
May I take your order?
I'll have the Stroganoff.
Okay.
Yeah, uh, give me
the fried spaghetti-dinner
breakfast pocket for lunch,
and a big bucket
of mixed sodas.
One kids' meal.
Got it.
Huh. Buggalo tots?
What exactly
are those made out of?
You got a warrant?
I'll just have something
from the lite menu.
How about the
gardener-lover's salad?
What kind of cheese filling
you want in that?
Ugh! Just give me the fruit cup.
Okeydoke.
What kind of cheese filling
you want in that?
Oh, God.
Fruit is spelled f-r-o-o-t.
And it's got quotation marks
around it.
Mmm. There's nothing wrong
with a little fast food
once or twice a meal.
Heart... at-tack.
I'm fine.
Oh! I got a bone in my fruit!
That's it.
From now on,
we're not eating anything
unless we know what it is
and where it's from.
We're going
to the local farmers market.
Aw, mom, do we have to?
This is what I'm talking about.
See all the dirt and earwigs?
That's the sign
of healthy food.
You think that's healthy,
try this.
I found it growing
at the bottom of my hamper.
Mmm, so fresh and musty.
It's what I do.
Hello, tiny man.
You want sample small-batch
Amazonian maple syrup?
Sure.
Mm. Ah!
That's the kind of sap I like.
You the kind
of sap I like.
I'm scare-roused.
Zuban tobacco?!
The richest, most
obnoxious kind!
Listen, pal, I'm looking
for a versatile smoke,
one that's equally good
in a crowded elevator
or an audience with the pope.
Forget the pope, my friend.
Smoke one of these,
and God himself will ask
to be seated far away from you.
Ooh!
Heirloom eggs?
That's so life-affirming.
I'll bet you run
your own hatchery,
just you and your wife...
Matilda.
No, ma'am. Matilda and I gather
them eggs in the forest.
And Matilda's really more
of a mongoose than a wife.
You're a lucky man.
But are they way more expensive
than regular eggs?
Way more.
Ooh! I'll take a dozen.
What?
You're not my breakfast friends.
What are you doing here?
Leela blackmailed us all into
eating healthy, organic food.
Blackmail? What
does she have on you?
As long as we eat
her filthy scrambled eggs,
you'll never find out.
They're not filthy.
They're wholesome, fertile
and fresh from the forest floor.
There's some filth.
"Fertile"? What does that mean?
It means it will hatch
into a tiny, little,
infant creature unless
we cook it first.
Hey, Leela, hurry up
with those scrambled infants.
What?! That's horrifying!
Zoidberg,
you're an inhuman monster.
What are you, my
driver's license?
Eating a sweet innocent chick
before it's even hatched?
Oh, no, you won'tn't!
I refuse to eat
an unborn animal.
I'm going to keep this egg safe
and warm and secure
until it hatches out
into the world.
And then I'm going to eat it.
♪ ♪
Should we turn on the TV?
Nah.
Bender, do you mind?
I'm roosting.
I'm considering buying a yacht
to house my thoroughbreds.
How do you expect me to do that
without smoking a cigar?
Think of the unborn embryo.
That's what
I'm gonna call the yacht.
Hey!
Leggo my eggo, crabbo!
Stop it, Fry.
That's sexual harassment.
Yeah, come down off your
round, white pulpit.
You're just going to
eat that thing anyway.
I was, but you can't
sit on something
for a week without falling
in love with it.
Whoever's in here
deserves a chance at life.
A chance to blossom
into a beautiful young man,
like I did as a baby.
And so I make this solemn vow.
To do everything I can
to make sure
this wonderful,
innocent creature
enters this world happy,
healthy, and...
All yours, Zoidberg.
Aw, look at the cute little...
Aah!
I was gonna go yachting
in those feet!
Relax, you babies.
It's no different
from stomping a puppy.
Everyone, stop!
He's not going to hurt you.
I'm standing in a pool
of my own feet.
Bender's right. Kill it
before someone names it!
No! Mr. Peppy just wants
to be our friend.
Oy. Look, I know he's ugly,
and kind of corrosive,
but we can't murder someone
just 'cause he's
hideous and annoying.
That's what we said
about Zoidberg,
and look where that got us.
Amy has a point.
Mr. Peppy's not
like Zoidberg.
He's my friend.
Aw...
♪ ♪
Where to, adulterers?
Calculon?! Then it
wasn't your body
they found in the harbor
after the bomb went off.
What bomb?
It takes more than that
to surprise me... Bender.
What you doing, little buddy?
Uh, yeah, Uncle Bender--
he's your friend.
Huh?
Oh, you want to play fetch.
Come on, boy, get the ball.
Dumb jerk.
Come on, get the ball.
Sweet freak of Mozambique,
that thing's colossal!
It's gonna kill us all.
It's so huge.
How big does one
of those things get?
Well, that depends on what
one of those things is.
That seems like a
fact worth knowing.
Good startling news, everyone.
I found a description
of the creature
in this medieval
monster manual.
Just as I feared.
Attack-type J.
No! No!
Yes! It kills its prey
by sucking out the skeleton,
leaving nothing
but a puddle of flesh.
Ew!
Hence, the Latin name
Bonus Vampirus,
or as you non-catholics
would say, the Bone Vampire.
Dios mio.
That's ridiculous!
Mr. Peppy doesn't eat bones.
I raised him on a simple diet of
brussels sprouts and mixed soda.
At least there's
only one of them.
The good news is, they
can't start breeding.
The bad news, everyone, is,
the beast reproduces asexually.
A single bone vampire,
left alone with some quiet music
and some bone vampire porn,
could produce dozens
of deadly offspring.
That lucky bastard.
I say kill it!
But it loves me, and I love it!
Kill them both!
Killing them seems
like a hassle.
Can't we just set it free
to live with its own kind?
Poor, ignorant Leela.
The bone vampire is now extinct
on its home planet.
That's perfect.
We can reintroduce it to the
wild and repopulate the species.
Yeah, let's do
those Leela things.
Well, buddy,
how do you like your new home?
See, he's happy already.
That thing doesn't have
emotions, Fry.
Its brain is the size
of a walnut.
So are walnuts, and
they're delicious.
I'll miss you, Mr. Peppy,
but you'll be happier here.
So go on, go.
G-good-bye, Mr. Peppy.
Come on, man, don't do this.
Go on now.
I mean it, don't make this
any harder than it has to be.
It's time to let go.
Ow!
Thanks, Leela, he just needed
a little extra push.
Come on, Fry, let's go home and
Hold up, there's alcohol
around here somewhere.
My tanqueraydar is going crazy.
Aha!
Thought you could get
away from me, huh?
You lose again,
you stupid intoxicant.
♪ ♪
We're not from around here.
Hello.
Airwhilka maur fleegle
bingo drooper snrk!
Excuse me, but we're guests
on your planet.
Speak English!
Behave yourselves, gents.
Offworlders best be
welcome here,
especially if we're trying
to get the Olympics.
May I buy you a drink?
We don't get a lot
of pretty faces around here.
Uh, sure,
but I'm driving.
I'll just have the smallest
whiskey you've got.
A small aquarium of whiskey
for the busty lass.
Thanks. I suppose
I should know your name
if I'm going to be drinking
ten gallons
of alcohol with you.
Maczongo.
Angus Maczongo.
Major Angus Maczongo.
Handsome Major Angus Maczongo,
Esquire.
Ooh, handsome and Esquire.
I'm Turanga Leela.
My crew and I are from Earth.
So what brings you folks
here to Doohan 6?
We just released an endangered
animal back into the wild--
a bone vampire.
No need to thank us.
Your shocked stares of gratitude
say it all.
Dear God, you brought
back the bone vampire?!
The damned things wreaked
bloody havoc
on our livestock for centuries.
Aye, until Maczongo here
shot 'em all
into extinction, he did.
Now we've got more livestock
than we can slaughter.
Oh, aye, 'tis a Bonnie time
to be an ignorant villager.
We kinna have no murdering
bone vampires back here.
Kill it afore it puts a bun
in its own oven
and repopulates
the bleeding planet.
No!
Angus is right.
I thought you were named Angus.
We're all named Angus.
Please, Mr. Peppy won't attack
your livestock.
He's a vegetarian, and he's
not even preachy about it.
Poppycock.
Once he gets the smell of bones,
there'll be no stopping him.
Tonight, Mr. Peppy must die.
Angus, wait, my strictly
platonic friend is right.
At least wait a few days
before you decide to kill it.
The last time I hesitated,
a bone vampire snicked out
me left shin.
Please, just a few days.
Well, 'twould give us a chance
to get to know each other.
The beast lives... for now.
Thank you, Angus.
You're welcome!
I don't trust that Maczongo.
Maybe I should go keep
an eye on Mr. Peppy.
Don't worry about Maczongo.
He and I are having
brunch tomorrow.
I'm thinking of wearing this.
It's nice, but there's
still something
I don't like about that guy.
My dad always said you could
tell a lot about a man
by the rigidity of his shins.
What is it?
Lang a muir a Gryffindor-
Slytherin hufflepuff!
It killed little Angus!
They're all dead, and
their bones are gone.
This was no accident.
Still think your Mr. Peppy
is harmless, Fry?
He wouldn't do this
in our sleep.
He would not,
could not to a sheep.
The deal is off.
The beast must die.
Ooh, pimpy.
What are we supposed to do,
just sit here and wait
for Mr. Peppy to be killed?
Sounds like a plan.
Guess I'll pass the time
by lighting up an El Jerko.
Okay, that's it.
I need some air.
Who's there?
Hermes, is this one
of your zany practical jokes?
Leela, are you okay?
Did you drink too many aquaria?
Look, the bone vampire.
Mr. Peppy attacked me.
Quick, count my bones.
There should be 205.
Okay, that's better.
Keep 'em coming.
I'm sorry, Fry,
but no vegetarian
could have done this.
I know, and as much as I love
Mr. Peppy, I love Leela more.
He has to be...
...Put down.
Aw, don't feel bad.
Major Maczongo
is an experienced hunter.
He'll blow Mr. Peppy's head off
as painlessly as possible.
No, not Maczongo.
If anyone is going to kill
Mr. Peppy, it should be me.
Fry, I know you're
upset right now,
but I hope you'll
consider donating
the body to science dinner.
Here, Mr. Peppy.
Mmm, lovely bones.
We've been walking for hours.
I hope we can find
our way back.
Don't worry, I left
a trail of bread crumbs.
And I left a trail of cigars.
You don't have to do this, Fry.
Mr. Peppy just gave me
a little love concussion.
Thanks, Leela, but
I have no choice.
I can't let my monstrous
deboner get anywhere near you.
There it is!
Well, this is it.
You guys wait here.
This is going to kill him
more than it does me.
Good-bye, boy.
I'll think of you whenever I sit
on something round.
What's happening?
Did you kill it?
The bloody idiot bloody shot me.
I'm all bloody bloody!
Mr. Peppy,
bullets make you talk?
That's not Mr. Peppy.
Jinkies, he Scooby-Dooed us.
Why, Major Maczongo, why?
Oh, it's been 30 years since
last I killed a bone vampire.
The villagers dinna idolize me
like they used to.
You seemed pretty popular
at the pub.
I work there as a greeter.
Your beast was my chance
to be a hero again,
but the damn thing
was a vegetarian,
so I slaughtered
the sheep myself.
But why did you attack me?
So I could impress you
by seeking revenge
on the creature.
Us greeters don't
get a lot of action.
On paper it seemed like
a win-win situation.
Do you realize
what this means, Fry?
Your pet's not dangerous
after all.
I told you Mr. Peppy's
a lover, not a fighter,
like Dwayne "The Rock"
"The Tooth Fairy" Johnson.
Hey, what's
that bone-sucking sound?
It's Mr. Peppy.
I'd know him anywhere.
Huh, so apparently
Major Maczongo
and Mr. Peppy were each doing
about half the sheep-killing.
Why, Mr. Peppy, why?
Ooh, that tickles.
Now I really do have
to kill you.
Wait,
don't shoot.
The beast is a godsend.
Like I said,
we've more livestock
than we can slaughter,
but thanks
to this ravenous bogle,
that's nae more a problem.
Angus is right.
The cursed thing
even debones 'em,
which is perfect for today's
fast-paced, lazy consumer.
Dersu uzala yojimbo,
rashomon!
The beast must live!
Sync and correction by Mlmlte
www.addic7ed.com
You know what the best part is?
From now on,
whenever we're eating
fresh, organic space-meat,
we'll know exactly
where it comes from.
One bucket of
double-fried, triple-salted,
boneless sheep tots, please.
What kind of cheese filling
you want in that?
All kinds.
Eh, make it two,
and a small whiskey. Large.
www.tvsubtitles.net