Sync by n17t01, corrected by gloriabg
www.addic7ed.com
I fear I may not survive
this war reenactment.
I can't believe we're only
12 feet from the parking lot.
This is every bit as fun
as the real Civil War.
Not the Civil War, private.
We're reenacting the Sith-al War.
Sith?
What the hoth?
Enemy invaders up in yonder sky!
I am Darth Stroyer.
Darth Stroyer?
That's the stupidest
name I've ever heard.
Let's hear the rest.
Darth Trocious.
Darth Sploder.
Darth Urderer.
Darth It-head.
Company, attack!
Don't fire till you see
the greens of their eyes.
It saves on bullets.
I shall rip out your heart
and show it to you.
It is done.
The candle that burns twice
as bright burns half as long.
Mm-hmm.
Whoa!
You're dead.
No, I'm just very old.
Whoa, that's good acting.
It's payback time, Sploder.
Tell my mother...
To pick me up outside Quizno's.
That's three dead.
Whoa-ooh.
Let's pick up the pace, people.
At this point in the actual War,
the death toll was 98 million.
You humans
and your fragile organs.
One little stab to the goo, and...
You're dead, Earth man.
Oh, cruel fate,
I'm dead.
They're putting me in my Sunday suit
and shoving me in a wooden box.
Now they're lowering me
into the cold, cold ground.
Hello, here come the worms.
If you were really dead, you
wouldn't be laughing so hard.
Yeah, yeah, death's a big deal
to you flesh bags,
but in case you didn't notice,
I'm a robot.
So? What if something heavy fell
on you, like a church?
You could still die.
Nuh-uh.
My wireless backup unit saves
a copy of me every day,
so if my body gets killed,
big whoop,
I just download into another body.
I'm immortal, baby.
What?! Then how come
you always scream
so much when you're in danger?
I never said I wasn't a drama queen.
And the winner of the war is...
Ah, let me just cross-check
my tabulation here.
Factor in the corsages
for the widows...
Hurry up,
you number-crunching crumbnuncher.
Everybody but me is
dying of old age.
Okay... ah.
The winners, at a net cost
of only $12 per life cut tragically short,
our Sith Overlords.
Hot diggity.
Oh, I mean...
Supreme diggity.
Good war, good war, good war...
It may have been a fake war, but
my scuffed knee is all too real.
I've got pains in joints
I had removed a century ago.
Bender, bring me my soft chair
with the wheels on it.
- Your wheelchair?
- I don't need a wheelchair!
The one with the wheels.
Poor flimsy humans.
Don't you wish
you were flawless like me?
A towering inferno
of physical perfection?
I hate to pop your blimp-like
ego, but you are not perfect.
- Am so.
- Are not.
- Is too.
- Says who?
Says the only human
whose opinion
I even remotely respect.
Inspector Five, the best inspector
a kid could want.
The day I was built,
he looked me over,
probably with tears
of pride in his eyes,
and proclaimed to all the world,
by means of this scrap of paper,
that I was perfect
and infallible in every way.
Hey, Mr. Perfect,
you wet the chair.
Huh? Wasn't me.
Must be some of that urine
you're all so proud of.
That's not urine. It's oil.
Impossible.
I'm triple-sealed
to prevent any chance of...
You call that an ink defense?
Good-bye, friends.
What could have caused the leak?
Excessive heat,
on account of I'm so hot?
Alas, no.
Oh, Bender, I'm afraid it's
a symptom of a fatal defect.
Eh, fatal, shmatal.
If I die, I can just
download my backup copy
into a new, equally fabulous body.
That's just it. You can't.
You were built without a backup unit.
There's no backup copy of me?
That's what I just said,
you mortal coil.
So, if I die...
You die, or as you put it...
Um, excuse me for a moment.
No...!
I can't believe it!
I'm gonna die!
How much time
does he have left, Professor?
Between a minute
and a billion years.
Well, at least
you can plan accordingly.
Dying sucks butt!
How do you living beings
cope with mortality?
- Violent outbursts.
- General sluttiness.
Thanks to denial, I'm immortal.
Damn it, I'm supposed
to be perfect!
Inspector Five gave me
his blessing!
How could he bring me into
this world, knowing I would die?
So you wish
you were never born, maybe?
Yes, anything less than immortality
is a complete waste of time.
Then suicide it is.
Step into my office.
I'll give you a nice kevorking.
Not until I hunt down
Inspector Five
and beat an explanation out of him.
I'm all for a good beating,
but you'll never find him.
Product inspectors are bureaucrats,
faceless bean-counters
who blend into the woodwork.
I beg to differ.
Stinkin' bureaucrats... I hate 'em!
Then again,
you might be able
to find Inspector Five
with the help of another
seasoned bureaucrat.
Hermes, old pal.
Old pal?
8.5 seconds ago,
you said you hated me.
Time heals all wounds.
You know what? I will help you,
but only to prove I'm not just
a paper-pushing file jockey.
Will you be taking
your portable filing cabinet?
None of your beeswax.
I'll only be away an hour,
but I'm counting on you to do
the all-critical filing in my absence.
Shall we review alphabetical order?
- ♪ A-b-c-d... ♪
- Get out of my office.
Yes, I'd like to request
a death certificate.
Sorry, that's Building C.
The Central Bureaucracy
maintains records
on all bureaucrats.
We should be able to
look up Inspector Five.
Application for ingress approved.
And the other potential entrant?
Uh... he's my pencil sharpener.
You betcha!
Proceed.
I maintain a cubicle here
for weekend getaways.
Wow.
Until now, I thought
giant cubes were exciting.
I did like the part
where they screamed.
This is mine,
right next to the Center Square.
Sorry, Hermes, I drank
all your white-out.
Once I log in, I can access
Inspector Five's profile.
Damn it, it won't go on!
That's because you're not me.
Hooray, it won't go on!
The bureaucra-scan
won't let anyone
but the assigned
bureaucrat log in.
Identity confirmed.
Also, you have a rectangular
mass in your colon.
That's a calculator.
I ate it to gain its power.
You locate Inspector five while
I slip into my ass-kicking feet.
Sweet file-not-found-of-puegot sound.
His record's been blanked.
Aw, man.
How am I gonna find
some anonymous guy
I don't know anything about?
I recommend the men's room
at the Twa Terminal.
Okay, just file it alphabetically...
♪ A-b-c-d... ♪
Well, this requires a little extra thought.
I'm a natural.
The information we need will be
here, in the physical files.
Those bastards won't know
what leafed through them.
It's on.
No! This is impossible!
Quit blacking out and look at this.
Inspector One, Two, Three, Four, Six!
There's no trace of Inspector Five!
But Five's the one we want!
Maybe if I kicked
the asses of Inspector Two,
plus Inspector Three...
Addition never solved anything, mon.
Let's cut our losses and go home.
So I'm doomed to die,
and I'll never even get
to punch whoever's responsible?!
Oh, what's the point?!
Bender, no!
Suicide isn't necessarily the answer.
It's not a suicide booth, you lard ass.
It's a phone booth.
They have phones in booths now?
Finally, I don't have
to lug this cell phone around.
Who the hell is this?
How did you get this number?
Is this the robot company?
'Cause I have a complaint
about a defective robot.
His name is me!
A defective robot, you say?
Stay right there, dearie.
I'll have tech support
take care of you.
Well, things are starting to look up.
Look up!
Who did you call, dial-a-bomb?
No, I just told the robot
company I was defective.
You dumb cocktail shaker!
Mom won't allow a defective product
to tarnish her good name!
She'll kill you!
Big whoop.
I'll just download into a new...
Oh, right.
If I die, I die.
Speaking of which...
You're right. You're right.
You're right.
That's what you get
for calling tech support.
I can't run anymore.
I'll have to skip.
Just a few more feet.
We have to get to that
pile of dead bears by 7:38.
A pile of dead bears
can only mean one thing.
But what?
It's the 7:38!
Jump!
Ah, shoot!
Someone said shoot.
Well, we're boned.
No, we're not!
We just got to limbo.
But I'm not designed
to bend that low.
Not without limbo music.
That'll do it!
Ow! Ow! Ow, ow! Ooh.
We're gonna get fired.
Someone said fire.
We did it!
12 straight hours of limbo.
I haven't done that
since my honeymoon.
Hermes, Hermes, remember
that flock of bats?
I sure do.
That was fun.
Where are we?
I have no idea.
Hey, we're just a stone's throw
from Tijuana.
See?
Dios mio!
A rock has fallen here
in the outskirts of Tijuana.
Is it within the city limit?
I think, yes.
Told you.
Hey, you want
to celebrate our escape?
Maybe grab a shot of Tequila and
take in a big-league cockfight?
Sure. No, wait.
I was built in Tijuana.
Maybe Inspector Five still works there.
He better do some 'splainin'
before I mash up
some face guacamole.
He's Mexican, I'm Mexican.
Let me handle this.
Sus papeles, por favor
Sí.
Ouch-o!
Here are our passports, visas,
and Homeland Security
permission slips.
Notarized and starched.
Okay.
I also would have accepted a bribe.
Nice work, butterball.
You know, I was in Italy last week.
My birthplace. It's closed!
There's not even a shrine to me
with a gift shop,
selling piñatas of me!
End of the line, mon.
Come on, we can still catch a
twi-night double-cockfight.
No, wait!
What's that in the Mexican garbage?
Looks like a half-eaten
cheese diaper.
No, next to that.
A half-eaten employee directory.
Inspector Five's home address!
His ass-ias is gracias!
Where are you hiding, you coward?!
Get out here
and get murdered like a man!
Bender, I'm afraid
our search is at an end.
He's obviously long gone.
Oh, yeah?!
Well, maybe this is him
in a costume!
I'm gonna squeeze you out of
there like Tijuana toothpaste!
Whoa!
Okay, Bender, you're mortal.
And okay, Inspector Five screwed up.
But that just makes the time you
have left all the more precious.
Do you really to waste
the rest of your life
in a bitter, homicidal rage?
No!
Yes!
I don't know!
Why? Why did he do this to me?!
All I wanted was a little quality control.
But he didn't care enough,
and now I'm gonna die!
I deserved better!
I'm Bender, damn it!
I'm Bender!
There, there, mon.
It's gonna be okay.
You are Bender,
which is something
Inspector Five will never be.
You know what?
You're right.
He was just a stupid bureaucrat.
A stupid, paper-pushing bureaucrat.
A stupid I-dotting, chair-squashing...
Oh.
No offense, Hermes.
You're not like that.
I mean, you're exactly like that,
but you're okay.
In fact, I'm putting you
on the do-not-kill list.
Come on, fellow mortal.
We're in Tijuana.
I want to live a little.
Help!
I'm gonna die!
That's the opposite of what I want!
Quick, run out the back!
I'll hack into Inspector Five's terminal
and fake your death,
so they'll call off the kill-bots.
You know that terminal is unhackable!
I'm not leaving you, and that's final!
Good luck, buddy.
Bender terminated.
Bender's saved.
Cease fire.
Mom called off the attack,
although I don't see how it's her.
Someone said Howitzer!
Yay!
All right! Yay!
Oh...
He did it!
And he's not looking back
at that cool explosion.
He's a hero!
What's happening?!
The phone's been disconnected,
the ship's repossessed
and Zoidberg's getting overcooked!
Aw, aw, aw, aw!
Ah, this place never changes.
Leela, what in the name
of Jah happened?!
Too much papers!
Not enough hiding plants!
It's all right.
This place just needs
a one-hour bureaucratizing.
You make it look so easy.
I've smoked a lot
a paperwork in my day.
Hey, Bender, did you ever find
that inspector guy you were looking for?
Nah. But thanks
to this knucklehead,
I did find a new outlook on life.
It's precious and sacred,
and you only get so many
millions of years on this Earth.
So let's get brick-faced!
Sync by n17t01, corrected by gloriabg
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net