Sync by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
We now go live to
our eye-in-the-sky hovercopter
on the scene of that terrible
hovercopter crash.
Jim?
The news is not good.
I've just learned that my final
words were "Back to you, Linda."
One for the blooper reel.
Oh, the news
is so violent.
Let's watch
Rachael Ray instead.
Oh, no, wait,
there might be chopping.
God, what a wuss.
Stop being
such a spineless jellyfish.
You know full well
I am more closely related
to the sea cucumber.
Not where it counts.
I hated Jim!
In other news, o our city's
filthy, urine-soaked walls
have been desecrated
by a mysterious tile-work
graffiti artist.
Police have no leads as to who's
behind this innovative scourge
of public art.
That is one sexy
bridge abutment.
Free corn?
Well, that'll suit me just fine.
The key is knowing
precisely where to strike.
Oops.
Well, well.
Time to beat him his rights.
Aah, oh, okay!
You know, that don't look
half bad on your buttocks.
It does sort of
class up the place.
The time is 4:00 A.M.!
We've been arguing
all night, Kif.
Can't we go to bed?
Is that all you
ever think about?
I'm not just some
piece of tofu, Amy.
I need to know where we
stand in our relationship.
We're just going
through a rough patch.
It is not a patch.
It's been ages, according to
your wildly inappropriate
hunk-of-the-
month calendar.
Leave Todd out of this.
Thanks, babe.
Also, today is
Canadian Independence Day.
Oop, that's Bender's ringtone.
I recognize the smell.
Hello.
Yo, Amy,
I'm in the slammer.
Oh, no.
That's enough lip
out of you, moneybags.
Just get five grand
and bail me out.
I don't have that kind of money
laying around.
Yeah, you do.
You know that floor safe
where you keep ten grand?
There's five grand in there.
Don't make me wait.
Hey, Bender,
you ever kill a
man with a sock?
It ain't so hard.
I'd better carve a shiv
for protection.
Rodriguez.
These two brothers
bailed your ass out.
Oh, thank God.
Tell me, have things
changed on the outside?
Is food finally
in pill form?
What about pills?
Are they in food form?
Hey, hot stuff, I'm Larry
the murder burglar.
Hi, Larry,
I like your tattoos.
Amy, that man
is a criminal.
I'm just checking out his tats.
Sneato.
I have one of my mom.
Want to see?
Sure.
I just don't get why
you have to flirt with
every bad boy in sight.
Quit exaggerating.
Nobody move or sweet
cheeks here gets it.
Ooh, you're bad.
Mama said
Spock you out.
That's it, Amy.
Pardon my language,
but I have had it
with you ruffling my petticoats.
You and I are through.
Aw, here's a little song
I wrote to cheer you up.
It's called "Let's
Go Already."
CHEWBACCA'S FEET
IRON MAN'S UNDERPANTS
ELVI'S PELVIS
CALCULONS AGENT
single,
lonely, and fabulous.
Thanks, everybody.
Looks like I'm back
in the game.
Yeah, the game
of old maid.
Excuse me, sir,
are those yours?
You're damn right,
and before you ask,
this is mine, too.
Where
am I?
Is this
TBS?
Tough break, Amy.
Are you and Kif
getting divorced?
No, technically
we were Fon-Fon-Rus,
so we weren't really married.
Wow, the interesting thing
about that is...
So, Amy, how can I phrase
this delicately?
Why did Kif dump you like a sack
of yesterday's turds?
He says I have a thing
for bad boys.
It's so stupid.
The truth is
often stupid.
Bender, why do you have
to be so mean to me?
Shut up, baby,
you love it.
Don't tell me to shut up.
You know what happened
to the last guy who
told me to shut up?
What?
That was great.
Shut up.
Oh, yeah,
come over here.
Remember, love between a
human and a robot is taboo.
We can't tell anyone,
not even our coworkers.
Got it. I'll show
the utmost discretion
as we get nasty
in this glass tube.
Ooh, yeah.
I think I'm coming down
with circus-itis.
I thought circus-itis
only affected children.
Children of all ages.
Bender, old friend,
what's on your face?
Uh... blood.
Uh, you know...
shaving of the face beard.
Amy, are those gear imprints
on your sweatpants?
Uh, maybe.
So what?
Well, I only brought it up
'cause Bender's wearing them.
Uh, I stole 'em from her.
Yeah, that's it,
call the cops.
Oh, my swollen feet.
I'd better take my pills.
Amy, I reckon sweet talk
don't come natural to me,
but of everyone
I've ever dated,
you are probably
in the top ten.
Aw, you always say
just the wrong thing
in just the right way.
Sinners!
Robosexuality is an abomination!
Oy, this guy.
The good book sayeth
a robot shall not lie down
with a human,
nor do it standing up,
nor at any angle in between.
Hey, he's right.
I don't like this.
...in the good book.
Look, a single mother!
Let's get her!
Quickly, into
the ship's basement!
Now then,
as you all know,
the county fair
is approaching once again,
so I'm preparing my entry
of pickled winds and weathers.
I've got sunny, snow flurries,
hail with onions,
even my grandmother's
cranberry-raisin typhoon,
but no tornado.
I'll be damned if I let
Mrs. Girdleson take
the blue ribbon again.
That's why I need you folks
to get out there
and harvest a nice ripe one.
This cattle prod
should help.
How will that...?
Aah!
Get out there!
Is everybody
in position?!
What?!
Is someone talking?!
Okay, good!
On three!
One!
What did she say?!
Two!
Wait, I'm not in position!
Three!
I'm ready for the countdown!
I'm not hearing anyone!
Abort mission!
She said go!
Good work, everyone.
Honestly, that went
better than I expected.
I just need
to reduce it
down into this pickle jar,
toss in a bay leaf to impress
those stupid judges...
Hey, where's
Amy and Bender?
They're missing out
on some hot pickle action.
Sounds like a muskrat's
caught in there.
That's Amy's
sweatshirt.
And that's Bender's hat
from the Playah's Ball!
Sweet tornado of Barbado.
Amy and Bender
have been torn to shreds.
Oh, the humanity.
Also Bender.
Wha...?
Wha...
Guh-oh.
What's going on here?!
Uh... nothing.
A pair of deviant robosexuals?!
Not under my roof.
What about
on the roof?
Get your mind out of the gutter.
What about in
the gutter?
Professor, there's nothing
wrong with robosexuality.
Yeah, when the lights go out,
it's nobody's business
what goes on between
two consenting adults.
Or one.
Thanks, guys.
Everything will be okay as long
as my parents don't find out.
Zai jian.
Mom. Dad?!
Come home, Amy.
It your decision.
We can't make you.
Attagirl.
Uh-oh,
not the innocent whistling.
Repent!
Oy, this guy.
WONG RANCH
NO BROKEBACKING
Look, we're your family,
and if you can't talk
about your problem with us,
that would be great.
I don't have a problem!
I'm in a happy relationship
that just happens
to be robosex...
You finish that word,
you kill your parents!
Low wine level
detected.
Thank you.
Stop seducing him,
you hussy!
Dad, gleesh!
I'm attracted to Bender,
not this emotionless
wine bucket!
♪ ♪
Hopes... deleted.
Robotic brothers,
the path to robot hell
is paved with human flesh!
Neat!
Over the course
of this escape-proof workshop
your software will be
reprogrammed through prayer.
And by some tech-support
guys in India.
But I read in Esquire magazine
that some robots
are hard-wired to be robosexual.
Don't believe
those lies, son!
The only lies worth believing
are the ones in the Bible.
Can I get a Amen?
I'll take-a three men. Holla!
Come on, Amy.
Pick a male human already.
I want to be a grandmother
nine months from
five minutes from now.
Cut it out, Mom!
I'm not interested in any
of these gross, ugly losers!
What about this
gross, ugly, smelly loser?
Fry! What you doing here?
I'm here to
rescue Amy...
uh, from her robosexual desire.
If I understand you correctly,
I've seen the error of my ways?
Look at all that
awkward winking?
It must be love!
My parents may be evil,
but at least
they're stupid.
In this phase,
you will literally wrestle
with your demons.
Your shapely, buxom,
human demons.
Look at the rack
on that one!
I mean...
that one on the rack!
Good!
That's very good.
Okay, everybody switch demons.
No point in staying
with just one demon.
Now, work it hard!
Harder! Till the sin
explodes outcha!
Mmm... mercy.
Okay, the Lord's work is done.
Now, now, cuddle,
cuddle with your demons.
Oh, Amy, I wonder where
you are right now.
I'm inside the dummy
to rescue you!
Well, that
answers that.
Wait, wha...? Amy?!
- Ow, ow, ow, ow!
- Aah!
Bender,
be careful!
Fry? Leela?
You're in there, too?!
Blech!
I guess we should
have waited in the ship.
Aw, phooey!
Listen up,
everybody,
I love Amy, and I'm tired of
pussyfootcupping around.
I finally found someone
I want to spend the rest
of her life with.
Amy...
Will you marry me?
Yes! Yes!
Oh, I'm just glad
I didn't live to
see this day.
Hey, wait a second.
Noooo...!
So, it's a stone.
Is it real?
Hooray!
Hooray denied!
Need I remind you that
robosexual marriage is illegal?
Not in Space Massachusetts.
You mean Space-
Tax-achusetts?
No chance,
stretch pants!
We're gonna fight to
legalize it right here!
Yah, Mon!
You got to legalize it!
We're talking about
robosexual marriage.
We're talking
about lots of stuff.
Cool. Can you turn
into a race car?
Nah, I'm just
a pre-op transformer.
Thank you for coming, everyone.
We're all having
some good, clean fun here.
Squeaky, squishy clean.
But it's time to discuss
a pressing issue--
the right to marry
who or what we want!
Legalize it!
Every other couple has
the right to marry.
Robot and fembot,
man and woman,
man and man.
Our poodle has two daddies!
Interracial,
interplanetary,
even ghost and horse,
but not robot and human!
Ooh...
That's why we're introducing
this ballot initiative
to legalize robosexual marriage!
If you hate intolerance and
being punched in the face by me,
please support
Proposition Infinity!
♪ ♪
As election day nears,
Prop Infinity appears doomed
to certain defeat.
Doomed...!
More fair and balanced coverage
after a word from our sponsor,
No on Infinity,
A storm is gathering.
A storm of robosexual marriage
that will rain down
on us like fire.
It's probably a firestorm.
If robosexual marriage
becomes legal,
imagine the horrible things that
will happen to our children,
then imagine
we said those things,
since we couldn't think of any.
As a mother,
those things worry me.
Vote no on Infinity.
Paid for by
the Farnsworth Foundation.
We can't compete against that
much stock footage of clouds!
We're boned!
Ah, but we still
have one hope--
my big televised debate!
I'm our A in the hole!
Professor, who's debating
for your side?
Oh, that guy, um...
you know, I...
I forget his name.
That's him!
Good evening. I'm
George Takei's head and neck,
your host for tonight's debate.
You may applaud.
We flipped a coin
before the debate,
and Bender stole it,
so we'll start with it.
Ladies and gentlemen
of the jury, I...
Oops. Sorry, heh--
force of habit.
♪ ♪
I support this proposition
because I love a goopy,
flesh-and-blood woman,
and, not surprisingly,
she loves me.
This is a simple matter
of justice, which
I'm not normally for.
So please, vote yes.
After all, our love
isn't any different from yours--
except it's hotter,
'cause I'm involved.
I haven't heard
such an eloquent speech
since Bill Shatner explained
why he couldn't pay me back.
Rebuttal, Professor?
This four-dollar coffeepot
talks about love,
but what he describes
is perversion!
You wouldn't
know perversion
if it put clamps
on your testicles!
You're just jealous,
'cause you've never
known true love.
Oh, no? Back when I was
full of piss and vinegar,
and my bed wasn't,
I feel in love
with the sweetest girl
ever to skip through
a field of posie.
Her name was Eunice,
and we spent out blissful days
working in a lab,
developing a poison to wipe out
that dreadful
posie infestation.
I thought our love
would last forever.
But then,
43 years later, she left me...
for a robot!
How could she do that
to me, her Farnypoo!
That's it?
You hate robosexuals
'cause your girlfriend
left you for a robot?!
She didn't just leave me
for a robot,
she was a robot!
Oh, God, her name wasn't Eunice,
it was Unit!
Unit 47!
My heart was broken,
and like a bitter old
picklepuss, I took it out
on robosexuals everywhere.
I'm so ashamed!
At the risk of
losing this debate,
I beg you, support
Proposition Infinity!
Give me a hug!
I, too, am hugging them
in spirit.
And now they're hugging me back.
Oh, my.
♪ ♪
In a stunning turnabout,
voters have approved
Proposition Infinity.
Robosexual marriage
is now legal.
What's next, gay
robosexual marriage?
We did it, honey!
Finally, we can have
a legal, monogamous marriage,
like everyone else!
Whoo-hoo! Yeah...
Monogamous?
And now, a long-distance
dedication
from a squishy green bad boy
to his pink pork dumpling--
at number 12,
it's Wailing Fungus
with... "Shut Up and Love me."
Sync by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net