On the count of three, you will awaken
feeling refreshed, as if
Futurama had never been cancelled by idiots,
then brought back by bigger idiots.
One
Two
Professor, my Fry-fro is all frizzy.
Okay.
-Well, that's all.
Oh also, I'm covered with severe burns.
So? What of it?
Well.. Why is... those things?
You mean you don't remember?
Nope. Nothing. It's like I passed out in college,
except no one drew magic-marker penises on my forehead.
Well, I suppose it's for the best.
Considering the unbearable horrors you've endured.
Let's never speak of it again.
It all began a few days ago.
We were interstellar fugitives
on the run from the law.
Fire all weapons and open a hailing
frequency for my victory yodle.
And so, as you and Leela kissed goodbye
in a tender display of tonguesmanship,
We plunged into a massive wormhole.
Never to be seen again.
Yeah, we're back.
Sweet coincidence of port-au-prince,
we're back at earth!
Of course!
That was the Panama wormhole!
Earth's central channel for shipping!
How humorous.
-Yes, it's sort of a comedy central channel.
And we're on it now!
I get it!
We've lost power to the forward gameboy.
Mario not responding!
Brace for emergency landing.
Roger that. Activate safety-spheres!
Also mine has airconditioning.
Yet thanks to my trusty safety-sphere,
I sublibed with only trivial braindabglid.
And the others?
-Right here behind this horrorcloth.
Are they dead?
-No, no, no, no. Much worse.
Subbed by: Daealis
Move over god!
Prepare for rebirth.
Wrong switch.
Come on stem cells, work your
astounding scientific nonsense.
Fetal stem cells? Aren't those controversial?
In your time yes, but nowadays
SHUT UP.
Besides, these are adult stem cells,
harvested from perfectly healthy adults
Whom I killed for their stem cells.
Hermes Conrad!
O' man, I'm dripping with placenta.
Good thing it's casual friday.
Amy Wong!
Ooh, baby soft!
-Indeed.
Dr. Zoidberg!
Hermes, my friend! Let me cut off your
umbilical cord.
And the rest!
Hooray! We're back in bussiness.
Over my dead body.
Eh, nevermind.
Bender, are the stem cells working?
I'm dying. I need mouth-to-ass resuscitation.
-I'm on it!
It's not working!
I die happy knowing you fell for that.
His power supply is shut. He's flatlining!
Only one thing can keep him alive.
Possibly this thing.
Whoo! I've never felt so energetic.
That's because the doomsday device I showed
all up in you puts out 15 gigawatts.
That's ten times your recommended...
-Who are you, my warranty?
For god sakes Bender, keep dancing!
Keep whooping it up!
You must burn off the doomsday energy
as fast as it's produced,
or it will build to critical levels!
You don't mean
-Oh but I do.
If you stop partying for a single second,
you'll explode and kill everyone here
in a fireball melted gears
and splattered bones!
Sounds like a party, baby! Oh yeah!
Hey speaking of splattered bowels,
can I cook you a romantic dinner tonight, Leela?
Where's Leela?
Is she ok? Why hasn't she
acknowledged my dinner offer?
Something's wrong! She's not
responding to my poking stick!
Poke harder, dammit!
-I'm poking as hard as I can!
I'm sorry Fry, but I'm afraid Leela
is in an irreversible coma.
My soulmate is gone. Why should I go on living?
Because the pain slowly fades,
but the love is forever.
But what if I forget the
sweet sound of her voice,
or the moist touch
of her eyeball on my lips?
Are you still hung-up on whatshername?
Move on already!
Maybe you're right.
-Maybe I'm always right.
Build-a-bot workshop.
It's time to start living again.
At least it's something to
distract me from Leela.
Nah
Now that I like for some reason.
I like jelly beans. Do you?
-I sure do honey.
Come now Fry, you can't
live out this sick fantasy.
Not without our help.
These security tapes record
everything at Planet Express.
Including the ship, shower and urinals.
At yet it still hasn't stop
the illusive bathroom burglar.
Maybe he's just trying
to feed his family
Computer, analyze tapes and and extract
personality profile of one Turanga Leela.
Analyzing..Analyzing.. Checking my E-Bay bid..
Dammit.
Analysis complete.
Hey, I was nuzling that.
Attributes transferred. Shoesize 12. Etc.
Brace for an emergency landing!
What? We survived the crash?
Oh Fry!
Party people in the house say...
This is wonderful. The last thing
I remember I was dying in an explosion.
Yet here I am in the flesh,
more alive than ever.
Alive?
You better tell her, Fry.
-Tell me what?
Anyway, my work is done.
I'm gonna hit the showers.
Nibbler. Come give mama a hug.
What the.. Bad Nibbler, bad Nibbler!
What're you doing, pooperdoodle?
It's me, Leela!
Am I really just a robot?
I mean, I have Leela's memories,
her opinion of gazelles - majestic.
her emotions - confused and hurt.
I swear, I didn't know this would happen.
The only thing I truly know is
I love you.
I mean her.
Wait, help me out here.
Do the Bender, do the Bender.
No thank you.
-I said do it!
The truth is Fry, I still have feelings for you.
but are they really my feelings?
Am I just an automaton, or can a machine have
sufficient complexity, legitimately achieve consciousness?
I agree
I need some time to figure this out.
Until then, friends?
Okay.
Listen up disco-dummies!
You just flunked out of Bender's college of
party knowledge.
Do the backdance, do the backdance.
Good news, everyone.
I'm going to make one final attempt
to awaken Leela.
After all, there's always hope.
Really?
-No, don't get your hopes up.
Frankly, she's just a brainless mound of
scabs and puss.
I didn't need to hear that.
No and you don't need to see this.
Wake up, wake up, wake up...
Well, that's it. I'm afraid
traditional medicine has failed.
No! I refuse to give up!
Wake up Leela!
I... LOVE... YOU!
Fry stop.
She's gone.
Dr. Zoidberg, can you note the time
and declare the patient legally dead?
Can I? That's my speciality!
As you all know, Leela's living will states
that in the event of coma,
her body is to be fed to the wild
cyclophage, a highly endangered creature
that eats only cyclopses.
Yup, that's what her donor-card says.
Goodbye my love.
The beast approacheth.
Bender cut it out. People are
trying to have emotions.
You think I wanna party?
I'm sick of partying.
Wohoo! More partying!
Bender! Shut the hell up!
Bender! Stop shutting the hell up!
Oh, right.
Leela's back, as if I care. Woo.
Alright, Leela!
Thanks. It's so nice to wake up and see..
Leela!?
-Leela?
Leela?
-Leela.
How is this possible? And can you believe
she wore a tanktop to my funeral?
Shut up! We got to get out of here!
No, YOU shut up we got to get out of here.
All aboard the party-ship!
There's no room for two
captain's butt's in this chair.
-There would be if you'd taken a spin class
instead of just lounging around in a coma!
This is crazy. It's like I'm looking
at an exact robot duplicate of myself.
That is what you're looking at.
Oh. How could you do this Fry?
Uh.. Coma.. Sad..
I have to go. This is just too freaky.
Please don't get upset, Leela.
She's nothing like you.
I have to go. This is just too freaky.
I need chearing up Bender.
I don't know, you want to
go out and party tonight?
I hate partying! If only I didn't have
so much cronk in my donkydonk.
Why does everything I date run away?
I love Leela, always and forever,
and if I loved robot-Leela too,
that's only because she had
so much of the real Leela in her
I thought she loved me too,
but obviously I was wrong as usual.
Wrong again.
You were right.
Leela? Leela-Leela?
Leela-Leela.
I've been thinking Fry. If I lost you,
I don't think I could stand it either.
I'd propably build
a copy of you too.
As long as robo-Leela's not
a jealous type like me, things will
I'LL KILL YOU YOU SLUTCLOPS!
He's mine!
Back off, missy!
Somebody do something!
Here, take this!
A gun? Do I really need to..
-Shoot her! She's the robot!
-No! Shoot her! She's the human!
But how do I know who's the human
and who's the robot?
We just told you!
-Yea you idiot!
Ok. Fine. If you're gonna be like that,
I'm not shooting anyone.
Right between the lungs.
Man that was close.
I'm a robot too!
Aha! That explains this growth on your driveshaft!
But how is this possible?
-Who knows.
Oh, I do. Allow me to explain what really
happened the day the ship crashed.
I'll protect you Leela. My love is stronger than
the vast majority of explosions.
Fry did infact save Leela, though
at a terrible cost to himself.
I tossed him into the stem cells, but
he just bubbled away like flem on a hot sidewalk.
Leela was so distraught, she went all
Blade Runner and built a duplicate.
Then uploaded Fry's personality from the
urinal surveillance tapes.
I sure love Leela.
Alas, in recreating Fry's adorable jelly-belly
she had overstuffed him with copperwadding.
The innevitable static discharge electrocuted Leela
And destroyed both of their short-term memories.
So that's why I'm so amazed
by these things I already knew.
What could I do? I hung up Leela
with the other bonebags
and went to procure the final ingredient
for my stem cell brew.
Professor, my Fry-fro's all frizzy.
My god, I can't believe I'll never see
that particular Fry again.
Hey where's my shoes?
Fry?
Oh I'm sorry. I didn't realise
I was already here.
Wait, what's with all the Leelas?
-Trust me, don't ask.
Ok dork. Listen, I'm gonna hit the urinal,
maybe talk about myself a little bit..
Hang on. It's time to sort things out.
The truth is, I love Fry. That Fry.
-And I love Leela. Any Leela.
We're robots and we're in love.
Let's ditch these meatjackets.
Whoa, cool!
Hasta la vista, weener.
We'll be back. For our stuff.
Why did their voices change?
That's the one thing
we'll never truly understand.
Uh, this is a bit awkward. Or is it?
-I'm not sure.
I lost track around the second robot.
Well, you know how I feel.
I waited for you for a thousand years,
I can wait a little longer.
What a load a mush! I've had it.
He's gonna blow!
-Party, Bender. Party for your life!
No chance high-pants!
I'd rather die and kill all of you
than party for one more millisecond!
The cyclops-eater!
Hold on, man! It ain't like that!
Jeesh, what does it take to kill me?
Bender, you blew out your excess capacity!
You're cured!
Sweet mercy! My hellish nightmare is over!
I never have to party again.
Well, that's that then.
We're back everyone!
-PARTAYH!
www.tvsubtitles.net