Sync by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
(applause)
As mayor, it is my deeply
tedious pleasure to kick off
the 83rd or 84th Annual
E-Waste Recycling Festival!
(cheering)
Down in front!
Sorry. I get
aroused in crowds.
I will now throw out
the ceremonial first dump--
this old, inefficient
vote rigger!
(cheering)
These old doomsday devices
are dangerously unstable.
I'll rest easier not
knowing where they are.
(grunts)
(devices thudding,
glass breaking)
So long, overly complicated
Japanese toilet.
TOILET:
Please not to throw away.
I give you happy poopie time.
Sorry, you know
too much.
(toilet crashing,
glass shattering)
(chuckles)
Seems like a good place
to ditch some evidence.
Flexo?!
What are you doing
in a hazardous waste bin?
Haven't you heard?
Us bending units
are dangerously outdated.
We overheat, we're radioactive,
we cause erectile dysfunc...
Who are you talking to?
No one. Your mama.
Shut up.
Take your pick.
(kissing)
(camera shutters
clicking)
Scoop Chang,
New New York Times
online podcast
blog comments editor.
Mr. Mayor,
isn't this e-waste dangerous?
Not at all, Scoop.
Not after it's hauled off
to the Third World
by an expendable team
of minimum-wbge nobodies.
(whispering):
Good news, nobodies!
(clanking)
Greetings,
my friends!
It shan't take long
to strip down
your clunker.
(clanging)
There's nothing wrong
with our clunker.
Really? Because we can smelt out
the deadly, deadly chromium
to make rat poison
and artificial sweeteners.
No, thanks.
We're delivering e-waste.
Pity. We're
halfway done.
(blowtorch hissing)
This thing is
40% chromium!
(bird squawking)
(crunch, hissing)
Gentle now.
Gentle with
the hoverdumpster.
Ready for processing!
(sniffing)
What smells like bloody sinuses?
We burn your e-waste down
to the usable metals,
safely releasing the
toxins into our air
and drinking water.
(panting)
Ugh! That's the worst thing
I've ever seen!
Really? Then don't
look over there.
(laughter)
Okay, kids.
Let's play find
the shiny!
(laughter)
(coughing)
That's even
more horrific!
Is all the
work done
by children?
No, not the whipping.
(whip cracking)
Granted, we later learned some
positive things about recycling,
but a better solution is
to use our electronics
as long as possible
instead of throwing them out
in the first place.
I'm gonna start
by keeping my old cell phone,
even if it is outdated.
OLD-TIME PHONE OPERATOR:
Hello, Miss Turanga.
Your call
to Saint Louis has gone through.
Well, let's at least
throw this TV out.
The batteries
in the remote are getting low.
No! Put that back
and turn it on!
I was just trying to help.
More on this breaking puff-piece
after a word from our sponsor.
(quiet piano music plays)
MALE ANNOUNCER:
With the new eyePhone,
you can watch, listen,
ignore your friends,
stalk your ex, download porno
on a crowded bus,
even check your e-mail
while getting hit by a train.
All with the new eyePhone.
WOMAN:
From Mom.
A new eyePhone?!
Forget this junk.
WOMAN (over phone):
Well, this is a fine
how-do-you-do!
So long!
Sayonara!
Bye-bye!
Good riddance!
Yup!
Toodle-oo!
Come on, let's buy
some eyePhones online.
(grunts)
Wait. I thought we were buying
our eyePhones online.
We are on line.
But I thought
the Mom Store
was across town.
It is
across town.
But I thought...
Stop
thinking, Fry!
(line moves slowly in lockstep)
I feel like
a mindless zombie.
I wish I knew
how long we've been waiting.
The eyePhone has an app
for that!
Is there an app
for kissing my shiny metal ass?
Several!
Ooh!
(line continues moving slowly
in lockstep)
Oh, no, the light!
I guess I'm off to hell.
That's the
store, Professor.
Whuh?
♪ Ooh, ooh-ooh, ooh,
ooh-ooh, ooh ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh-ooh, ooh ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh... ♪
Amy:
Swow! It's that obscure
underground song
that's constantly
playing everywhere.
Hello, dearies.
Welcome to the Mom Store.
The new eyePhones
are in short supply,
so please form an orderly...
Out of the way!
I need...
(crowd clamoring)
(panting):
Are there any left?!
There may be one.
Okay, it's $500, you have
no choice of carrier,
the battery can't
hold a charge,
and the reception
isn't very...
Shut up and take my money!
The new eyePhone is wonderful.
I use it to check recipes
and send threatening e-mails
to unauthorized
third-party app developers...
Say, you're from one
of those ethnicities
that knows
about technology.
Why is it called
an eyePhone?
I'll explain after
I install it.
(screaming)
Neat.
(computer trilling, beep)
Now for the
ear piece.
But my favorite app
is called Twitcher.
(hammer blow)
FRY: Ow!
Twitcher lets you send
and receive short messages
or videos called twits.
Why, here's a twit now.
Hi, Mom. I love you
more than can...
MALE VOICE:
Low battery.
But don't takey word for it.
Unbiased-Reviews-dot-Mom says
Twitcher is the killer app.
And when I say killer app,
I mean killer app!
(evil cackling)
(evil laughter)
(groaning)
Ow!
WEBISODE ANNOUNCER:
And now another downloadisode
of The Real Housewives
Of SIM City.
(repeated thudding against wall)
She needs to reset.
I'll say it
to her face.
No wonder traditional
media is dead.
Check out this webisode
of Hypnotoad.
(mechanical humming)
Enjoy your outdated
format, Grandpa.
Nowadays, cool kids like me
mash up our own phone-isodes.
It's from the
kidnappers.
My nephew is alive!
And he's... in
this envelope.
They cut off one
of my dimensions!
No! No!
(sobbing)
Oh, my God, it's Bender!
He'll save us!
(phone ringing)
What's happening to me?
Is it puberty?
It's a phone call, dingus.
These eyePhones are phones, too?
Duh.
Fry-lo.
LEELA: Hi, Fry.
Did you know
these eyePhones are phones, too?
Duh. Hey, is it safe
to talk while you're flying?
Oh, totally.
This thing's hands-free.
That's how I can eat this taco.
And this spaghetti.
Ow!
I'm hanging up now.
Hey, check out
this Internet video
of some idiot
crashing her spaceship!
Ow!
You recorded that?
The eyePhone records everything.
All I did was add a laugh track
and twit it
to my 10,000 followers.
Ow!
(laugh track plays)
Oh, that reminds me.
It's time to my hourly twupdate.
(beeping)
'Sup, followers.
Fry here. (belches)
Burping eggs,
scratching my underarm fungus,
looking for love.
Send.
Underarm
fungus?
Ugh! Too much information.
Ow!
It's exactly the right
amount of information!
For years,
I've collected personao data
with old-fashioned methods,
like spybots and info-squitos.
This guy sure
loves porno.
But now,
thanks to Twitcher,
morons voluntarily spew out
every fact I need
to exploit them!
(crosshairs beeping)
Target acquired, Mother.
Fire direct marketing algorithm!
(whooshing)
(computer chimes)
Do you suffer
from the heartbreak of...
FRY:
My underarm fungus.
Then you, Mr. or Mrs....
(Fry burping)
...need the soothing relief
of Mom's Caustic
Anti-Fungal Bleach!
Oh. Can I somehow charge it
to my eyePhone
for an additional fee?
Hell, yes!
(computer chirps)
Hey, fatso, stuffa you face!
(gasps)
This thing always seems
to know when I got the munchies!
(clicking)
Attention followers.
It's free topping day
at the pizza place
across the street! Send.
(computers chime)
Duh. That's why we all came
over here for lunch. Send.
(computers chime)
Greetings followers.
This is day five
of my solo kayak journey
around the world. Send.
(laughing)
Can you believe 50,000 idiots
swallow that crap? Send.
Oops.
FRY:
Wait.
You have 50,000 followers?
I only have three. Send.
(computers chirp)
I unsubscribed yesterday.
I got the most
followers 'cause
I give the people
what they want.
Like this video of you doing
karate in your underpants.
(goofy karatf yells)
Ow! Help! Police!
Send.
That is low, Bender,
even by your standards.
My what now?
Since when is the Internet
about robbing people
of their privacy?
August 6, 1991.
I'll bet I can get
as many followers as you
without sinking to your level.
What do you say? First one to
a million followers wins a buck.
You're on!
(zapping)
Ow!
Send.
What happens to the loser?
Let's make it interesting.
Shplecch.
Why is Mr. Chunks
doing that?
Because the loser of our bet
has to do a double somersault
into a tub
of alien goat vomit.
(chuckles)
Wait, let's make it
interestinger.
Vomit and diarrhea.
Good idea.
That way we don't waste an end.
Ugh, it's putrid.
What do you feed him?
What comes out one end,
we feed to the other.
Also Indian food.
(vomiting)
Let the contest begin!
(howling scream)
♪ ♪
(bell dings)
Amazing.
Some dumb bastard has nearly
a million other dumb bastards
following his every twit!
Are you dumb bastards
listening to me,
you dumb bastards?
Why are you so
angry, Mommy?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I guess I'm just a little
nervous about my evil plan.
You dumb bastards!
(all groan)
You see,
the plan is about
to enter phase two.
As soon as someone reaches
a million followers,
I'll use them to transmit...
the twit-worm.
Oh, Mother,
you devious hag.
Tell us more
about this "twit-worm."
It's a very special
computer virus,
for instead of
infecting computers,
it infects the human brain.
I like it.
The million followers will
become an army of zombies,
eager to obey my
every command.
(cackling laugh)
The important thing is,
we're a family.
No, it's not!
(yells)
(stops vomiting)
(sneezes,
resumes vomiting)
Ew, he sneezed
in it.
Oh, God, I'm going
to lose the bet.
I'm gonna have to swim in the
juice of the Puke-Me-Poop-You.
Don't give up.
You just need
more titillating twits.
Trust me, I want
twits that tittle.
Then you're going to have
to sink to Bender's level.
Stop acting
like the queen of England.
FEMALE VOICE:
♪ La, la, la, la, la, la, la. ♪
Who was that--
the queen of England?
Uh, e-excuse me.
I have to... someplace.
That was odd.
Where'd that singing
come from?
It wasn't the goat.
All of its orifices
are in use.
FEMALE VOICE:
♪ I dreamed a dream in time ♪
♪ Gone by ♪
LEELA AND FEMALE VOICE:
♪ When hope was high ♪
♪ And life worth living ♪
♪ I dreamed that love
would never die ♪
FEMALE VOICE:
♪ I dreamed that God ♪
♪ Would be forgiving. ♪
(screams)
What the hell
is that?
Nothing.
LEELA'S BOIL:
I'm not nothing.
(sobbing):
All my life everyone's
called me nothing.
You have a boil
on your butt
that sings show tunes
with you?
Don't look at me.
I'm a freak.
No, no-- well...
Oh, I've been ashamed of Susan
as long as I can remember.
You named your boil
Susan?
A boil Kinna have a name?
They also said a boil
Kinna sing, but...
♪ Amazing grace ♪
♪ How... ♪
Aah!
(groans)
Ew, she's Scottish.
I Lance r every few months,
but she always grows back.
It's hard enough
being a Cyclops,
but if anyone found out
about Susan, I'd be devastated.
♪ Amazing grace ♪
♪ How... ♪
Aah!
Whoa, gross.
Million-follower gross.
Fry, delete that.
Delete that
right now!
What?
Oh, okay.
(Bender humming)
(chuckles)
So much for a pleasant swim
in vomit.
(coughing)
Send.
Did you delete it?
Eh.
Thanks, Fry, you're
a good friend.
Eh...
♪ Amazing grace ♪
♪ How... ♪
Aah!
(both laughing)
Hey, there she goes
in the genuine.
Let's get
to hooting.
Hoo!
Whoa-oa-OAS!
If it ain'ts the world's
number ones Internet sensation!
Where?
Also... what?
♪ Amazing grace... ♪
(gasps)
♪ How... ♪
Aah!
(all laughing)
Play it one more time.
No, it's humiliating
and degrading to Leela.
Play it ten more times.
(sighs) I know
I shouldn't have twitted that,
but not swimming in barf
might ease my conscience.
But if Leela should find out,
her dignity sac will rupture.
That's why
we can't let her see this.
Leela, lock the door
so Leela doesn't...
(squeals)
(sobbing):
How could you do this?
♪ ♪
(fly buzzing)
Poor Mr. Chunks.
At least he died
doing what he loved.
He's in a better place now.
Thar, I turned a regular board
into a diving board.
Mm-hmm.
Impending news, everyone.
We're about to learn
the winner of the bet.
Oh, boy, oh, boy, oh, boy.
(whispering):
I hope it's me.
Wait a minute.
There's a chance I could lose?
That wasn't part of the deal.
Sweet Georgia Brown
of Kingston Town.
It's a tie.
Since no one lost,
no one has to jump.
All right, a tie!
I win again!
Oh, I'm a scuzzball.
Don't feel bad.
At least you're not Leela.
A tie?
This worked out better
than I could have hoped.
Now I'll have
two million zombies.
Actually,
Fry and Bender may share
some of same followers.
All we can say for sure
is that there will be
between one million
and two million zombies.
All I can say
for sure is...
Ouch!
Now, stop getting slapped
and power up the twit-worm.
(both laughing)
It's both disgusting
and inspiring,
like Jared from Subway.
Okay, I'm a freak
with a singingutt boil,
but I'm still a human being,
more or less.
Singing butts boil?
That's yesterdayses news.
Like that giant caterpillar
what ate Jared from Subway.
Nows us Internet geeks gots
a whole new video sensation.
So my humiliatiois over?
Who are you?
And now, to create
an unstoppable army
of between one
and two million zombies.
(thunder cracks)
Uh, shouldn't
you wait
for the weather
to clear up?
No.
I give you the twit-worm.
Send.
Aah, I'm sick
of my head doing things.
Leela!
Fry, I came
to talk to you.
No, I came to
talk to you.
It looked like you were just
sitting there, but whatever.
I am so, so sorry
for what I did,
and I know I can never
make it up to you...
You don't have to apologize.
In fact, I came to thank you.
I think you mean hit me.
Everyone knows my secret,
but no one cares.
I have nothing
to hide anymore.
Oh, Fry, thanks
to your selfish rudeness,
a terrible weight has
been lifted from my heart.
Susan:
That's not the only place you
need a terrible weight lifted.
(squishing sound,
Susan screams)
Susan and I
are agreed.
For the first time
in our lives,
we're not ashamed
of who we are.
Susan:
I was never ashamed.
Come here.
(sniffs)
What stinks?
Were you rolling around
in New Jersey?
Leela, I knew I could
never make it up to you,
so I did the
next best thing--
I put myself through the same
humiliation I put you through.
(screams)
(grunts)
(gagging and sputtering)
(screams)
(laughs)
Aw, you didn't have
to do that.
I didn't?
Damn.
Don't worry.
By tomorrow,
no one will remember.
Can I have another hug?
No.
Susan:
Oh, hold your nose
and give it a go.
Introducing the
new eyePhone
Damn bastards.
Sync by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net