1x13 - Homecoming
Previously on Green Lantern...
Atrocitus used those planet killers
to tear a hole right through the Maelstrom.
Big enough for his whole
spite armada to roll into Oan space.
I'm sorry, Hal. I'm now a soldier for
the righteous crusade of Atrocitus.
So that's it.
That's your plan.
Fine. I just got one question.
Are you nuts!?
Ok. This harebrained scheme
makes my other schemes seem
well-thought-out and practical.
But what else can we do?
Nothing. Thanks to us,
the Red Lantern fleet
will have no trouble
pouring into Guardian space.
And we're stuck here while
Atrocitus flies the Interceptor to Oa
and exterminates the Guardians.
My plan won't help us
beat them to Oa, but maybe,
just maybe, we can get to the
same galactic neighborhood.
Let's move out.
Kilowog.
No. Even you can't beat
an entire armada.
I can slow them down,
maybe buy a little time
for that plan of yours.
You'll need every minute.
You got this, sergeant.
Godspeed, Hal.
Coordinates achieved.
Dropping out of ultra warp.
Oa. At last. Now, the day
of vengeance has arrived.
Incoming message from the surface.
Unidentified vessel,
you have breached Oan space.
Identify yourself immediately.
We are discovered. Initiate attack
before they send Green Lanterns!
Belay that order.
Drusa, your puppet.
I repeat, identify or face...
This is Green Lantern craft Interceptor
requesting emergency landing.
Hal Jordan and Kilowog
have been wounded
and require immediate
medical attention.
I also have vital information
regarding the Red Lanterns.
Understood, Interceptor,
and welcome home.
What's going on here?
Where am I?
I... I know her.
It's her. It's...
- Carol. Carol!
- Hal?
Hal!
It is you!
Hal, what are you doing here?
I...
I promised to take you to diner.
In brightest day, in blackest night,
no evil shall escape my sight.
Let those who worship evil's might
beware my power, Green Lantern's light.
Salaak, bear the injured
to the medical dome immediately.
Yes, yes, as soon as I've received this
vital intelligence the A.I. spoke of.
Then, prep the ship to rendezvous
with our corps in sector...
- Hello, Guardians.
- Atrocitus!
Fall back. Fall back!
How is this possible?
What are we to do?
For the moment, nothing, Guardian.
We are in the most fortified spot on Oa,
and even with the corps deployed,
we are not without defenses.
Blast them!
This, perhaps, is not
unlike what the people
of the forgotten zone experienced
at the hands of our Manhunters.
It's hard to believe
it all actually happened.
It was like a dream or something.
One minute, I'm in my office,
and then, bam!
I'm on another planet fighting you.
What?
You look gorgeous, by the way.
Hal, are you all right?
Of course. I'm with you.
Refill?
No, thanks. It's just that
you seem a little...
Look, Carol, all I know is I was
far from you and needed to find you.
And now, we're together.
Everything's going to be ok.
But what happened out there?
Frontier space, the Red armada.
What?
The Red Lantern army.
Were they stopped?
What about your friends out there,
the other Green Lanterns?
What's a Green Lantern?
Ok, Reds.
It may be just a matter of time,
but I'm not making this easy on you.
- Where is it?
- Carol, what's wrong with you?
Why are we back at the base?
You didn't even look
at the dessert menu.
It's got to be here somewhere.
- What's got to be here?
- Your power battery.
You once told me...
well, Green Lantern told me...
That your power ring has to be recharged
by a battery that he keeps close by.
- Green Lantern told you?
- Yes, you as Green Lantern.
Anyway, since you spend more time
at Ferris air than anywhere else,
it must be... here.
What is it?
Where did it come from?
I believe it came in a gift set
with this.
I think they know each other.
- What are you doing?
- Maybe nothing,
but whenever I have trouble
with my desktop,
the I.T. guys reboot the system.
I'm hoping this will reboot
your system.
Hal, try to remember.
Will yourself to remember.
In brightest day, in blackest night,
no evil shall escape my sight.
let those who worship evil's might
beware my power, Green Lantern's light!
I remember.
Had to do the impossible.
Get to Oa before Atrocitus.
I could only think of one way.
Zamaron. Now I see why you
wanted me along as your bodyguard.
Easy, quick draw.
We're not here to fight.
We're here to beg.
Great Aga'po,
I know you think I'm your enemy,
but there's a galaxy-wide
tragedy brewing,
and only the power of the
Star Sapphires can help stop it.
You risk much, Green Lantern,
asking favors of an enemy.
But perhaps I should first
consult my royal advisor.
Ghia'ta.
It was you who opened my eyes
to the true meaning of love,
Hal Jordan.
My enlightenment met
with resistance, at first.
But then, the truth took
root and spread quickly.
It seems that over the ages,
the Star Sapphires may have lost
sight of the emotion we serve.
Since you helped us regain our
path, what do you ask of us?
I need you to teleport me
my home planet.
What you ask for cannot be done.
But I saw you teleport Carol
Ferris here all the way from Earth.
So use my feelings for Carol
to send me to Earth.
From there, I can fly to Oa and
stop a tragedy before it happens.
The jaunt from Earth was the
longest we've ever attempted,
and we've never sent
anyone the other way.
There is something more.
The spatial displacement
can render the traveler...
- ...unstable.
- It is too dangerous.
If he doesn't reach Oa, not only
will the Guardians be destroyed,
but Atrocitus will lay waste
to all the worlds in their care.
Love and everything else will
cease to exist in Guardian space.
I've got to try.
Please.
Make sure this galaxy remains a
safe garden where love can bloom.
- Carol...
- I know.
The galaxy's in danger, and
you stopped for a 4-course meal.
Go already.
But you're still on
the hook for dessert.
Well, if it's my time to clock out,
at least I know
I went down swinging.
Whoa.
Who are you supposed to be?
I am merely the conduit of the
great hope that surrounds us all.
I am St. Walker,
and I believe I am the first
Blue Lantern in the universe.
Thanks for the power boost.
But one extra soldier ain't
exactly going to turn the tide.
I agree.
That's why I brought a friend.
I am honored to help
Green Lantern Kilowog.
Now, that's more like it.
You're leaving us, Razer?
I won't lounge here in
luxury while evil triumphs.
Then go
in the spirit of love.
Love will doubtless be
foremost in my mind
as I hurl myself into the path
of an unstoppable armada.
You are not as far gone
as we had assumed, Razer.
There is still love in your heart.
If you truly wish to help Hal Jordan,
there is another way.
You go, Mogo!
You know, considering
my backup is a couple of rookies,
I'm starting to feel lucky.
Don't put your trust in luck,
friend. She is fickle.
Shoot it, Mogo. Now!
- What are they?
- Liberators.
Planet killers.
Our triumph is at hand.
Only a few feet of Raconian
stands between me
and the vengeance
I have awaited for centuries.
Any final words, Green Lantern?
Yes.
Open dome.
Welcome Green Lantern.
You've arrived just in time to watch
the Guardians pay for their
crimes against the forgotten zone.
Well, as much as I've been looking
forward to the winner-take-all,
no-holds-barred cage match,
I've got something to say...
Something I never thought
I'd hear coming out of my mouth.
You're right.
What the Manhunters did
to your sector was a tragedy.
Your rage is earned.
But destroying life here isn't
going to change what happened there.
Let's work together to find a solution,
a way to make things better for
the people of the forgotten zone.
Let us help.
You can help, Earth man.
Your dying screams will help
soothe the restless souls of our dead!
If you are going to destroy me,
there is a more expedient method.
Destroy you?
I wouldn't dream of it.
I'm just deleting
all of your higher functions
so you'll behave like
a proper NAV computer.
Say good-bye, my puppet.
Razer.
H... how...
It does not matter.
We must find Hal Jordan.
Hey, moon face, that blue ring
of yours is boosting me,
so why ain't it boosting Mogo?
I think I have to be
within a certain proximity
to a green power ring
to amplify its power.
Mogo's is inconveniently located
miles below the surface.
I got an idea.
Let's hope this works.
Well, what do you know!
I've been looking forward to this
for quite some time!
You are no match for me.
You never... had...
a chance!
He cannot fight on.
He has not the strength.
He may not have the strength...
but does he have the will?
Guards! Retreat!
Wait!
Zox, soldiers, all of you!
Listen. Stop this
war before it begins.
I was telling the truth.
The Green Lanterns will help
rebuild your shattered sector.
Do you seriously expect us to
believe that anything will change?
Who here would ever
come to the forgotten zone?
I will come.
What happened to your sector
was a tragedy,
but our willingness to ignore the
tragedy we caused... was a crime.
I pledge to you
the Guardians will make restitution.
You will find me a loud and grating
voice of justice for my sector, Guardian.
Whatever reparations you think
are enough, start by doubling them.
Meet the new boss,
same as the old boss. More or less.
Can the Guardians trust Zilius Zox?
They can trust him to do whatever's in
his best interest, and that's a start.
Razer, how in the world did
you get to Oa as fast as I did?
I...
2814, you have not
yet been debriefed.
That is, we Guardians
have not yet had a chance to...
to thank you, Hal Jordan.
You just did.
But I've got to get back to Earth.
You have just
averted an intergalactic war.
What on Earth could
possibly be more important than that?
Dessert.
www.tvsubtitles.net