1x06 - Lost Planet
Previously on Green Lantern...
Those power rings are
currently in search of new hosts
or en route back to Oa.
Once I found out Dulac was dead,
I knew his ring would go
to the most worthy person.
Now that you're a Green Lantern,
will you join us in our fight
against the Red Lanterns?
All right, you jackwagons,
sound off like you mean it.
- Aya.
- Present.
- Razer.
- Heh.
Jordan. Jordan!
Whoa. Kilowog, there are only
four of us, and we're all here.
We may be a half a universe
away from Oa,
but that doesn't mean we can't
maintain a little discipline.
Discipline's overrated.
And I called this meeting
so we could assess our situation.
Easy. We'll be dead
within a month.
How about we leave the tactical
analysis to sergeant Kilowog.
[sighs]
That's right.
We're in deep umtec splat.
Just when things look
a little hopeful,
we lose our newfound
Green Lantern Iolande,
'cause she won't leave home.
So it's two Green Lanterns fighting
the entire Red Lantern invasion.
Pardon my interruption,
but I've completed my search
for the late Shyir Rev's
power ring.
There is good news
and there is bad news.
Let's have good news.
The ring's signal
emanates from a nearby planet.
Outstanding. Must have found
a replacement G.L.
Could be another recruit for us.
Change course immediately.
I know I'm going to regret
asking, but what's the bad news?
The planet in question will be hit
by that asteroid in 5.2 minutes.
I say we blow that
thing apart before it hits.
Due to the asteroid's
huge mass,
My canons will have no impact,
even at full power.
Maybe we don't need to destroy it.
We just need to slow it down.
Asteroid bearing unchanged.
I cannot maintain this level of output.
What about our personal lanterns?
Can you siphon
an extra boost from them?
Affirmative. Accessing.
It's working!
Power drum at critical level.
- Shut it down.
- No, keep firing!
Field regulations, Jordan.
We don't let our batteries
dip below 20%!
Enough with the regulations!
Keep pouring it on!
[groans]
[cracking]
Main and portable batteries
nearing failure threshold.
Talk to me, Aya.
Did we do it?
Asteroid progress delayed.
We now have six hours until impact.
Yeah, great.
We blew all our power doing it.
Now when we go down there,
our rings will be running on fumes.
No one will mind that our
rings are only partially charged
as we rescue them.
Scanners now at limited capacity,
reading few scattered life forms.
Looks like we have six hours to find
the new Green Lantern
recruit down there
and get him and any others
off the planet in one piece.
Shooting from the hip as
usual. Gonna get us all killed.
Jordan, regulations exist for a reason.
They're not suggestions.
And since we're at war,
we should follow them!
I concur. Putting the lives of two
well-trained Green Lanterns at risk
in an effort to save one
untrained novice, is impractical.
Look, I may not have followed
all the regs to the letter,
but there are people on that
planet who need to be rescued,
not to mention a Green Lantern.
And one Green Lantern
can make all the difference.
So, which way?
A strange seismic interference
is disrupting the scanner's ability
to pinpoint the ring's exact location.
But it is in this vicinity.
Then let's move.
We come in peace.
- I've always wanted to say that.
- Why?
Greetings, travelers.
You are well met on this
desolate rock of a planet.
I am Zartok.
My fellow castaways
are Drusa and Grood.
I'm Hal Jordan.
This is Kilowog, Aya and Razer.
Where did your ship crash?
We didn't crash.
We landed just over that rise.
That, what you're holding,
is a Thalian moon staff.
Only soldiers that fought in the last
stand of Thalius Prime wielded that blade.
I know.
I was in that battle.
We're looking
for a Green Lantern, here.
A search, I want to point out,
that is pathetic and pointless.
Look around you.
There's no Green Lantern here.
Oh, ok, we should just give up.
Or we could look for ourselves.
That asteroid's going to hit
in six hours.
We'll get you to safety
before that happens,
but in the meantime, we could use
some help finding our Green Lantern.
You will have our aid.
We'll split into teams.
We can cover
more ground that way.
I'll go with Zartok.
If you don't mind,
I'd like to go with Aya.
Nice to talk with another...
girl for a change.
Must be losing
my game out here.
I work better alone.
Oh. Well, I guess
it's just you and me, pal.
So, Grood...
I bet you're like
a senator on your planet.
A great orator,
a voice to be heard.
No, no, no, wait,
you're a storyteller
who weaves a magic
tapestry of words,
charming everyone around with
your ingenious turn of phrase.
What is it?
Did you find something?
I-- I don't see anything.
What is it I'm supposed to--
[groaning and grunting]
Hey, hey, get off!
[groaning]
Ok.
That doesn't make any sense.
Hello? Anyone?
Come in!
Maybe this was a really
bad idea after all.
I've been working with
grunts and posers for so long.
It's an honor to be
in the company of a soldier--
A true soldier.
So your leader, Hal Jordan,
disappoints you?
Hal ain't exactly my leader.
In fact, I'm not even sure he's got
the right stuff to lead this war.
But the defenders
of Thalius Prime are legendary.
If it wouldn't be too rude to ask,
I would love to hear of the battle--
the last stand.
It was...
The greatest moment of my life.
A glorious battle.
Never have I seen such bravery,
such soldierly duty.
The cartonian hordes
were terrifying--
murder in the eyes
and thirsting for blood.
A good day to die.
I've been marooned on this
planet for quite some time.
It's so exciting to see you--
A walking, talking
artificial intelligence.
Such technology.
Such perfection.
Perfection is incorrect.
I must continually adjust
a 0,0001% flaw in my programming.
Well, you sure sound
perfect to-- oh, ahh!
[groaning]
Ohh. Stupid.
I twisted it.
I can construct a field dressing
and splint from surrounding materials.
I'd feel better if you took me back
to your ship for medical attention.
Certainly.
[grunting]
[laughter]
Don't turn your back on me!
[birds chirping]
Hold it right there, Grood.
Whoa!
There was much blood.
Many lives lost.
But my battalion
still had fight in 'em.
My personal guards stood
with me in the thick of battle.
The Cardonian horde were
ruthless and relentless.
That Thalian moon staff has probably
seen more action than any of us.
It has earned its place in history.
To be honest, we're here
looking for a ring.
It can be tried to choose one of you to be
a Green Lantern, like us.
Personally, I'm hoping it's you.
Such power would be
a great honor.
This ship is more than my home.
I have never known anything else.
It is correct to state
that I was born on this ship.
- Is this the infirmary?
- That, and numerous other uses.
There is not sufficient space
on the ship,
so each room serves multiple functions.
What's this?
That is the main access panel
to my CPU chamber.
Perfect.
A graveyard of space wrecks.
Rashe pirate ships.
War ships of the Cardonian horde.
Yes. And those are space
clippers of the Tarconian marauders.
Who are you?!
One of the castaways?
Those over there are catty slavers
from Gur. Quite the collection.
All of them seriouy bad people
who have done seriously bad things.
Tell me who you are,
or so help me...
The path they walked
led to their doom.
It is the same path you travel now.
I am Saint Walker.
And you are?
About to kick your smug rear.
That is not a very pleasant name.
Not in the least.
- You got a problem with me?
- Do you have a problem with you?
I only have one problem,
but it's a problem I intend to correct.
[grunts]
Come in.
Can anyone hear me?
How am I going to warn
the others if I can't find them?
Ok...
Well, it's a stretch,
but it's a better lead
than anything else I've got.
And the great battle
of Thalius Prime was over.
What an inspiration.
And what an honor to hear about
it in your words, Zartok.
We would have won if my
battalion hadn't been captured.
You did win! The Cardonian
horde was defeated that day.
Precisely.
Because my battalion
was the Cardonian horde.
And I was their general!
[grunting]
Taste the power of my rage!
Rage has no real power,
or taste, for that matter.
[grunting]
It's the orphan
child of fear and despair.
[grunting]
Moon staff.
Only the defenders of Thalius
Prime carry that weapon.
Yes. And I personally pried
this one from the cold hands
of one of their fallen soldiers
as a trophy.
Ahhh!
Your kicks need work.
A little higher
at the knee, I think.
Speaking of taste, though,
you really should
try this melon, brother.
Very sweet.
[grunting]
You don't deserve
to wield that staff.
You're supposed to be a soldier.
How could you destroy such
good people as the Thalians?
They were brave warriors
that stood with honor!
I massacred them
because they were weak.
[both grunting]
My soldiers
followed orders perfectly,
with unquestioning loyalty!
[both grunting]
If you were truly a soldier,
you would know that blind loyalty
is far better than honor or bravery!
[grunting]
[gasping]
Sit still so I can hit you!
No, brother.
You sit still.
[groaning]
There's a storm coming, brother.
And the galaxy will need everyone
of strong and true heart to survive.
What in the name of Grotz
are you talking about?!
Your anger and rage
may lead to your doom.
Personally, I think
you should avoid that.
But there is always hope.
- You're the Green Lantern.
- No, not me.
I travel a different path.
Nice going, kid.
- You found the ring.
- Actually...
Funny that the ring hasn't
chosen a Green Lantern yet.
Maybe one of the castaways.
[chuckles] No, those castaways
are bad news, trust me.
We need to find the others
and get off this planet... now!
[both grunting]
Good fight, Kilowog.
It is a good ending.
[groaning]
[yelling and grunting]
No.
That's a good ending.
Luckily for you and your friends,
it is a very good day to die.
[console beeps]
General, what about Grood?
Forget him.
We have his ship now.
Let's get off
this horrible rock.
I look forward to watching that
asteroid from a safe distance
as it obliterates
this accursed planet.
[groans] I'll knock
that smile off his face.
Uh, Kilowog, is there a reason Aya's
flying off and leaving us?
She's not.It's those castaways.
They stole the ship.
Unh!
- Whoa!
[console beeps]
[grunting]
- Unh!
[groans]
[beeping]
Aya's back online.
We're ready to blow this munktor stand!
Jordan, now!
It doesn't make sense. Why did
the ring stay here on this planet
and not go back to Oa?
Go! Go back to Oa!
It can't be.
Kilowog, take off now.
Right now.
I have to stay behind.
There's something I have to do.
Jordan, time's up.
The ring didn't find
a replacement. We gotta go!
It did. Our hero's
been here the whole time.
Get Aya and Razer off this planet.
Trust me.
I ordered you off this rock.
What are you doing?
I'm disobeying orders.
[booming voice]
I... am... Mogo.
Thank you, Hal Jordan of Earth.
You have saved me.
Rather, by giving me the ring,
by knighting me,
you allowed me the power
to save myself from that asteroid.
Our pleasure.
For countless millennia
I have trapped evildoers
here on my surface until they reform.
I will keep these prisoners
if you do not mind.
Knock yourself out.
You have given me
new purpose, new power.
I am proud to be a Green Lantern.
Very proud.
And I will be here
whenever you have need of me.
I gotta say, Jordan, you're
gathering one unorthodox team,
but it's an honor to be a part of it.
Welcome to the
Green Lantern corps, Mogo.
www.tvsubtitles.net