1x09 - In Love and War
Previously in Green Lantern...
I'll pick you up
after work. I promise.
Maybe we'll be back in time for
your date with Carol after all.
Dinner will have to wait.
We're here now.
We fight them.
We stop them.
Is that all it takes
to stop a Green Lantern...
a broken heart?
You want to talk about it,
Sir Mopes-a-lot?
No.
I miss Galia, ok?
Hey, I know.
You're not the only one
who left someone they care about.
You need something to take your
mind off this emotional stuff.
Sensors indicate an entity
8,000 meters off the starboard bow.
Contact in 20 seconds.
Thank you, Aya. That's
exactly what I'm talking about.
So, Kilowog, you're in charge.
What's your move?
Look, Jordan, I appreciate
what you're trying to do,
but I'm just not up for this.
[crashes]
[all grunting]
Unh! What the heck?
[snarls]
Oh!
- That's a real monster.
- I did give ample warning.
I thought you were
playing along. Let's go, guys.
[roars]
[snarling]
[all grunting]
Aya, shock that thing off the...
[grunting]
[squeals]
[growling]
[grunting]
[all grunting]
[roaring]
[squealing]
How many lantern colors
are there?
So you're, what, Pink Lanterns?
Not precisely, Green Lantern.
Where you value willpower,
the Star Sapphires channel the power
and serve the cause of love.
[purring]
Thanks for the assist.
How do you happen to be
in this neck of the woods?
This sector of space is ours.
But pardon my manners.
I am Aga'po.
This is my niece Gieta.
You're mighty handy
with those power rings.
We sure could use your help
fighting the Red Lantern corps.
I would enjoy allying
myself with you, Hal Jordan.
We are close to our home planet.
Perhaps you'd accompany us
for rest and repair
before you resume your mission?
[chuckles]
I don't mind if I do.
Course plotted for Zamaron.
Kilowog, you seem so bereft.
I'd rather not talk about it.
You suffer from a great loss.
A broken heart.
Razer, you sure
you don't want to come out?
They're throwing us a party.
How delightful for you.
I'll pass.
Not a people person yet,
but we're working on him.
Aga'po, you weren't surprised
when you saw us.
How do you know about
the Green Lanterns?
Long ago, we were of one race
with your masters.
You and the guardians?
Thanks for putting that in my head.
And usually, hot girls
don't go for the nerds.
It was long ago.
We took very different paths.
They refused to allow any emotion
to influence their judgment.
We found this insufferable
and foolish.
Sounds like our guardians, all right.
My people believe that only
love can save the universe.
Love fuels our rings.
Its power is unfathomable.
Hail, Queen Aga'po.
We will celebrate
with a feast this evening.
Gieta, entertain them
until then, yes?
So, not that I'm complaining,
but are we going to be
the only men folk at this party?
We of Zamaron have found that
life is more peaceful and loving
when women are in charge.
I don't know.
I've had some female bosses
who could be a real pain in the...
We have some time
before the feast, Hal Jordan.
May I show you some sights?
[sighs]
Well, Hal Jordan? Is it not
the most wondrous of places?
Yes.
Uh, but let's not be late
for the banquet.
We shouldn't keep your aunt,
the Queen, waiting.
Galia?
Is it really you?
Hello, my love.
What are you doing here?
And in one of them
Star Sapphire outfits?
Don't you like it?
Baby, you'd look good
in a gorlian sand sack.
But I don't understand.
How is this possible?
- How did you...
- Hush.
I have something to show you,
something to keep our love
alive and thriving forever.
Repairs from the attack
are complete,
but Green Lantern Kilowog
is not responding.
- His energy level has gone flat.
- He's dead?
No. He seems to be
in stasis.
I knew this planet was going to
be more trouble than it was worth.
Interceptor to Hal Jordan.
Kilowog's not answering hails.
Is he with you?
Kilowog's a big boy, Razer.
[chuckles] I'm sure he's fine.
What is taking so long?
These Lanterns can help us
much more than ordinary males.
The Bolovaxian came willingly.
The earthling should be
as easily persuaded.
My Queen, Hal Jordan is different
from any other male I've met.
I've never felt like this,
never experienced the...
Remember who is supposed to
fall in love with whom, Gieta.
Take stronger actions, or I will.
[gasps]
Delicious.
What is it?
The juice of the Kavleen fruit.
It's said to replenish the
spirit and enhance the senses.
This is my favorite place
in the palace.
- Is the view not wonderful?
- Yes.
It's... romantic, don't you think?
Very.
Of course.
He already has a true love.
How else could he resist Gieta?
[kisses]
Miss Farris,
we've done everything possible.
We've turned over every rock,
followed every lead.
There's no trace of Hal Jordan.
What are you saying?
At this point, we'd advise you
to terminate your search
and move on.
I'm very sorry.
Thank you for your efforts.
[weeping]
[gasps]
Carol Farris of Earth,
you have lost your true love.
The Star Sapphires offer
to make your heart whole again,
to reunite you,
to make you one of our own.
I don't wish to harm you,
but know that I will.
- Now, stand aside.
- Stop.
This is an honored guest,
one of the heroes who rescued me
so valiantly today.
Now, tell me,
what's bothering you?
What have you done to Kilowog?
Where is he?
I do not know where he is
at the moment,
but I am certain he has come
to no harm.
Come. We'll find
your comrade together.
Kilowog's life force signal
is nearby,
but his vital signs are too weak
for me to pinpoint.
Robot, you are not welcome.
But I must. I am...
We have no use
for emotionless machines.
Your presence is tolerated
on my planet
only because of
the heroes you serve.
Wait here, Aya.
I will conduct my own search.
I wonder how Kilowog's doing.
Maybe we should look for him.
You seem tense, Hal Jordan.
Look, you shouldn't...
Ahh. Ha.
That does feel pretty good.
Ah. Let's... let's give him a few
more minutes to turn up on his own.
And you should really stop that.
In 4 or 5 hours.
[beeping]
[beeps]
Razer, I must speak with you immediately.
[grunts]
Ahh!
Ohh!
Stop!
What a shock.
Kilowog's not here, either.
Worry not.
We'll find him.
I always get what I want.
I am the Queen.
[both grunt]
Razer,
they have imprisoned Kilowog.
Let me get you a refill,
Hal Jordan.
- Green Lantern?
- Carol?
The ring said
it'd take me to my love, but...
It's you.
You're Hal.
Oh, Hal. Oh.
I can't believe I was
ever fooled by this stupid mask.
Carol, I don't understand.
How... how can you be here?
How on...
I thought you were dead. I...
Oh, Hal, I thought
I'd never see you again.
I see I've interrupted something.
No, no. Carol, I...
Ahh! [grunts]
[grunts]
All this time,
I thought you were dead.
Well, now you're going
to wish you were dead.
You've got it all wrong, baby.
She's just a friend.
Don't worry, sister. I won't
forget your part in this.
You're suffering delirium
from the transformation.
We Star Sapphires are
beings of love.
Carol, stop.
I don't know how you got here,
or into that outfit, which you
look great in, by the way, but...
Oh, I do, because your little
tramp here is in the same outfit.
You've got to shake this off.
Whatever they've done to you...
What they did is give me power.
[grunts]
You let me think you were dead.
And all the while, it was just
party time for old Hal, wasn't it?
First of all, nothing happened
between me and Gieta.
And second, this is nuts.
Let's just talk.
You want to talk?
Talk to the hand.
Oh!
Do not believe
the soulless automaton.
I have ample reason
to trust her over any of you.
Guards, take them.
[grunts]
- Let me go!
- I won't.
Letting go of you the first time
was the hardest thing I've ever done.
- You're lying again!
- Carol...
If that's what you think...
Hal?
What's going on?
Where on Earth are we?
We're not on Earth, Carol.
It may sound crazy,
but we're on the other side
of the galaxy
on the front lines of a war.
If my friends and I can't stop
this Red Lantern invasion,
we lose everything.
And that's why I'm out here
and not with you.
Hal, I don't understand
all of this.
But if Earth needs someone
fighting for us out here,
they couldn't have chosen a braver
or more resourceful champion.
Handsome.
You forgot handsome.
Carol Farris,
you can keep him here
safe from harm,
safe from the war.
The power of your love
can hold him here.
Oh, honey, that's not love.
That's selfishness.
Real love is sacrifice,
putting another's needs
before your own,
doing what's best
for the person you love. Here.
You can have this ring back.
Pink's not really my color.
Though I will miss the boots.
But... no one has ever rejected
the Star Sapphire power ring.
No one has ever had
the strength.
You look pretty strong to me.
You shame me,
Carol Farris of Earth.
I did not truly
understand love until now.
You will be returned
to your home planet.
Carol, I...
Do whatever you have to do,
then come home to me.
[distant explosion]
Green Lantern Hal, you are needed.
Just where Aya said he'd be.
Galia.
Oh. You.
What'd you do that for?
I was so happy!
Yeah, I'm the bad guy for not
letting you stay a lawn ornament.
Snap out of it, sergeant.
We have a war to fight.
[all grunting]
[grunting]
[groans]
You will surrender Kilowog, witch.
Child, your friend is happy,
like you soon will be.
Aga'po, please listen.
We must release the men.
We've been laboring under an
imperfect understanding of love.
Earthling Carol Farris
rejected the ring
and put her love's needs
ahead of her own.
- That is true...
- Silence!
Men spread war.
The Star Sapphires bring
the gift of love.
The galaxy will know peace only
when all men have been gentled
by love's violet light.
So, you did have a true love.
One who died...
but whose form lives again.
In this robot.
It's true. You.
You were in my mind.
You stole the image of Alanna
from my memories.
I meant no harm.
I simply based
my mechanical form
on the last imprint I had
in my database.
Enough talk.
This Red Lantern is dead inside.
He has nothing to fuel us.
It is a mercy to destroy him.
Aah!
By the way,
is that a "no" on the whole
teaming up against the threat
to the galaxy question?
Summon the Cephalon!
[rumbling]
[roaring]
[all grunting]
Go, Hal Jordan.
Go while you can.
I owe you one.
- Galia?
- Kilowog, we have to leave.
Galia!
I am disappointed in you, Gieta.
You have much to learn.
No, my Queen.
I have much to teach.
www.tvsubtitles.net