1x10 - Regime Change
Previously on Green Lantern...
This threat may turn to be
nothing more than a few extremeses.
If the truth does come out,
many will wonder why it isn't
recorded in the book of Oa.
Because, Sayd, history
is written by the victors.
So, you've come to gloat.
That's not why I'm here.
The power ring chose you over me.
You get to be the all powerful
Green Lantern Queen Iolande.
And I, your poor, ordinary relation,
I get to decay in a cell.
I'd give back the ring if
it could change what happened.
You broke my heart, Ragnar,
the day you killed
Green Lantern Dulak
and raised your sword
against me.
- And now I'm your prisoner.
- But also my brother.
And I thought you'd like
a good meal.
Get out!
Get out of here!
I should be a Green Lantern, not you.
I hate you!
I'll destroy you all!
The Green Lanterns, you,
everyone!
Ragnar of Petrasis,
you have great rage in your heart.
A Green Lantern force is leaving Oa.
Even in light of my concerns,
I persuade the Council.
Don't take it personally, Ganthet.
Like you, Appa acts only
with the best of intentions.
I only hope it was a wise decision.
In their absence, Oa is vulnerable.
Hal Jordan and the other Lanterns
have been alone in the frontier.
Now, in mere months they'll have help.
In a year and a half they'll have help.
I may have a way to help them now.
[dinging]
Green Lantern of sector 2814,
what is the reason for this call?
According to the files Aya downloaded,
there's a massive Red Lantern
fleet headed to guardian space.
Naturally, we're wondering if you and the
rest of your blue man group have a plan.
We're deploying the corps
to defend against the invasion.
What?
You went right into attack mode?
Did you actually read my
report or just skim it?
Rest assured, your report
was submitted to the Council
and taken into consideration.
What is your point?
My point is, the Red Lanterns are
convinced that your army of robot assassins,
the Manhunters, slaughtered their citizens
and annihilated their entire sector.
They think it was a calculated
attempt to wipe them out.
Yes, a dramatic
and emotional story to be sure.
Atrocitus is merely using
propaganda to rally his troops.
But if this whole invasion
is based on lies,
wouldn't that be a reason
to try diplomacy?
If we could convince them
of the truth...
Do not presume
to question us, 2814.
The Guardians are the
greatest minds of the universe
and have come to this decision as one.
Jordan, you've got to hear this.
We have picked up an SOS signal
originating from planet Petrasis.
2814, what's going on?
Explain...
Sorry, got to take this.
We'll finish later.
This is Queen Iolande of Petrasis.
We are under attack by Red Lanterns
and desperately need
immediate assistance.
Please come.
Iolande?
Guess again.
- Ragnar.
- He's a Red.
Like the outfit? I have you
to thank for it after all.
[growls]
I used to think being
a Green Lantern
would give me everything
I ever wanted.
But I wasn't good enough, was I?
Well, it turns out my
hate for the Green Lanterns
did give me everything
I ever wanted. And more.
I rule Petrasis, as it should be.
Where's Iolande?
Don't worry, she's perfectly fine.
Or should I say perfectly confined?
We're not leaving here
without the Queen.
Kill them!
[all grunting]
Aah!
Uhh!
Oh!
[grunts]
Ahh!
Correct me if I am wrong,
but is a withdrawal not in order?
[grunts]
We're getting creamed out here.
If we don't pull back now, we're
dead and the mission's over.
- Ok, let's blow this montour stand.
- Hey, that's my line.
Uhh!
The Red Lanterns have blocked
our access to the ship.
That's what we get for
parking in a bad neighborhood.
Let's go.
Hello, Green Lantern.
You've made a fatal decision
returning to Petrasis.
Kothak, after all
that we've been through,
you still want to kill me?
I'm trying to keep us
from being spotted.
Come. Their patrols
are hard enough to avoid
without a Red Lantern
manhunt going on.
Ragnar and his new friends captured
Iolande and took over Petrasis.
I've been leading the resistance since.
But yesterday things went
from bad to unthinkable.
I've heard them call it a Liberator.
- Can you imagine?
- Yes. Yes, I can.
We must do something immediately.
That device will blow
this planet to dust.
So you've dealt with these before.
How did you defeat it?
Uh, that one didn't go so good.
- Then you are less than useless.
- Not quite.
You must disarm the weapon
before it destroys Petrasis.
This is not a sparsely populated colony,
it is a planet of 2 billion.
Maybe there's a way
to diffuse the situation,
show the Red Lanterns
that Atrocitus has been lying
through his weird teeth all along.
What are you speaking of?
The Red Lanterns believe this
crazy story where billions of
years ago you guys sent an army
of killer robots to wipe them out.
Atrocitus told everyone,
so they want revenge.
If we could convince them he's lying,
we could stop this war.
We cannot do that.
Because it did happen.
Wha...
I mean, the robots were real?
And killed all those people?
The Manhunters were created
by the Guardians long ago.
They were the forerunners
of the Green Lantern corps.
For awhile the Manhunters
were the perfect police force.
They were never swayed by emotion,
only right and wrong.
But this is not a universe of absolutes.
Their inability to understand
and interact with emotional beings
ended in tragedy.
The Manhunters destroyed
people, planets, entire sectors,
forming what we now call
the forgotten zone.
The Manhunters are
our greatest shame,
the Guardians' darkest secret.
It's time for the source
of collected guardian guilt
to face the light of day.
You focus on disarming
the Liberator.
I may be able to assist you,
but I must first speak with Appa.
We're counting on you, Ganthet.
Hey, Red, any chance
you and I can get our ship back?
I believe we can handle
that little errand.
Kothak, we have a Queen
to rescue and a bomb to disarm.
The fact is we will never be
able to end this Red Lantern threat
without admitting to our own
tragic part in their history.
You indulge in guilt, Ganthet.
It clouds your better judgment.
The Council, you with us,
decided silence was best.
The corps only need know
what we tell them.
We must not allow Petrasis
to pay the price for our sins.
The loss of a planet,
however unfortunate,
is inconsequential
against maintaining
peace and order
on a million others.
I disagree strongly
with your moral calculus.
And there is still hope for Petrasis.
Before Hal Jordan
borrowed the interceptor...
Stole, you mean.
- Ahh. At your urging.
- I put something aboard,
something that could boost
their power exponentially
should the need arise.
Not your prototype.
Ganthet, an experimental device
based on a theory
about hope and will
is emotional madness.
And to do this without
the Council's knowledge?
Hal Jordan needs our help.
We must act now.
Perhaps you are right, Ganthet.
It is time for the truth to come out.
[beep]
- Hal.
- Come on, there's not much time.
Guardians of Oa,
you have been called here
to discuss a grave matter.
There has been an unforgivable
breach of trust
that must be brought to light.
What he says is true enough.
There is a traitor among us.
And his name is Ganthet.
Consider what you are doing.
Silence. According to Guardian
law, the accused will not
speak before the charges are
brought before the Council.
By his own admission, Ganthet
aided and allowed Hal Jordan
to take the interceptor
without Council approval.
But worst of all is Ganthet's
blatant use of an unreliable emotion.
It is true.
I believe willpower is not enough.
We need hope.
We all need hope.
Embracing a base emotion is a violation
of the trues that we hold sacred.
And for that, you are banished.
I'm sorry for getting
you all into this mess.
Oh, don't apologize.
We love this kind of stuff.
What are you doing here?
The Liberator is under attack.
They think me weak?
Kill Iolande.
Dunce! Your sister is one of the
Green Lanterns attacking the device.
Grr!
Send everyone!
I will lead the counterattack.
All units report
to the Liberator at once.
Your treachery threatens
everything we believe in.
I am not the threat here,
Ganthet. You are.
The citizens of guardian space
put their trust in us,
come to us for guidance.
What would happen if they learned
the truth about the forgotten zone?
All order would be lost.
There would be chaos and suffering
beyond anything the Manhunters had done.
You maintain a lie.
Ganthet, you are hereby
banished, sentenced to live out
the rest of your days cut off
from your species and civilization.
I almost feel the base emotion
pity for you.
Only almost, though, Appa?
And there's the pity.
[gunfire]
Uhh!
[all grunt]
Hold on. I've still got
an ace up my sleeve.
[dinging]
Guardians of Oa,
this is Green Lantern of sector 2814
calling for Ganthet.
I need immediate assistance.
I'm afraid Ganthet
is no longer with the Council.
Where is he?
My apologies, 2814, but as you
say, I must got to take this.
- What did they say?
- We're on our own.
They're closing in!
[growls]
Aah!
Ahh! Ohh!
Ahh!
- Excellent aim.
- Thank you.
Yah!
The cavalery has arrived.
- Sayd.
- Ganthet, I've come to trust you.
I reprogrammed the ship's destination.
You could be banished
for what you've done.
If there's a chance we can
help Hal Jordan, we must try.
It's sealed.
Get that door open.
Aah!
Warning.
Lantern engine overheating.
[all grunting]
- Will it work, Ganthet?
- I don't know, Sayd.
But we must have hope.
You've lost, dear sister.
I am the ruler of Petrasis.
Do you understand me?
Ragnar of the Red Lanterns!
Uhh!
Huh?
Ahh!
Aah!
That's never happened before.
It's... it's a miracle.
See, the gods are with us!
[all cheering]
Do you guys see this?
Hoo hoo! Yeah!
It's like I'm super charged
or something.
[machine whirs]
- Why is it doing that?
- It's about to blow.
If we can't disarm it,
we'll get rid of it.
You've got to be kidding.
How are we supposed to lift this?
I can get used to this.
[all cheering]
You don't think that whole blue
light show was Ganthet, do you?
I don't know what just happened.
But I'm glad it did.
Thank you for all you've done, Sayd.
But still, I must leave Oa.
I wonder if what we did today helped.
It did.
I can feel it.
- Telepathy, Ganthet?
- No. Hope.
www.tvsubtitles.net