1x07 - Reckoning
Previously on "Green Lantern"...
You belong to the Red Lantern corps.
How's that phony ring holding up?
Without a Red Lantern battery,
eventually its charge will die.
Sooner the better.
Kilowog, get ready.
Should be in view right... now.
There it is...
Red Lantern mother ship.
Aya, make sure we have max
resolution and magnification.
Full spectrum scans. I want to
know everything about this rock.
Yep, waste dump at 06:00
mean sola time, like clockwork.
[clapping slowly]
Congratulations.
After weeks of stalking Shard,
you've unlocked the secret
of when they dump their garbage.
Can total victory be far behind?
I'm not hearing any better ideas
coming out of your talk hole, Red.
Hold on.
We're repairing the ship
so we can use the ultrawarp
and bring reinforcements from Oa.
While we're waiting,
I'm gathering as much intel as I can
without getting us killed
or letting the Red Lanterns know
we didn't die when they
blew up that planet.
Let me tell you
what Atrocitus would do.
He'd come after you relentlessly.
He'd keep coming until you were dead,
even if it meant his own death.
I was a fool to join you.
Soon I'll be as useless as you two.
You have no chance of victory if you
aren't willing to die for your cause.
[electronics beeping]
- What are you doing?
- None of your business.
Negative. You must have
permission to leave the interceptor.
Explain yourself.
I'm not a crew member.
I just quit.
Technically, you are a prisoner.
Now please return to the ship.
I do not want your actions to be
misunderstood by the others.
- Heh. Misunderstood?
- I know you are not evil.
Then you don't know me at all.
You have forced me to alert
Green Lanterns Hal and Kilowog.
They will help me bring you back.
No, you'll all be busy saving the ship.
[alarm sounding]
I've got a quadruple failure
in the ultrawarp reactor.
Is that even possible?
Life support offline.
Float controls offline.
Internal grav offline. Does
anything on this bucket work?
We're not floating,
so we have internal gravity.
I'm reading the boards right,
Jordan. And where's Aya?
I am here. Scanning systems.
Contrary to the readouts,
all functions are nominal to profile.
Maybe she's right. Cycle the
rocker switches for a hard reboot.
- So this was a... what?
- A diversion set by Razer.
We fell for the oldest
trick in the book.
Where's our little saboteur now?
I'd like to congratulate him
on his success.
He left the ship.
I do not know where he went.
Oh, I know exactly where he went...
Shard.
Intruder! Seize him!
Have you forgotten me so soon?
Legion leader Razer?
But you're dead!
We went to your memorial service.
You died a hero.
Not yet...
but soon.
Lord Atrocitus, Razer is back.
He's at battery square.
He's about to recharge his ring.
Zilius, prepare a proper
welcome for our Razer.
[beeping]
With blood and rage
of crimson red,
we fill men's souls
with darkest dread
and twist your minds
to pain and hate.
We'll burn you all.
That is your fate.
Ah, a lost son has returned to me.
I have.
I was captured by the Green Lanterns.
But it was only a matter of time
before I gained their trust.
Then I blew up their ship.
You did well, Razer.
I could only think of being here...
by your side.
To do this!
[gasps]
Did you really think I'd allow
you to recharge your power ring
without finding out
your true intentions?
What you received
was a mere light show.
Now tell me, what have you
really been doing all this time?
See? I told you
he was a lost cause.
And I say good riddance.
Who knows? Maybe he was
planning this the whole time!
If that were true, why didn't he
just kill us when he had the chance?
Instead, he took the time
to create a very convincing diversion.
Agreed. The program
is nearly undetectable.
My subsystems are studying
how it works even now.
My bet is he went to settle
his score with Atrocitus.
Then he should have made
funeral arrangements,
'cause that's a one -way ticket.
And he knows it, which is
why we have to stop him.
Of all your stupid ideas,
Jordan, this one wins the prize!
If you trust no one, Razer,
you're never disappointed.
[beeps]
Master, I can't believe you're
bringing out your personal battery
to power his interrogation.
He doesn't deserve this.
Elements of your story are true.
You have been with
the Green Lanterns.
And by the end of our talk,
you'll tell me everything
you know about them.
Now, let's begin.
This could go quick or slow,
but I really hope you choose slow.
[screaming]
They're shooting
at the asteroids, Jordan.
[screaming]
No. No more.
I'll talk.
See? A matter of time.
Speak up.
[growls]
Aah!
I'm going to miss you, Razer.
Schedule his execution.
We'll make an example of this one.
Aya, do you remember the plan?
You won't forget anything?
I am less likely to forget
than you, Green Lantern Hal.
- How's she gonna get in?
- With ease.
- I forgot she could do that.
- Patrol.
Come on.
It is by hate alone
I set my will in motion.
It is through the breath of rage
that vengeance is made manifest.
[indistinct]
For Wrath only do I live and die.
All hail...
who's there?
[grunts]
I warn you,
I can defend myself.
You hide.
I'll stall.
[grunts]
What are you doing here
in the middle of the night?
Official business. Sorry, sir.
Do I look like a "sir" to you?
I'm cleric Loran.
Lucky for you,
soldiers are always welcome
in the house of our lord Atrocitus.
Cleric Loran, it's been a
long time since I've been here.
I'd love to hear the story behind
these beautiful stained-glass windows.
Of course, my angry child.
The city represents the capital of
Ysmault before the guardians arrived,
but it would be any city on a thousand
worlds in our now-ravaged galaxy.
And then the guardians
descended upon us.
They said they would bring
peace and order,
but as the book of rage tells us,
lies tumbled from their mouths.
They said, "kneel before us,
and you will want for nothing."
but we would not worship them,
and their wrath was
deep and terrible.
The blue devils unleashed
their automaton manhunters,
and the guardians' soulless
avengers snuffed out every life,
stealing every breath
and stilling every heart.
It was his holy hate that bore
the first fruit of a Red Lantern,
he, our lord Atrocitus
of the five inversions.
So, by Red Lantern's light,
we shall bring vengeance
to those who laid us low.
[doors slam open]
Just what do you think
you're doing?
Does this look like your mess hall
to slam my door like that?
Have you no respect?
Pardon, cleric. We're
searching for two missing gunners.
I'll sweep here, men.
You go down the street.
[grunting]
[rifles cocking]
Hold your fire.
- Do you trust me?
- Uh...
Remember this lesson well.
This is what happens to those
who stray from my righteous path.
- Zilius, proceed.
- This might sting a bit.
[clattering]
Who dares?
I just caught this stinking
Green Lantern in your shrine.
Oh, boy.
So, it seems Razer wasn't the only one
to survive the explosion
of Colony 12.
You Green Lanterns are harder
to kill than I thought.
Uh, master? Permission
to cut off Razer's head?
What's your name, soldier?
Uh, Wrath, my lord.
You can execute
the one you caught
at the same time
Razer meets his doom.
Let's get started.
Death to all enemies of Atrocitus.
Aya, now!
Aah!
Warning,
power controls overloading.
Retreat to interior
safe zone immediately.
Hyah!
You were foolish to come!
I made my intentions clear!
Do you even have a plan
to get out of here?
Don't need one.
And you're coming with us.
They've infected our reactor
with a virus.
It's a trick, you buffoon.
You!
[all grunt]
Unh!
With blood and rage
of crimson red,
we fill men's souls
with darkest dread
and twist your minds
to pain and hate.
we'll burn you all.
That is your fate!
[screaming]
Huh?
Aah!
I know you'd willingly die today,
but do you have the strength
to live for a cause?
Because we sure could
use you right now.
Aya, we are go.
Table for 3.
Finish them.
I don't want prisoners.
I have shut down shard's
automated defenses
to allow the interceptor
to pass through.
Estimating arrival at docking bay 22
in 8 minutes and 40 seconds.
Good. Meet us there.
My own arrival may be delayed.
I am currently downloading a large file.
Don't be late for dinner, baby.
Over and out.
Ok, I've had about
enough of you posers!
[red lanterns grunting]
Unh!
[growls]
Everything's spinning.
Aya, ETA 30 seconds.
Where are you?
Your plan didn't work,
guardian lapdog.
If you'd like to reclaim your toy,
meet me at battery square.
[groans]
- It's a trap.
- Of course it is.
But we don't leave anyone behind.
I'll get the comp...
Aya, I'll get her.
Not alone, you won't.
You've got to get the sergeant
to safety and prep the ship for takeoff.
We won't get away from a dozen
Red Lanterns with only ring power.
We need that ship.
Too risky. We board the ship
now, and then I'll find Aya.
By then it will be too late!
You're always going on about
having the courage not to fight,
so do you have the courage
to leave this to me?
I'm trusting you to bring back
a member of my crew, Razer.
Don't make me regret it.
[groaning]
- Leave her alone.
- You want her?
Anything for you.
Unh!
I hoped you would choose wisely.
I hoped you'd be
an ambassad for my legacy.
A legacy of murder and hate.
Unh!
Aah!
I had such high ambitions
when I created you.
Aah!
You didn't create me, I did.
If only I had listened to...
If only you had listened
to your sad little farm girl?
Unh!
Aah!
Do you think what she said to you,
what you felt for her,
mattered in the least?
It was I who conquered
your world,
who set your warlords
against each other
to create destruction
and chaos and hate!
Unh!
It was I who saw your
potential and recruited you.
And when I saw
you needed only a nudge
to become a truly hateful creature,
then I sealed your fate.
It was I who slaughtered
your precious Elana.
Aah!
[groans]
Razer, we have to get
to the interceptor.
I have vital information
for Hal Jordan,
but my mobility has been impeded.
Will you aid me?
No. Do the best you can.
You die now.
If we do not leave now,
we will all die.
[groans]
[electronics beeping]
Aya, are you all right?
I am fine. Although my repairs
shall take some time,
that is inconsequential.
Your actions put us all in danger.
Atrocitus knows we're alive now,
and he'll be looking for us.
Our job just got infinitely
harder thanks to you.
Attention,
I have unlocked the encryption
on the files I stole from
the Red Lantern mainframe.
Warships, hundreds of them.
Better keep your ring charged, Red.
Looks like we all should.
www.tvsubtitles.net