1x04 - Into the Abyss
Previously on Green Lantern...
You proud of what you did?
Answer me!
Easy there, Kilowog.
We just got our butts
saved by a Red Lantern.
He's comin with us.
Unh!
Ahh. Grub time!
You got a problem, poozer?
Only that I dislike
clumsy 7-foot pigs.
Err!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Kilowog, break it up.
You, too, Razer.
What did I say about
killing each other?
Come on, Hal.
We're just fooling around.
Right?
The ship's too small
for this nonsense.
I want you two to shake hands.
It's an Earth custom to show
there's no hard feelings.
Come on. Shake hands.
Not like that.
Attention,
incoming distress call.
This is captain Goray of
the container ship Truvedon.
I've struck a pinhole
and unable to proceed.
One of my engines has failed.
The other is at full power,
but it's just slowing the inevitable.
I need help.
Aya, hold the transmission.
Could be a trap, Hal.
We get there,
the disabled ship opens up,
and the Reds start pouring out.
There are no Red Lanterns
in this sector.
- It's not a trap.
- How do you know?
I was in charge of
setting those traps.
This is Hal Jordan of
the Green Lantern corps.
Sit tight, Truvedon.
We're on our way.
I've got two questions:
"A" How far are we from that pinhole?
1.8 teraquads and closing.
Which brings me to "B."
What's a pinhole?
It's a microscopic
black hole at the center
of a whirlpool of energy.
The closer that ship
gets to the pinhole,
the stronger gravity becomes.
It will compress
that cargo ship into a space
tighter than a grub worm's vacuole.
That's close enough, Aya.
We don't want to get pulled in, too.
Deploy the tractor beam.
Anomalous gravitational
readings are infecting my instruments.
Unable to compensate.
Captain, do you have
any tow cables?
Deploying them now.
Ah. Heh heh.
Missed.
We'll have to go out
there and attach them to
the interceptor manually.
Anomalous gravity always
puts a bug in my britches.
If you don't think
you're up to the task...
Just try and keep up, punk.
Green Lanterns train
in variable gravity.
Let's see how you fly
when you 1,000 kilos,
then 6,000, then 2,000.
This is
a dangerous undertaking.
Why are we risking
3 lives to save one?
A Green Lantern protects
innocent life even
at the risk of their own.
That's what we do.
Oh.
Quite... a downdraft!
That's downdraw.
You don't make it over the gravity
whirlpool, you're dark matter.
[grunting]
[groaning]
All right, Aya!
Let's haul this baby out.
Warning. Gravitational
pull is too intense.
Cables cannot
withstand the strain.
The ship's stable for now,
but sooner or later,
I'm telling you,
it's going in.
We'll have to get
the captain ourselves.
Err.
You could have
given him a hand.
I don't need a recruit on
my 6 and especially not a Red recruit.
Down here!
Deal with it.
Thank the grollmother
you're here!
I'm at half power and have
no way to pull myself out.
Exactly what
are you hauling?
Some kind of eggs?
Leave them. With
the refrigeration out,
they're goning to
spoil anyway.
Spoil? It's only
a matter of time
before these things hatch.
Hatch?
I can't tell what kind
of creature's inside.
Who cares? Only vermin
and insects hatch from eggs.
- I hatched from an egg.
- My point exactly.
- Err.
- Ease up.
The Truvedon's logs
identify them as Spegnarians.
They are incredibly rare
ever since their planet was
devastated by volcanic activity.
So these eggs are some
kind of last-ditch colony?
I suppose so.
I was paid to avoid
major shipping lanes.
Well, you sure did that.
Change of plans.
We're gonna rescue
every life form here.
It's a waste of time.
He's right.
The starboard engine's dead.
Then we'll restart it.
I'll get the civilian clear.
You're leaving me
with him?
You two need
some bonding time.
I heard of you Green Lanterns.
I know you're brave and all,
but you're crazy to go back.
Brave, crazy--
it's a fine line.
Green Lantern Hal Jordan,
I have several suggestions to
conserve energy until
the inoperative engine is repaired.
Yeah. That's great, Aya.
Keep us out of the crush zone
for as long as you can.
He must not have heard me.
Engine room's this way.
This way.
That's the main power line.
As if you know how
a cargo ship works.
It's not some Red Lantern
death ride made ou
of lead foil and scrap wire.
And stay in front of me.
How's that phony
ring holding up?
Without a Red Lantern battery,
eventually its charge will die.
Huh. Sooner the better.
But for now as long as I feel rage,
it's as strong as yours.
[rumble]
Whoa!
Err!
I hope you're good at maakila.
That wasn't me.
This ship is falling to pieces,
and I'm sick of your
self-righteous braying,
you fat, green oaf!
Aah!
You kids stop that now, or I'm turning
this ship right around.
Isn't that exactly
what we're trying to do?
Try something like that
again, and I'm blowing
my ring charge on you,
pinhole or no pinhole.
I'm not afraid to die.
[boom]
You should be.
You'll live longer.
Unh!
Huh?
Hello? Can you hear me?
Start the engine now,
or both ships are going in.
Goray, why is
the computer offline?
Aya, are you there?
Aya!
What happened to her?
I don't care!
We're out of time!
Err!
Wait, captain.
Ease off that winch.
Unh!
We're going in!
The pinhole's overpowering
the ship's autograv.
Hold on!
Unh!
[metal creaking]
There.
It's braced for now.
But we're on the lip,
almost in the crush zone.
- Let's get out of here.
- Not without the eggs.
Where are you going?
To buy us some time.
Errrr!
Unh!
I'll keep you out of
the hole as long as I can.
Fix that engine, and,
Jordan, watch your back.
It's hopeless. Kilowog's a fool!
He'll die out there.
[grunting]
You see that?
The eggs are hatching.
Let's keep moving.
They're eating
the power lines!
My constructs don't
even slow them down.
Mine do.
Hey, hey, hey.
Remember?
Incredibly rare species?
What's the hold up in there?
Hatchlings. They're eating
through the power cables.
Don't stop unless you
want to get a lot thinner.
[groaning]
Navigation. Hello?
Hello?
Is anybody out there?
Goray, you're alive.
Tell Aya to bring
the ship closer.
Ring's almost empty.
I need her to spell me.
Your nav computer must
be damaged, not responding,
but I'll help.
[groaning]
Oh.
Ooh! Better not
touch that again.
Oh, great!
They're moving past us.
If they start eating the engine
before we get there, it's over.
We need a shortcut.
It's less cluttered
out here.
Yes. We'll have a nice, clear
plummet into the pinhole.
How you doing, buddy?
Errrrr!
Aah!
Aaaah!
Razer!
More hatchlings.
We're already outnumbered.
Think of how bad it will be once
the rest of the eggs open.
Look. I have no problem
bringing a Red Lantern onto
the team, but I will not
tolerate pessimists.
- They've doomed us all.
- What now?
This engine isn't just offline.
It's frozen solid.
Those alien hatchlings ate
through the lines
that power the heaters!
It would take a team
of engineers to restart it
before we collapse
into the pinhole.
We don't have a team
of engineers or time.
Razer, let's light this candle.
You want us to fire a frozen engine?
The explosion will be spectacular.
He's right, Hal.
If we start going in, Kilowog,
I want you to cut us loose.
Not happening.
You go, we all go,
and the worst part is
that the captain
who can't fly straight
gets to keep the interceptor.
Your stubborn friend is right.
I can't fix this, not without
another 5 pairs of hands.
We're not giving up.
Yell about the unfairness
of it all afterward.
Then we'll go down fighting.
At least my Red energy
makes a dent in them.
That's right. Green energy
doesn't affect them.
Wait, stop. Maybe I can get
you those 10 hands, Razer.
What are you doing?
Those things didn't
come from the eggs.
They came from the interceptor.
- They're Aya.
- You're deranged.
Aya's been gone since
before the bugs showed up.
Somehow she must have put
herself into these little bots
and snuck on board.
But they ate the power lines.
She was shutting down nonessential
systems to save power.
[ice cracks]
- Both engines are up.
- Aya, full reverse!
Even with the engines back online,
we're past the point of no return.
I live past the point
of no return.
Express elevator going down.
Not a bad shot for a Red.
[grunting]
It's no use!
We don't have enough
power to pull away!
I'm not trying to pull away.
I'm gonna fly this baby
right at it.
You're going to what?
If I can fly with
the current of the pinhole,
maybe I can generate
enough velocity
to slingshot us out of here.
Aagh!
Come on. Hold together.
Yeah, baby!
Still got it.
[chattering]
Well, what do you know?
So that's my cargo.
Cargo, huh?
Heh heh heh.
Look at you.
Heh heh. There's a few more
of these rascals running
around that tub of yours.
Err.
And to think, I was
going to abandon them.
You were foolishly brave today.
Yeah. Well, back at you.
Nice job saving me.
Thanks.
And thank you, Aya.
We'd all be feeling pretty
cramped right now
if it wasn't for you coming out
of your shell like that.
Yes, like a hatchling from an egg.
I'm not done.
It was dangerous to up
and leave your post.
We need to set a few
parameters, young lady.
A Green Lantern protects
innocent life, even
at the risk of their own, correct?
Wait. Wait a minute.
Aya, you do understand
you're a navcom,
not a Green Lantern, right?
You can't be a GL.
Why not?
Well, first off,
the ring's got to pick you.
- Why?
- Help me out.
Oh, no. No.
I want to hear this.
- Red?
- Leave me out of it.
Look. Green Lanterns
positively got to have
a physical body to walk around
and interact with people,
not a bunch of creepy bugs.
Parameters set.
A body like this?
[groans]
www.tvsubtitles.net