Previously on Green Lantern...
There are Lanterns dying out there!
We need to get out there and stop
who ever is targeting them. Now!
1x02 - Beware My Power, part 2
Hal Jordan of Earth, soon to be
former Green Lantern of sector 2814.
You are now charged with
treason, grand theft and...
Let's postpone my lynching until
I tell you a couple of things.
You see these handsome devils?
They're the Lantern killers you said didn't exist.
Call themselves Red Lanterns.
Ring any bells?
Red Lanterns, are you sure?
He has concocted this ruse to save himself
from a deserved punishment.
Respectfully, sir. I got an aching jaw
that says they ain't no ruse.
Their Power Rings fire
some sort of red energy tha-
They have rings?!
Powered by what?
Best guess... a huge desire to
mash us all into pulp.
I say we high tail it back to Oa, cram the
interceptor with as many GLs as she'll hold...
...ultra-warp back and kick their red butts
until they're black and blue!
Despite the colorful terminology,
a logical course of action.
Sensors have picked up an unmanned
probe sweeping the area.
Markings match the insignia of the
recently encountered hostiles.
Right. Red Lanterns.
Aya, plot intercept course. It's go time.
Hal Jordan of Earth,
do not terminate this communication..!
Sorry, gotta take this,
don't be a stranger.
This threat may turn out to be nothing
more than a few extremists.
If the truth does come out...
...many will wonder why it isn't recorded
in the book of Oa.
Because Sayd, the history is written,
or unwritten, by the victors.
Forget about snaring it, just blast it!
Warning! Shield degrading.
Hal, break off!
Stick to the plan.
We go for reinforcements, then come back!
We can't let this thing give away our position!
What position?!
We're going home!
The Red Lanterns cought you with your pants
down back on that rock and you want payback!
Direct hit to port ampoules.
Shield's degrading to critical.
Please do not let that happen again.
Get ready to fire when I clear that rock.
Peekaboo.
Happy?
That felt good!
A probe tlike that means the Red Lanterns are
more than two killers with rings and a symbol.
They're organized.
Yeah...
Looks like we can't hog all the fun.
Let's hit HQ and load up
the boys like we planned.
Aya, take us home.
Arching ultra-warp drives.
Ready in three... two... one...
Impel.
Are we there yet?
Aya, what happened?
Overload due to hairline crack
in the ultra-warp coil.
Most likely caused by last
missile hit by enemy probe.
For the record, she said most likely...
Not totally likely.
- What does that mean?
- It means we're gonna be a little late to Oa.
That's okay, I like to make an entrance.
Aya, please estimate time for repairs.
Calculating.
- Ultra-warp ready in nine point two...
- Nine minutes, no problem!
Nine point two one months.
Okay...
Can we form a construct and replace
the defective part for the ride home?
The construct would have to be an exact
copy of the ultra-warp coil mechanism.
And it's 56 moving parts to within
a 0.8162 microns tolerance.
Can either of you do that?
- I make hammers.
- Look, maybe it's for the best...
The Guardians won't deal
with the problem like we will.
We'll make those Red Lanterns pay.
Is he all right?
Just... a little light headed...
He's taken a beating.
He needs a real doctor, he's not making
nine hours, never mind nine months!
I was kinda looking forward to seeing Oa.
Aya, scan for the nearest inhabited world.
Preferably one with a hospital.
Don't bother...
I know my own sector anywhere.
We're not far from my home colony.
Sounds like a good place to lay low
for a while and get you fixed up.
You had three Green Lanterns
in your grasp, and let them escape?!
Perhaps you're not wholly committed
to our righteous crusade.
I live to serve the mighty Atrocitus,
your will is the core of my very being.
What good is that to me Zilius Zox...
... if you're not competent to kill
a mere three Green Lanterns?
It was this child's fault! He's been
promoted too quickly, and on false grounds!
He pitied them!
The destroyers of our system!
What do you have to say for yourself Razer?
Zox lies. But these Lanterns were
different from those we eliminated before.
Tougher... Better trained...
How could they know already?
- Who my lord?
- The Guardians of Oa!
If they've sent reinforcements then
your failure may jeopardize my plans!
No!
They must be destroyed!
They must die for Shard,
all for you and Shard, master!
That's right Zilius.
Shard is sacred ground.
A piece of the remains of
our world which
the Guardians attempted to
erase from the universe.
They did not succeed then,
and will not today!
Look.
It seems one of my hunter killer drones
found the Green Lantens.
Your "hunter killer drone" isn't
much on the killer part, is it?
The done's attack was a feint.
It's actual goal was to plant a tracker
which will lead us to them.
And then we'll draw out these
Guardian lapdogs and destroy them.
Wherever they may hide.
Don't be such a baby.
Very handy to have a doctor for a wife.
Medicine is something I picked up
because of my husband's second job.
She's actually the colony's head geologist.
I was an engineer, that was how we met.
Beata's the genius who dreamed up
using the volcanoes lava for thermal power.
So was that your secret identity,
engineer?
Secret what?
That's Hal's hang-up,
that thing on his face, it's a mask.
He wears it in case
some earthling sneaks
into the interceptor,
while in space mind you and goes:
Aha! The Green Lantern on my
planet is Hal Jordan! I'm telling everyone!
Haha... Talk to me when your planets invents
paparazzi and the 24-hour news cycle.
Daddy!
Wait... Who is this giant?
What have you done with
my daughter Amala?
I am Amala!
Now, now... Time for hugs later.
Let daddy rest.
Bye daddy!
This is some place...
Kinda reminds me of where I grew up...
Bolovax Vik.
I'm sorry.
Even here we heard about it's destruction.
Your planet was destroyed?
I-I never knew... how did...
Just concentrate on gettin' us out of
this mess you made hotshot.
Attention!
I have found a tracking device
on the interceptor's hull...
... and require assistance removing it.
Do you think they..?
Yeah.
Pretty sure they do.
Whoa!
What is it?
This colony know enjoys the protection
of the Red Lantern Corps.
You have been liberated from
the tyranny of the Guardians.
But their Green Lantern
lackeys are here...
You have one solar hour to
bring these war criminals to us...
... or your planet will be vaporized.
Those murdering red...
We have to turn ourselves over to them.
Shyir, no!
- We don't have a choice!
- These guys are murderers.
They're gonna blow up this rock
no matter what you do!
We do have a choice.
We can fight them. And keep fighting,
until we can't fight anymore.
That thing is a fortress.
A frontal attack would be suicide.
Hey, if you've got
another way, I'm all ears,
but we've got to take that thing out!
The Earth-Man is right, we must go!
Shyir, wait!
I have another way!
Time's up! Shall I initiate
the countdown to detonation?
No. Razer will do it.
Atrocitus, our cause is right and just...
But, to kill innocents...
As I told you master, he's weak!
Weak...
The Guardians and their lapdogs
destroyed my homeworld.
And Zilius's.
And countless others.
By making an example of these disloyal few,
we save millions later.
Show weakness now and
you doom our people forever.
I am not weak.
I am not a coward.
For the greater good.
And vengence!
Countdown sequence initiated.
You have five minutes to get
to minimum safe orbital distance.
Knock, knock!
Anybody home?!
Zox, come!
Razer, stay and guard the device.
If attacked, do your duty.
Soon your ring will be
all that's left of you Lantern!
Settle down, demented beach ball.
I am Atrocitus.
Lord and master of the Red Lantern Corps.
I am the one who will destroy
the Guardians and all they stand for.
I am wrath!
I am hate!
I am righteous vengeance!
According to Beata's map,
we're right under it.
Boy, I hope she is right about this.
I'm bakin' here!
She's always right.
This way!
That must be the controlpanel.
You think you can disarm it Rev?
I'll need a few minute-...
Die, die, die!
Hurry up, Rev!
This guy's not playing around!
Keep him back,
for just a couple of minutes.
This is your fault!
You Green Lanterns might
enjoy destroying worlds. But I do not!
I case you haven't been
keeping up on current events...
... you guys put this thing here,
and pressed the button!
You wanna help!?
Stop fighting us!
I won't listen to your lies.
I'll destroy you both!
And what, you gonna mass murder
them by blowing up the planet!?
You know what you're fighting againts, kid.
But what are you fighting for?!
Dumb kid...
Where are Shyir?
Lets have some good news!
Detonation in thirty seconds.
This is disappointing.
If you're the best the Guardians have,
my victory is assured!
Master, the bomb is active.
We need to move away.
Three...
Two...
One.
Detonate. Detonate.
Time to go.
I can keep the laser from igniting
the plutonium, for a little while anyway.
I know what happened to Bolovax Vik.
If you had a chance to save your world...
What would you do?
It's been an honor.
It's foolish to stay when there's
no hope, Green Lantern.
Yeah... we're dumb that way.
But there's always hope.
I know you're not all bad.
Maybe it's time you let others know too.
Best get going, son.
I can handle this last part myself.
It appears you were wrong about Razer.
Never have I been so happy to be wrong.
I'll have the choir scream his
praises at the Rage ceremony.
Now that we've eliminated
the Lanterns from Oa...
soon this galaxy will be ours
for the taking.
And then the Guardians will pay
for what they've done!
Kilowog? Rev?
They aren't here anymore.
Is that the best you can do?!
You think that will stop me?!
You won't will unless you can
do what is necessary.
Can you do it?
Can you?!
Finish it.
You'd like that, wouldn't you?
But you're not getting of that easy.
You'll live with the consequences
of what you've done.
No! You must kill me!
I'm the one responsible for all
this death and destruction.
I deserve it!
Which is why you're going
to help make up for it.
Coward...
Are you too weak to take your vengance?
Don't... push it...
- You ganna help me with this, hotshot?
- Kilowog!
I got most of the colonists up before
the big bang, but my ring is running low.
I believe I can help.
What's he doing inside that bubble?
Never mind him.
You are a sight for sore eyes. You too, Aya.
Thank you.
What about Rev.
Did he make it?
I hope everyone knows the sacrifice
Shyir made.
They do. The elders are going
to name our new planet after him.
Your daddy was very brave, Amala.
He saved us all.
Is it okay if I still miss him?
Yeah. We all will.
You know,
Shyir really did save them all.
He asked me what i'd do if I had
another chance of saving my own planet.
And thats when it hit me,
I'd save the people.
At least one of us got it right.
Cooling system now functional.
Continuing repairs.
So, what's next?
Next, we find the Red Lanterns.
Just how are we gonna stop who knows
how many super poweredful
Red Lanterns with just the two of us?
That's a really good question, Kilowog.
Here's another one, what should
we do with the one we captured?
www.tvsubtitles.net