Green Lantern
~ The Animated series ~
Previously on Green Lantern...
For the greater good...
...and vengeance!
I'm the one responsible
for all this death and destruction!
Which is why you're going to help
make up for it.
Season 1, episode 3:
"Razer's Edge"
You like looking at that stuff,
"Boozer"?
You proud of what you did?
How many of you Red Lanterns
are out there?
And why are you hunting
Green Lanterns?
Answer me!
Easy there, Kilowog!
This thing's a rental, remember?
The Red Lanterns abandoned you,
Razer.
Left you for dead.
I think that calls for a little payback,
don't you?
Help us.
Tell us what you know.
I do hate the Red Lanterns
for what they've made me.
But that doesn't mean
I stopped hating Green Lanterns.
It just means
I have more people to hate.
Hal Jordan stole the Interceptor.
And you wish to reward him
by giving him command of it?
Appa, we have no choice.
They are our only line of defense
on the Frontier.
Besides, at that distance,
there's very little we can do
to punish Jordan, anyway.
Then, we are of one mind.
The crew of the Interceptor
is tasked with gathering intelligence
on the Red Lantern threat
and taking reasonable action
to slow their advance.
We may be of one mind,
but only on the protest.
Now. What is the status
of the Red Lantern's ring?
Safe.
In a stasis box.
Yeah, the ring doesn't take
that much room.
Unfortunately, Razer does.
What do you suggest
we do with him?
Even you know your duty,
Hal Jordan.
He must be imprisoned.
Fools! For what I have done,
they should execute me.
I do not understand
your desire for self-destruction.
If one regret's one's actions,
one should find a way
to make restitution.
I'm not about to debate this
with a computer!
- Any orders?
- Yeah, find me a prison.
It's not like we can just drop Razer off
on a handy Lantern science cell.
Frontier Lanterns
use privatized penitentiaries.
- I can compile all the detailed places...
- That won't be necessary, Aya.
- Just something nearby.
- But nothing too nice.
Wow, she really took you at your word
about the "nothing too nice" thing.
It ain't that bad...
Are you kidding?
This place gives me the creeps.
It's like fear radiates
from the walls.
It's a dark dang repulsive hall
full of...
Spiders!
I was gonna say "rats", but...
Oh...
Well, well...
Green Lanterns!
It's been a long time since
we hosted a prisoner
for our esteemed
colleagues in justice.
I take it you're the warden?
I am Myglom. I operate this prison
on behalf of the Spider Guild.
Aah... it appears
you have something for me.
This piece of work is Razer.
We have documented evidence
of his crimes against sentient...
Oh, I'm quite confident
he's guilty.
No one has ever escaped
from this facility.
I'm very proud of that...
But I'm even more proud
of our rehabilitation program.
You'll find that nearly 100%
of our former... guests
never returned to a life of crime.
Well, I'm sold!
Myglom, we hereby officially
remand custody of Razer to your care.
That's one Red Lantern down...
More where that came from...
Make yourself comfortable,
prisoner...
I doubt very much
that these machines will be able to...
...rehabilitate me.
Oh, don't be concerned
with any of these.
Soon you'll find yourself far...
...far away.
I don't know about you,
but I'm gonna sleep a whole lot easier
knowing that guy ain't on board.
Now we can get back
to nailing those Red...
...Lanterns.
- Did you see that?
- What?
Out the window?
In space...?
There!
Right there!
Right where?
I am not crazy!
I saw something there!
What is up with you?
Fan out.
Our hitchhiker's hiding somewhere.
Will you stay out of my way?
We're going about this all wrong!
Whatever it is, it's intelligent.
It's watching us
and staying one step ahead.
- Why are you yelling at me?
- To cause a distraction,
so I can do this!
OK, squid, start talking.
Kilowog here loves seafood
and has a big appetite.
- What? - It's an old
interrogation method from Earth.
Good cop, hungry cop.
Goggan will not go back!
Cannot go back!
Destroy me, but do not take me
back to the grim rock!
Do the lockage like my worst?
Wait... ugly and nuts!
You escaped
from the Spider Guild's prison.
Yes... with this!
Goggan cannot... from here!
And insane, saneeee!
Goggan rid the airshaft
and flew!
Still sane...
You shouldn't have bothered,
nut job!
Cause you're just going right back
to prison, where you belong!
No...
Please, no!
Mercy!
Not back to nightmare rock!
Goggan lives his pain there.
Torture...
Goggan is a child to handhold
the worst of fates!
Again... and again...
What? The squid con
would say anything
to stay out of prison!
- And if he's telling the truth?
- Razer's worse than a criminal.
If the spiders wanna
torture him, let 'em!
It's our job, our duty
to serve and protect.
Even if they're criminals.
Intriguing!
The criminals must be punished.
Surely prisoners deserve their fate.
They deserve justice, which
sometimes involves punishment.
But not torture.
Look... We've got to take...
this back, anyway, so...
We'll have a look around.
OK. But even if there is
something wrong with the prison,
it's not like Myglom's
gonna let us see it!
They'll clean up their act
as soon as they'll see us coming!
That's why they're not going
to see us coming.
Please, don't say it...
We're going to break
in to prison.
It's worse than death!
Infinity upon infinity...
You mustn't go!
Don't worry, Goggan,
just taking a quick look around.
Dinner's in two hours.
If we're not back, start without us,
because we're probably dead.
We really doin' this?
Really?
The fighting is stopped.
For now.
They'll be back.
The warlords always come back.
Maybe someday
they'll leave us alone.
The Forgotten Zone will be a place
where we can raise a family...
Without worry...
Without fear...
I'm going to help
make that happen.
By joining the Militia.
Razer, no!
Please, no!
I'm sick of hiding,
while the warlords take what they want.
You think more fighting will help?
Our people need teachers
and doctors and builders.
Not more soldiers!
I'll gain power in the Militia
and protect everyone.
Especially the ones
I care about most.
We should check out
the accommodations.
Well, there's no view...
But there's clearly entertainment.
For the guards, anyway.
We don't know that stuff's for torture!
This could be the rehabilitation
that Myglom talked about.
Whoever was being rehabilitated here
was scratching desperately to escape.
These yellow stones are everywhere.
They make my skin crawl.
I've never seen you scared before.
I ain't scared of no rocks!
Let's get out of here.
I'm almost 90% sure
I remembered to charge it this time!
Ilana!
Dar...
I came back for you...
I came back!
Rings are still down.
It makes no sense.
They're charged, but the only thing
working is the universal translator!
Something's interfering with them.
My Green Lantern friends...
I'm shocked,
shocked to find you
in this untore position.
Well, then cut us down.
I'm afraid, not.
Now that you've seen our...
humane cells.
Oh, your rings won't work here.
You must have noticed
this unusual metal, hm?
We stumbled upon a rich range of it nearby.
Not only does it
power and light the facility,
it has an interesting side effect.
It nullifies the energy
of a Green Lantern Power Ring.
So you do run a gulag,
after all.
Not at all...
We don't torture
the prisoners here!
Not in the...
traditional sense.
These devices
force the wearer to relive
their worst moments
again and again.
So, that's what you got
in store for us?
A couple of bad dreams?
Oh, no, no...
The memories
are only the beginning!
After we treat our prisoners...
Then, we eat them.
They're dead by now.
We must leave, leave,
before we're found!
Negative.
We will continue to wait.
The one said
he'd be back before dinner,
two hours ago!
Dinner time has past.
Dead!
There is a high probability
that Hal was attempting
to be humorous.
If they're not dead yet,
they will be soon!
Worse than dead, even!
Unacceptable.
Action must be taken
to rescue the Green Lanterns.
Even at risk to this unit.
Computer?
But...
But I came back for you.
I came back!
I came back for you...
I came back for you!
Razer,
of The Forgotten Zone
You have great rage
in your heart.
You belong to
The Red Lantern Corps.
Give in...
The Ring knows your pain...
Someone must pay!
You'll have your revenge...
This,
your new Master,
Atrocitous,
promises.
Razer, listen to me.
None of this is real.
This is not really happening.
Do not panic.
I am the Aya program.
I know this is a fantasy.
An illusion,
meant to bring me pain.
You know...
Then, why...?
The memories keep replaying,
over and over, in my head.
They hurt.
But I don't mind.
I get to see her again.
Even if
it's for one more moment.
I do not understand.
Pray you'll never do.
I need your help.
I cannot save Hal and Kilowog
without you.
Some force is keeping me
out of the prison.
The prison?
What are the Green Lanterns
even doing here?
They've heard the prisoners
are being tortured here.
And Hal thought
it was unacceptable.
They came back here
to investigate.
And to save you,
if that was true.
They shouldn't have done that.
I deserve to be here.
I helped destroying
an entire world.
All those people died
because of me.
No. Kilowog was able
to rescue the settlers
before the world
was destroyed.
What?
Then, I didn't...
It doesn't matter.
I'm still the one
who pressed the button.
In my heart,
I'm guilty of murder.
I'm going to stay here...
What you want is irrelevant.
I will never forgive this.
I have seen your past,
and know your pain.
No one knows my pain!
Certainly, not a machine.
Where, now?
Some force is preventing me
from exploring this direction.
I believe this is where
they are keeping Hal and Kilowog.
And the other way?
That is the path
back to the ship.
No!
You cannot leave them
to die!
Enough!
These two need
but little tenderizing.
Green Lantern is best eaten...
fresh.
And what are you
supposed to be?
I am Goggan.
Are we leaving?
Great timing, kid!
We just got our butt saved
by a Red Lantern.
I noticed.
We gonna stand for that?
No!
Oh, you want some boozer?
Cause there's plenty for everyone!
You weren't gonna leave
without saying "goodbye".
No... You have it
all wrong, Green Lantern!
I was kicking butt long before
I ever got this ring.
And I've been squashing bugs
even longer.
Myglom has been capture in the jail, sir.
Like you ordered!
The Guardians have dispatched
a new warden.
He should arrive
in 18 months.
In the meantime...
I'm designating
a temporary warden.
Congratulations, Goggan.
I'm leaving the prison in your capable...
hand...
...things.
I trust you can free the prisoners
from their cocoons?
Yes... yes!
Of course, I...
No one will ever be tortured here
again!
You know, for a second, I thought
you were gonna make Razer the warden.
Are you crazy? I couldn't possibly leave
a Red Lantern in charge of this place.
Because
he's coming with us.
You know how that thing
the Spiders used
made you relive
your absolute worst moments?
Yeah...?
I got a new one.
You do not seem
to have recovered from your ordeal.
You have seen my past.
It is private.
The intrusion was necessary
to ensure the crew's survival.
You are an artificial intelligence.
But you risked your existence
to save them.
A Green Lantern
would do no less.
www.tvsubtitles.net