1x05 - Heir Apparent
Previously on "Green Lantern"...
We fight them, we stop
them, whatever it takes.
Just how are we gonna
stop who knows how many
superpowerful Red Lanterns
with just the two of us?
I'm getting more comfortable
in my human/robotic form every day.
I can now assemble
myself in 2.1 seconds.
And up until two days ago,
you weren't much more than
a real smart disembodied voice.
Jordan, back me up here.
Any girl who can get ready in less
than 3 seconds has my stamp of approval.
Sensors have located
the energy signature
of a Green Lantern power ring
approximately 18.2 teraquads from us.
Great work, Aya.
Plot a course directly to that signal.
We're doing a little recruiting.
Which if successful will bring the total
of your Green Lantern Force to 3.
Atrocitus will be shaking in his boots.
4 including you.
And there would be 5 of
us if you included me.
Right, and how I could
forget with you constantly bringing it up?
Jordan, you got stuff the
genie back in her box.
You can't let our nav
computer get used to walking
around like a real person.
You may be unaware that
I can hear every sound on this vessel.
Aya, I appreciate
the enthusiasm, but I think
It's best if you stay with the ship.
Our queen and sovereign.
- Great timing as usual, Hal.
- It's a gift.
Hold. Observe their
garb and manner.
They are Green Lanterns
and friends.
I am Queen Iolande.
I welcome you to Betrassus.
Dulac used to tell
me stories of other
Green Lanterns,
but I thought they
were nothing but tall tales.
This is my brother Prince Ragnar.
Iolande, your name
sounds like a waterfall.
Worst line ever.
We're looking for the
Green Lantern that serves your planet.
Green Lantern Dulac.
He has protected
Betrassus for many years.
We need his help to fight a
deadly threat on the frontier.
You speak of the Red Lanterns.
Several of our off-planet
outposts have been attacked
by these vicious marauders.
You're probably the only
ones strong enough to fight
off the Red Lanterns.
Enough!
Betrassus doesn't
need Green Lanterns.
We need a king to command its
army, and that will be me!
Kothak, once again you
overstep your bounds.
It is our custom.
If the queen is coroneted
without a husband, then the
greatest warrior may claim
her hand and share the throne.
Face it, princess.
You don't have what it takes
to rule this kingdom alone.
Will no one challenge
Kothak for my sister's hand?
I will challenge Kothak
for the hand of Iolande.
I think we found our man.
I've seen the destruction caused
by the Red Lanterns with my own eyes.
I would be proud to join
your fight against them.
It will mean leaving the queen.
Iolande has no love for
a tired old warhorse like me.
I'll marry her to keep her
throne save from Kothak.
He is not to be trusted,
but once I win her hand,
I can best protect her and our
world by joining your crusade.
It's pretty easy to see why
you were chosen by your ring.
Happy to have you aboard.
I still can't believe you're here,
another actual Green Lantern.
I am sir Dulac's greatest
supporter, and now I'm
here to offer you equal devotion.
Excuse me for overhearing, but
you said the ring chose you to
be a Green Lantern.
Were there many tests of
your strength and bravery?
No. I was nearby when the
Green Lantern in my sector
died, and his ring came to me.
Anyone can seem like
a warrior when wearing the most
powerful weapon on the planet.
The terms of the challenge
state that we face
each other equally armed.
Then you'll see I'm more
a hero than Dulac will ever be.
We shall see.
He ought to be on a leash.
I will put a stop to
Kothak's scheming tomorrow.
Then you shall have my aid.
[cheering]
Boo!
[indistinct chatter]
Hmm.
Milady, sir Dulac cannot be found.
[crowd gasping and murmuring]
Clearly your precious
green knight has fled.
That doesn't make any sense.
Name one Green Lantern you've ever
known to run away from a fight.
So Dulac forfeits the challenge.
Iolande is mine.
We saw yesterday that there
is no one else on Betrassus brave
enough to face me.
No, but the is
one brave enough now.
Here we go.
I will fight for
the hand of Iolande.
[cheering]
I will not allow it?
This Green Lantern is an outsider
with no royal blood whatsoever.
If you win, you're gonna
have to stay here and rule.
We've got an agenda,
an intergalactic menace to destroy.
Don't get your
regulation undies in a bunch.
I'll defeat Kothak, then release
Iolande to rule in her own right.
Everybody wins, happily
ever after, boo-yah.
Does he understand the
challenge must be fought
without his precious power ring?
He does.
He's also right here in the room,
so you don't have to talk
about him in the third person,
and he looks forward
to kicking your butt tomorrow.
Err.
The ship is primed
and ready to leave.
Why aren't you back here
with the Lantern we tracked?
He's gone missing.
I can easily find him.
No. You can't just go running
around in that Red Lantern getup.
We've got enough on our hands
without you starting a panic.
My talents are
wasted waiting here.
Stay with Aya.
Have her run a scan
for Dulac's power ring.
Sensors have located
a weak energy trail.
It is possible that it is
Green Lantern Dulac's ring.
The energy trail is too
distant to make that
determination with
total confidence.
So you're saying we
need to be closer.
It would aid me, but
our orders are to remain on the ship.
I was ordered to help you
trace the power ring, which is
exactly what we'll be doing if you
put yourself together and go with me.
Only 2.1 seconds to assemble.
Are my components
properly aligned?
You look fine.
You also look fine.
You'll need practice.
Kothak is very skilled on his machine.
I could help you.
Back on my home planet,
I'm a test pilot for supersonic aircraft.
I don't think this little sidewalk skimmer
will give me any problems.
In fact, I'll probably invent a few
new moves while I'm feeling it out.
Whoa, whoa.
Whoa, whoa, ohh!
Unh!
You're right.
That was new.
For future reference, when
in my physical form, I prefer
not to be pushed into the dirt.
Whoa!
Nnunh!
Some hero.
I look forward to destroying you
in the tournament tomorrow.
You know, I think I'll
gratefully accept a couple of pointers.
Well, come along then.
If you can keep up, that is.
She fell for the waterfall line.
Unbelievable.
I thought you might be thirsty.
I like a little more slime
floating on top, but thanks, kid.
Have I told you what an
honor it is to have you here?
Over and over.
My beloved kingdom is under
threat and not just by the Red Lanterns.
There's an internal threat,
as well, so having two
Green Lanterns here
is a great comfort.
3 lanterns counting Dulac,
soon as we track him down.
Heck, 4 if you count Aya.
Heh. She'd love that.
Ha ha ha!
[motor sputters]
I had no idea these
machines were so unstable.
They aren't.
You think someone
did this deliberately?
Kothak is capable of anything.
This situation is
getting far too dangerous.
I want you to back out of
the challenge, for your own protection.
Back out? Not on your life.
This just got interesting for me.
You are brave.
I don't know if fighting for
my throne is even worth it.
A queen must be wise, strong,
clever, and a million other
things that I don't know if
I am or will ever be.
You're all of those
things and so much more.
How can you be so sure?
I'm a pretty good judge of character.
My sensors indicate the
energy signal is getting
stronger, but it seems
our search is over.
Not quite.
Dulac.
There doesn't seem to be any
signs indicating a struggle.
So he didn't go down fighting.
Odd.
His ring is gone.
Has it gone back to Oa?
The interceptor's sensors
would have noted that.
The signal is still near here.
It's time we notify the others.
Great job obeying orders.
Do I need to write
them down from now on?
A warrior acts.
A warrior listens to his superiors.
Enough. I'll give them the
insubordination lecture later.
What have you found?
We found his body in the catacombs.
We're still trying to
locate his power ring.
If it hasn't chosen
a new bearer already.
My sensors indicate that the ring
is somewhere within the castle walls.
My gut instinct tells me
so is the killer.
Then we must find this
murderer and bring him to justice.
It is what Green Lanterns do.
We will, but we have to do it carefully.
We'll need proof.
You go back to the ship.
We'll call if we need backup,
but we might have to make
a quick exit.
Kilowog and I have a trap to set.
[crowd cheering]
And here, another flagon of that ale
you so enjoyed before.
Hey!
You remembered the slime!
Iolande, prepare to wed
as soon as I defeat this peasant.
Know your place, Kothak.
Queen Iolande, I fight so
that your people might have
the capable, honest ruler they deserve.
Keep your chin up, Jordan!
Focus!
[cheering]
Come on, Jordan!
[coughing]
[choking]
Aah!
Ohh! Poison!
He's been murdered!
Kilowog! Come on, buddy.
Speak to me! Please.
Hal, he's gone.
No!
Whoever did this will pay.
The death of the outsider
is inconsequential.
I demand my challenger return
to the field so I may defeat
him and become the
rightful king of Betrassus.
Look! The ring!
[gasping]
Finally. It's mine!
The power I've dreamed of!
Again, I protest this delay.
Your silly contest no
longer matters, Kothak.
What matters is that I'm
a Green Lantern, the most
powerful citizen of Betrassus.
I shall be your ruler.
Bow down and grovel to me,
your new king!
You did this!
You murdered my friend!
I had to. You told me that
when a Lantern dies
his ring searches for the next
worthy person.
Knowing myself to be most
worthy, I killed Dulac so
that his ring might come to me.
[booing]
Do not judge me!
I loved Dulac more than any of you.
That's why I killed him,
to honor him by being his successor.
And Kilowog?
Why him?
Dulac's ring didn't come
to me, so I had to try again.
I had to!
Sorry, but I can't let
you get away with this.
You don't have a choice,
none of you!
Unh!
What happened to my ring?
Where is it?
I want my ring!
I still have it.
The ring you thought chose you was
a construct I made while playing dead.
Bravo, Kilowog.
Excellent performance.
Heh.
Aw, gee. Thanks.
I thought maybe slobbering
the grog all over a was a bit
much, but I sure has heck
wasn't gonna drink any.
Oh, Ragnar, I am heartbroken.
This is my planet.
I was born to lead!
I'll show you all!
My queen!
Your reign is over, sister.
Look at how easily I paid
off your guards.
If I cannot rule Betrassus,
then neither will you.
Attack now!
Kilowog, my ring.
Aah!
[groaning]
Give it up, Ragnar!
Don't be a fool!
Close the gates!
- Unh!
[moans]
Stay back!
Let me go, or I'll kill her.
Iolande, put the ring on now!
Aaaaugh!
Please!
I beg for quarter.
The true enemy is defeated.
We thank our lantern friends
for bringing him to justice.
Guards, round up the traitors
and take my brother to the tower.
You'll all be sorry.
I will be a Lantern, and then you'll pay!
You'll all pay!
You will be... nay.
You are a great leader.
You are my queen and sovereign,
and to you I offer all my loyalty.
Better late than never.
Our queen and sovereign!
Did you know all along
Ragnar had killed Dulac?
No, but he was a little too curious
about how you become a Green Lantern.
Then Kilowog remembered that
Ragnar was happy to have
two Green Lanterns on Betrassus.
Only someone who knew Dulac was dead
wouldn't include him in the count.
But how did you know
I had the ring?
Once I found out Dulac was dead,
I knew his ring would go
to the most worthy person, and like I said,
I'm a pretty good judge of character.
Thank you for everything.
Now that you're a Green
Lantern, will you join us in our
fight against the Red Lanterns?
I would love nothing more
than to go with you, but I'm
more than
a Green Lantern to my people.
- You're their queen.
- Yes, and duty to them comes first.
Unfortunately my
birthright is not a choice.
In fact, there are very few
things I can choose,
but this is one of them.
Good-bye, Hal Jordan.
www.tvsubtitles.net