Ba-bum.
[croaks]
[panting]
[horse neighs]
[soldiers yell]
[soldier yells]
[soldier screams]
[grunts]
[horse neighing]
[theme music playing]
[Callum] It feels like a
lifetime since we left home...
but it's only been a week.
We left because we found something
the world thought was destroyed...
the egg of the Dragon Prince!
Ezran and I decided to take a
dangerous journey across the world...
and carry this precious egg
home to its mother in Xadia.
Maybe then we can stop the war.
It's been an amazing adventure. I'm
even learning how to do magic!
Ow!
Though it hasn't
always been easy.
In fact, it's probably been the
hardest thing we've ever done.
[indistinct yelling]
But we haven't done it alone.
We've been traveling with
a new friend, Rayla,
who is a Moonshadow elf.
Nothing I believed
about elves is true.
Rayla is kind and good. She's
fearless, fast, strong...
[Rayla] And daring.
Oh, so daring!
Hey, have you just been
standing there the whole time?
[scoffs] Don't let me interrupt.
You were looking for another
good word to describe me, right?
Well, I consider
myself quite daring.
Quite?
Well, I'll be sure to tell my
stepdad how "quite daring" you are.
You're writing a letter...
to the king?
He'll be worried about us.
It'll mean a lot to him to know why
we left, and that we're doing okay.
In journeys, there are
always surprises.
[shrieking]
- Things never go as you plan.
- [roaring]
We dropped the egg, and
thought all was lost.
But something
incredible happened.
Now, instead of carrying an egg to
Xadia, we're taking care of someone new.
The most powerful creature
in the entire world.
[yips]
[exclaims]
[both laughing]
[growls]
[yips]
[Viren] Dragons! The Xadian
threat grows every day.
There have been sightings of
terrifying shadows in the clouds,
flying high above the towns
and cities of Katolis.
War dragons! We
must take action.
No, we should wait.
Xadia sent assassins and
they took the king's life.
And we must answer!
There hasn't even been the slightest
skirmish since then. Maybe that was it?
They've had their revenge, and
everything will just settle down now.
Settle down? Can't you
see the danger we're in?
[sighs] General Amaya reports
that elven forces are gathering
on the Xadian side
of the Breach.
We must be prepared to fight, and we
won't be able to fight them alone.
We must call for a
summit of the Pentarchy.
You're out of order, Lord Viren.
Only a king or queen
can call for a summit.
Frankly, I doubt the other rulers
will even look at a message
that doesn't bear
the king's seal.
But this is a crisis of
historic proportions.
Humanity could face extinction
if we don't work with the other
four kingdoms to do something!
None of that matters
while we have no king.
Therefore, our top and only priority
must be finding the princes.
Until we do, our hands are tied.
Come and get it, everyone.
Elves and humans over here,
and those with three or more legs
can sit there, with Phoe-Phoe!
You named her Phoe-Phoe?
She is a Moon Phoenix. Her name
is short for "Phoenix-Phoenix."
[Phoe-Phoe exclaims]
You have the best food up here.
What's your secret?
Well, my secret is...
is that it's all fake.
- What do you mean?
- You know, fake.
They're delicious illusions.
You're actually eating grubs.
[groans]
Oh, you must mean "grub." As in,
"Wow, this is some good grub."
No. Do you see what
Phoe-Phoe is eating?
- [Phoe-Phoe chomping]
- [Ezran] That bowl of worms?
[Lujanne] Yes, that's right.
Those are grubs!
[groans]
I don't care. [swallows]
This illusion pie is the
best I've ever had.
[Ezran retches]
Hey, everybody.
Well, you're in a good mood.
It does feel good to have
two working hands again.
- Uh... no offense, Ava.
- [barks]
I can slish and slash
with both swords again!
I can clap. [claps]
Do handstands...
I can even do that thing you do when you
finish a nice song and dance, you know?
[exclaims]
And how's everybody
else feeling?
- [Ezran] Amazing!
- Great!
- Fantastic!
- Good!
‘Cause it's time to go.
- [Callum] What?
- [Ellis] No!
- We can't!
- [Ezran] Why do we have to go?
We've only been here two days.
Danger's coming for
us, I know it.
The longer we stay here,
the higher the risk.
Hmm, she's right. The night
the Dragon Prince was born...
[sighs] I sensed
something amiss.
Those strange purple wisps...
Dark forces are pursuing you.
Nobody likes dark
forces, which is why...
- Making use of those two hands, huh?
- You bet.
Besides, we've got
precious cargo to deliver.
War is coming like the
world's never seen,
unless we get the wee
dragon home to his mum.
[Bait grunts]
But Zym, he's so little. He still
needs to learn how to fly.
[chuckles] You seem to have a special
connection to the dragonling.
Perhaps you could teach him?
Me? I could try.
And I was hoping to learn something
about Moon Magic while we're here.
Hmm. I could show
you some things.
Hey! I thought you
were on my side?
A few more days, Rayla,
that's all we're asking.
[sighs] Fine. One extra day.
One!
But I'm serious
about the danger.
I'll keep patrolling. Everyone
else, stay on your toes!
Except you. You work on
getting off those toes.
[yips sheepishly]
I can't believe I'm going to
learn magic from a real mage!
How do you know I'm real?
Uh...
Don't worry, I'm real.
This is the Moonhenge.
Thousands of years ago,
when Xadia was one land,
the ancient ancestors of Moonshadow
elves performed fantastic rituals here.
Historia Viventem.
[gasps]
[Lujanne] The legends say they
could use the power of the Nexus
to open a portal to another plane. A
shimmering world beyond life and death!
[Callum] But it's ruins now.
What happened?
The Moon Druids destroyed it themselves
when Xadia was divided in two.
They decided it was safer to
disable this magical place.
That's so sad.
Ever since then, there has always
been a guardian of the Nexus.
A mage, like myself, whose duty is to
prevent humans from discovering it.
What happens when humans do discover it?
Do you...
[exclaims] like, kill them?
[laughs] Nah, why kill them when you can
break their brains with insane illusions?
I've got some real mind melters. They
would completely freak your bean.
Interested?
I'll pass.
Okay, it's time to buckle
down and get to work.
[Bait chattering]
[Ezran] Flying is a natural
and beautiful thing.
Now, that doesn't mean
it's going to be easy.
[Bait grunts loudly]
You don't need to
keep doing that.
[Bait groans]
Ready, Zym? Wings out...
and flap!
[Zym grunts]
Come on! You have to
flap those wings.
[Zym groans]
Oh, no, are you okay?
[growls]
One more time. We'll
try it nice and slow.
[slowly] Flap...
[growls]
[chuckles] That's not flying, but
it's a very, very good start.
[scoffs]
[soldiers clamoring faintly]
"Oh, can't we stay a bit longer so
I can learn some magic tricks?"
And, "Oh, I wanna play around with
the wee dragon." [scoffs] Humans!
Only the noble elf cares about
keeping us all alive, apparently.
There's something out here, I know it.
Something bad.
[rustling]
[birds cawing]
[chittering]
[shrieking]
Ugh, you again. Save it
for someone who cares.
[whimpers]
And we're back. This time we're
here with a special guest.
She's mystical, magical, moon-powered
and she knows how to fly.
- [chirps]
- Please welcome Phoe-Phoe!
Ready, Phoe-Phoe? Show
him how it's done.
See? It's easy.
- [chittering]
- [Ezran] Yes! Yes, that's right!
Now, I'm going to show you
what flying feels like.
Can you feel it? Can you feel the
whoosh of the air beneath your wings?
[Zym chittering]
- He's doing it! He's amazing!
- Yes, yes! You can do this!
[gasps]
Ezran, you killed
the Dragon Prince!
Oh, no! I'm so stupid!
Oh, no, no, no!
[yips]
I'm so sorry, I wasn't trying to
hurt you, I promise. Are you okay?
[spits and chirps]
[groans]
[Lujanne] Though Primal
Energy is everywhere,
it may be weaker or stronger
at different times and places.
The ocean is strongest
at high tide,
sky is strongest in a storm,
and the moon is strongest...
When it's full!
Please don't
interrupt, but, yes.
And there is more. There are six special
places where the magic of Primal Energies
are most pure and powerful in this world.
Such a place is called a Nexus.
This is the Moon Nexus.
It reflects the moon perfectly.
When the moon is full, its light
completely fills the lake.
I love this. I love
learning about magic.
But I want you to teach
me to do some Moon Magic.
You know, maybe some
hands-on learning.
We get in there, you show me how to do a
moon beam, a moon ray, a moon... shine?
Humans can't do magic.
Um... but I did do magic.
Right, with a Primal Stone.
But then you smashed it, so now
you're just a standard human again.
Ah, but look on the bright side,
you've got those extra fingers.
The little ones, what do
you call them? Pinkos!
But I know other
humans who do magic.
We do not call that practice magic.
It's an atrocity.
This can't be. I thought
magic was my thing.
I was good at it.
It looks like you
could use some cake.
That's really a plate of worms.
[laughs] Ah, you're too smart
for old Lujanne's illusions!
How about some nice
old-fashioned iced-cream? Hmm?
[groans] Worms again.
[sighs]
So, he had a whole day of training.
Can he fly now?
No, not yet. I'm doing
my best, Rayla.
And so are you. I know you are.
Well, either way, we're
leaving tomorrow.
There's danger coming, I know it.
We have to get moving.
Then we should all
get some rest.
Nope, not for me.
I'm going out on patrol again.
One more perimeter check.
[exclaims]
[sighs]
- Tough day?
- You could say that.
Us too. Lots of jumping and
flapping, but no flying.
But we'll get it. No matter
how impossible it seems.
We believe in ourself, and
we're not giving up, are we?
Know what? Neither am I.
[crows cawing]
Crow Lord.
[clears throat] Crow Lord.
You! Sir! Crow Lord!
Oh! Sorry, I heard you
calling for the Crow Lord.
Uh, he's not here right now.
Then, who are you?
Oh! Well, I'm... I'm
the Crow Master.
It's sort of like... Assistant Crow Lord.
I just got promoted.
Congratulations. Are you
able to send the mail?
Sure! Sure, of course!
Oh, um... hmm. These... these
seem to bear the king's seal.
Yes.
Well, uh... yikes. Uh, the king is...
you know...
I can't send these.
Hmm. I understand your dilemma.
You were recently promoted, yes?
And you are trying
to do a good job?
Yes. Yes, exactly.
Right, well let me be
perfectly clear, Crow Master.
You will send these to the leaders of
the other four kingdoms immediately.
If you refuse, you will also be...
you know.
Um, now that I think about it,
I'm just gonna go ahead and
take care of these for you.
Mmm, I thought you might.
[crow cawing]
[Callum] You're wrong.
Callum! What are you doing here?
It's late.
- I'm never giving up.
- Callum...
Growing up, I was supposed to learn
horseback riding, sword fighting,
archery, battle tactics, but
I was so bad at everything.
But then, you didn't give up?
And you got good?
Well, no, I gave those up, but then
I tried magic, and it felt right.
It felt like I was finally
good at something.
I will learn magic.
It's who I am.
Hmm. I admire your
determination.
But learning magic
is not your destiny.
You can't do Primal Magic because you
weren't born connected to a Primal Source.
I don't get it. What do
you mean, "connected"?
In Xadia, all creatures are born
connected to a Primal Source.
They have a piece of it inside them.
We call that piece an arcanum.
Wait, what's an arcanum?
It's like... the secret of
the Primal, or its meaning.
- The secret of the Primal?
- Yes.
That secret becomes a spark.
The tiniest possible flicker
of a Primal Source inside you.
But enough to ignite the
world with its magic.
[wind whistles]
All right, so what is it?
What's the arcanum of the moon?
It's something I just... know.
It's not easily put into words.
- Well, try. Please.
- Very well.
The arcanum of the moon is about
understanding the relationship
between appearances and reality.
Most people believe that reality is
truth and appearances are deceiving.
But those of us who
know the moon arcanum
understand we can only truly
know the appearance itself.
You can never touch
the so-called reality
that lies just beyond the
reach of your own perception.
I'm confused.
I don't blame you. After
all, you're only human.
[ocarina playing faintly]
[sighs]
[ocarina continues]
Do it.