Ba-bum.
[croaks]
[panting]
[Runaan]
Previously on The Dragon Prince...
[Claudia] Well, maybe it's just a mirror.
[Viren sighs]
Of all the treasures, artifacts and relics
in the lair
of the Dragon King and Queen...
they kept this close to where they slept.
It must be important.
Oh, no.
Something's wrong with the egg.
I'm afraid it's dying.
Wait!
We learned about a miracle healer.
Someone who might be able to help the egg.
- And maybe your hand too!
- Really?
The only catch is,
the healer lives up there...
the Cursed Caldera.
There she is! She's an elf!
[mob clamoring]
Forget it.
No point following them up there.
They'll never make it out alive.
[theme music playing]
[roaring]
*The DRAGON PRINCE*
Season 01  Episode 08
Episode Title: "Cursed Caldera"
[Callum] I think we're safe.
[sarcastically] Safe? Sure.
So, how are we supposed to find
this miracle healer?
[Ellis] Come with me.
I'll help you find her.
- This way!
- [Ava barking]
So...
Hi, there.
But who are you exactly?
Me? I'm Ellis, and this is Ava.
- She's a wolf.
- [panting]
Wolf? Really? I thought bird.
Oh, I should have introduced you guys.
Ellis, this is Rayla,
who we originally met because, uh...
Well, she broke into our castle,
trying to kill Ezran.
But it doesn't matter.
We're past that now.
People meet in so many interesting ways!
Hmm. So how do we find this healer?
Truth is, I never found her. She found us.
We were hiding in a big, twisty,
hollow tree. Up near the rim.
Then we need to get to that tree.
Even if it takes all night.
Wait... that's all we have to go on?
A weird tree, where this miracle healer
showed up three years ago?
It's our only chance. Got a better idea?
As a matter of fact...
I do not.
I'll get us to that tree.
The healer will find us there,
and she'll save the egg!
And maybe she can help your hand.
Don't worry about my hand.
The egg is all that matters now.
- [Bait exclaims]
- [Ezran yelps]
[Ellis sighs] It's so beautiful.
It's like the sky is painted with honey.
Wow.
[chuckles] Too bad it also means
the nightmare's about to begin.
[stammers] What do you mean?
Oh, you know, enormous monsters,
indescribable terrors.
Stuff like that.
- Stuff like that.
- Yeah.
And the higher we go, the worse it'll get.
All right! Well, let's go.
No, no, no, wait.
We're going to need a plan.
How do you plan for indescribable terrors?
I feel like you need to be
able to describe them first.
Um... horrifying! Blood-curdling.
Creepy, but in a super extreme way
that feels like it's lighting
your soul on fire.
I think that helps.
Wait! Wait, wait, wait! I've got it.
Flash! Woof! Whoosh! Slish-slash!
Awesome!
Um, is he okay?
I think he's finally cracked
under the pressure.
No, that's the plan.
Ezran, you have the first job.
You hold Bait in the air so he can flash
and blind whatever monster it is.
Whack!
Wait... but then I'm not really
doing anything.
I'm just kind of holding up Bait.
You're support!
Every team needs a great support.
Ellis, you're next.
Ava will bark, and you'll ride around
in circles to confuse the monster.
- [barks]
- I don't know.
Do you think you can run around
and bark a lot, Ava?
- [barking]
- She's ready!
Then, me, I'll use my windbreath spell.
Whoosh!
[gasps] You're going to cast a spell?
It's just a simple rune thing I picked up.
No big deal.
Yeah, he's going to blow on the monster.
Ruffle its fur real good.
It's either that, or the half
of the lightning spell I know.
Specifically, the half that doesn't
shoot lightning out of my fingertips.
That monster won't know what hit it!
Oh, wait, it will. It'll be wind.
- [laughs]
- Rayla!
You're last. The finisher.
You'll take down the blinded, distracted,
windblown monster with your blades.
Slish-slash!
My hand is in pretty bad shape.
I'm only going to be able
to use one blade.
Okay, then you're just... slash!
No way. That won't work.
This is my slish hand.
Uh, really?
- No, not really, dummy.
- [Ezran laughs]
Wait. Callum, you may be a dummy,
but you're not a fool!
Am I supposed to feel flattered by this?
You said Claudia called you a fool
when you interrupted her lightning spell.
But I'll bet she was actually
trying to say "fulminis."
It's the draconic word for lightning.
So, if "fulminis" is the trigger word...
Then you know the spell for lightning!
Revised plan!
Flash! Woof! Zap! Slash!
[Rayla sighs]
If you don't eat, you'll die.
I am already dead.
You don't look dead.
Though that hand has seen better days.
I went out of my way to acquire
some rare Xadian fruits.
They're remarkable! So strange and exotic.
And these Xadian oranges... no seeds.
Incredible.
No?
I understand the whole
honor-in-not-eating thing,
but at least drink something.
Don't worry, it's berry juice.
[sighs]
I have a proposition.
I simply want you to take a look
at an object, and tell me what it does.
After that, I will unchain you
and you can walk out of here.
Decide.
You can be free,
or you can sit here and die.
I told you.
I am already dead.
[sighs]
Yes, wait a second.
I think I've heard about this.
It's a Moonshadow elf thing, right?
A philosophy of accepting you are
already dead...
so you will not fear death.
What a beautiful challenge
you've given me.
I must come up with something
you will fear...
more than death.
[Gren] Excuse me.
I would love to try some Xadian fruit.
Very good.
Well, it's dark,
but I think the scariest thing
I've seen so far is an angry cricket.
And he's more, like, mildly annoyed.
[cricket chirping]
Yeah, are you sure this is
the Cursed Caldera?
Or did we accidentally
wander up Humdrum Hill?
[all laughing]
Maybe we took a wrong turn
and wound up on Sleepy Slope?
- [all laughing]
- [all sighing]
I'll have to check my map,
but I'm fairly certain I recognize
the unmistakable topography of...
Mount Monotonous!
[dead silence]
[cricket chirping]
Anyway, it is a little odd
that nothing bad has happened yet.
- I see a huge, scary monster!
- [yelps]
But don't worry, it's dead.
Then why did you say it like that?
- Say it like what?
- [echoing]
[Ezran] I've never seen
anything like this.
- And look at those circles.
- [Callum] Don't touch it.
What a strange birthmark.
I don't think that's a birthmark.
It's a bite mark!
You're right.
Something's drained all its blood.
[Ellis] Guys!
[growling]
[Ellis] I see a huger, scarier monster!
[roaring]
The plan! Time for the plan! Ezran?
Okay. Okay. Where's Bait?
[cricket chirping]
Bait, come on, you're supposed to...
Ahh! Too soon! Too soon!
I can't see!
None of us can.
[Ava barking]
Okay, what about the rest of the plan?
I probably shouldn't do lightning
if I can't see, right?
Don't do the lightning!
Maybe a new plan?
Scatter! Run!
Is that to distract the monster?
[Callum] No, it's just to get away
and live!
[Rayla] Come with me.
Hop on. Ava will get us out of here.
[roaring]
You can climb trees right?
[grunting]
[Rayla] What do we do now?
I think that thing
is waiting for us down there.
We don't even have that much blood!
I know.
We would be a very unsatisfying snack.
[roaring]
We don't have a choice.
We just have to wait it out.
Ugh, I'm sorry my plan was a mess.
Nah, your plan was fine!
Our execution was a little off.
It came out more like,
"Argh! Oops! Help! Run!"
In a moment, I will remove this cover,
and you will tell me what you know.
Understood?
I've brought something that I hope
you will find motivating.
[coins jingling]
You're more foolish than I thought.
Don't you know only humans can be bribed?
Oh, this isn't a bribe.
[coins clattering]
It's a threat.
Go on. Take a closer look.
You're a monster.
You're mistaken. I'm a pragmatist.
It seems to be hanging in there.
Barely.
I'm so sorry I messed up the plan.
Ah, you should cut yourself a break.
Everyone messes up sometimes.
Or in my case, all the times.
What are you talking about?
Trust me, if the plan hadn't gotten
messed up when Bait flashed,
I'm sure it would have flopped
when it was my turn.
Are you kidding? From what I can tell,
you're awesome at everything.
Well, it's true.
I am pretty awesome at everything.
Right up until the moment
when it really matters.
And that's when I just... poof,
screw things up.
What do you mean?
- I don't know.
- [Bait grunts]
I hesitate, think too much,
get confused about the right thing to do.
And the next thing I know, I failed.
[monster growling]
I can't believe you're a mage.
I've never met an actual mage before.
You're not at all what I expected.
- What were you expecting?
- You know, taller, long robes, wrinklier.
- Super smart.
- [chuckling]
And maybe like a weird amulet
or something?
Well, I am in the market for
a weird amulet, if you know anybody.
[laughs] And you're so confident!
It's funny to hear someone say that.
I don't think of myself as confident.
Really? You should be,
having all that incredible power.
Maybe. The truth is, it's not me.
It's this.
All the magic, all the power,
all the confidence...
It's just because of this amazing thing.
A Primal Stone!
The morning I came to your castle,
my team was discovered by a human guard.
It was my job to chase him down
and stop him.
- But when I caught him...
- Please!
He looked up at me, and he was
so afraid.
And then I just let him go.
- I don't know why.
- Because you felt for him.
But he was a human... my enemy.
Yeah, but then you saw he was scared.
And you knew he was a person,
just like you.
That shouldn't have mattered.
I had a job to do.
Do you realize
I'm an assassin who's never killed anyone?
Uh, I think that's a good thing.
And by the way,
thanks for failing at your mission.
I like being alive.
I'm glad you're alive, Ezran.
Knowing you is definitely worth
losing a hand for.
That's the weirdest, nicest thing
anyone's ever said to me.
Well, who knows,
maybe this is my unlucky hand,
so when it falls off, my luck will change!
- [Ezran] That's horrible.
- Funny, though?
[Ezran] Funny and horrible.
[Ellis] That Primal Stone needs you
to do all that amazing stuff.
Without you, it's just a neat, glowy ball.
I guess so.
But without this, I'm nothing.
Just a guy who can draw and make
wry comments from time to time.
And they're not even that wry.
I'm not convinced.
I have a feeling you'd be pretty amazing
even without your magic ball.
Well, you seem pretty great, too.
- [Ava barks]
- And Ava's also great.
Is it okay if I pet her?
- [barks]
- Whoa!
Aww, you're such a fuzzy wuv-munkin!
[chuckles]
[Rayla yelling] Hey, guys?
I think that thing might be gone!
Haven't seen it or heard it in a while.
Seems like it moved on.
See ya, sucker!
Get it? Because it's a giant leech?
- So, more of a description than an insult?
- A little of both.
Mmm-hmm.
It's probably gone,
but let's not taunt it, okay?
There's a little thing called irony,
where just as you say one thing,
like you're really sure about it,
that's when the opposite happens.
Nah. Maybe that's how things
work in stories,
but in the real world...
- [screeches]
- [all screaming]
[Ezran screams]
[both scream]
[monster roars]
[Ezran screams]
[Ellis] That way!
Focus! We can do this! The plan!
Ez and Bait, you're up!
Flash!
[monster shrieking]
Yes! Ellis and Ava! Woof!
[Ava and Ellis barking]
Perfect! My turn for... zap!
Here goes nothing. Fulminis!
[monster shrieking]
Yeah! Yeah! Get zapped!
Oh, get zapped by the zap hand!
My zap hand! Yeah!
Can you be astounded later?
Right! Uh, Rayla, finishing move.
You got this! Slash!
[yelps]
- Rayla!
- No!
[monster shrieking]
[Rayla panting] That was too close.
If that thing was a split-second faster,
I would have been...
[groaning] Help! Help me!
Aspiro!
[Callum] Yes!
[chuckling] How 'bout that?
I knew "whoosh" should have been
part of the plan.
[footsteps approaching]
Enough brooding, elf.
My patience wears thin.
Tell me what you know about this relic
or I will seal your fate.
You have succeeded.
Oh, have I?
That mirror? You have found something
worse than death.
Then, tell me. What is it?
I will never help you.
Then you are of no use to me.
[chanting]
[Runaan grunting]
- [whistling]
- [chanting continues]
[Runaan screaming]
[chanting and screaming continue]
[screaming stops]
[gasps]
I always seem to capture
the same expression.
Defiance, giving way to absolute fear.
Look! Up there! That's the tree!
Yes, we're almost there!
We can do this, team.
We can make it to the rim!
We're going to find the healer
and save the egg.
[Ava whimpers]
- Oh, no.
- [Callum] What is it?
I have really bad news.
I don't know how to tell you.
Just say it.
Even if we make it to the rim,
it doesn't matter.
There is no miracle healer.
Sync corrections  by  srjanapala