Ba-bum.
[croaks]
[panting]
[Ezran] Previously on The Dragon Prince...
[Rayla] My parents aren't really dead.
But I wish they were.
When the humans came
and killed the Dragon King,
the Dragon Guard, my parents,
failed in their duty.
They ran away. I'm so ashamed.
[Viren] You are to return
with the terrible news
that the princes have perished.
What am I supposed to do
if we find them alive?
Oh...
you'll know the right thing to do.
[Janai grunting]
[guard] King Ezran, a visitor has arrived.
Prince Kasef of Neolandia,
eldest son of King Ahling.
My army stands outside your city gates,
at the ready.
What? No.
Katolis will not go to war.
We don't have to strike back.
We can choose peace.
If you can't take action against Xadia,
you have failed as a king.
[theme music playing]
[roaring]
[Rayla] I can't believe I'm almost home.
Somehow I'm happy and excited,
but also terrified.
- [adoraburr squeaking]
- You're just nervous.
Once they see you and widdle baby Zym,
I'm sure they'll help us.
There! Five in a row.
These fellas are so stackable.
When the other elves see me and Zym
is one thing.
But my new human friend
might not be so popular.
[adoraburrs grunting]
But you know who is going to be popular?
Your charming new elf friend.
Oh, no. Please, no.
Get ready to meet...
Elf Callum!
- [Zym yips]
- You know, I'm one of those forest elves,
with the...
with the antlers.
Oh, you're supposed to be
an Earthblood elf?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
The illusion's not complete.
[exhales]
[in thick accent] Oy, mate.
I'm an Earthblood elf.
All me best mates are trees.
"Mate" is Earthblood for "friend."
High four?
- Down low?
- No, we're done.
[Zym chirps]
[indistinct chatter]
[horses neighing]
[Bait grunts]
Prince Kasef, thank you for coming.
Why have you summoned me?
Have you had a change of heart?
No, but there's something
I want to tell you
that might change your heart.
Try me.
Some bad things have happened,
I know that.
My dad is gone. Your dad is badly hurt.
But there is something
you don't know about.
There is a hope.
This war started because Xadia thought
we destroyed the egg of the Dragon Prince.
But we didn't.
The Dragon Prince is alive!
- And he's really cute, by the way.
- [Bait grunts]
[groans]
And my brother is bringing him
back to the Dragon Queen,
with the help of an elf named Rayla.
When the Dragon Queen sees her baby,
her heart will change.
There could be peace again.
We just have to believe in it.
So, what do you think?
I think you're a little boy
putting his hopes in fairy tales.
[all gasp]
You don't need to throw me out.
We're finished here.
[door slams]
[Saleer] Prince Kasef.
May I have a word?
The human prisoner communicates
in some kind of hand language.
Sign language, actually.
And she probably uses
Katolis sign language specifically.
You see, many of the regions
use different...
Can you translate, or not?
Oh, um, yes, of course.
I was top of my class in linguistics.
Although I don't suppose a hand language
would technically be linguistics.
What would you call it?
Finguistics?
Welcome to Lux Aurea, human.
[yelps]
- [sighs] We're here. My home.
- Here?
Uh, no, I mean, I like it. It's... modest.
[sighs] It's hidden by an illusion.
To get in, I perform a special ritual
that lets me see through the spell.
It's like having a magic key.
Huh. So how do I get in, then?
You'll use my key.
Come on, it's easy. Just do what I do.
[Zym chirping]
[Callum exclaims]
This is it. The Silvergrove.
- Wow.
- Isn't it amazing?
I want to show you everything.
Oh, are you hungry?
I can take you where they make
the best Moonberry Surprise.
Ooh! Moonberry Surprise? What's in it?
I can't just tell you
what's in a Moonberry Surprise, Callum.
Oh, right.
I can show you where I grew up,
where I went to school, and...
- Rayla, something's wrong.
- What is it?
[Callum] They have no faces.
Oh, no. Oh, no.
What's happening? What's wrong with them?
It's not them, it's me.
I'm... a ghost!
[Aaravos] Get up.
Get up. You have visitors coming.
You're going to need to look presentable.
[Claudia sighs]
[Viren] My children.
I'm so glad to see you safe.
What happened, Dad? Why are you down here?
While I tried to unite the five kingdoms
against Xadia,
the Council was more concerned
that I broke a few rules along the way.
But none of that matters.
The egg, did you get it?
[stammers] It's not an egg anymore.
It's hatched.
It hatched?
That dragon will become
the most powerful creature in the world,
and you've let it fall back
into Xadia's hands?
But, Dad, Soren could've died.
[Viren] That doesn't matter!
Dad?
[sighs]
I do not mean to be cruel.
But we must be ready to sacrifice.
Even the things we love.
I would have asked you to choose the egg
over my life, if it came to it.
Do you understand?
Everything I do,
and everything I ask of you,
is for the future of humanity.
Is that why you told Soren
to kill the princes?
- Um, hello? Anyone?
- [Zym whimpers]
It's no use.
They can't see me, and they can't see you
or Zym because you came in with me.
I don't get it.
They made me a ghost.
It's like being magically banished.
It's what happened to my parents
when they abandoned the Dragon Guard.
And now it's happened to me.
But you didn't run away from anything.
They just don't know what happened.
Yeah. Yeah, it has to be a mistake.
Come on.
There's one person who will understand.
I'm going to uncuff you now
so you can speak.
Don't do anything stupid.
What were your human soldiers
doing on the Xadian side of the border?
What are the humans planning?
[sighs] I'm losing my patience.
Say something!
[interpreter] Um... oh, my.
Well? What did she say?
If my interpretation is correct,
and it is...
she suggested an unusual way in which
your body might accommodate your sword.
[clears throat]
I suppose you think that's funny.
That's a common sign for "yes."
We'll see if you have the same attitude
with our Queen.
[Rayla] Remember Runaan,
the leader of the assassins?
Uh, I think so.
Tall, pointy, aimed a bow at me?
Mmm-hmm. He seemed nice.
When my parents joined the Dragon Guard,
I went to live with Runaan
and his husband, Ethari.
They were my parents' best friends,
and they took care of me for years.
- We're going to meet Ethari.
- Will he be able to see you?
He wouldn't have done the spell.
He always had faith in me.
[exhales]
Ethari! It's me. I'm so glad you're here.
There's been a mistake.
They made me a ghost.
But you have to tell them,
I didn't run away.
Ethari?
[gasps]
Your Radiance.
We captured this human general
at our border.
But she refuses to cooperate
with my interrogation.
Dispose of her.
No! Ethari, not you, too.
[Zym whimpers]
This isn't fair. There has to be a way
to get his attention.
Hey! Ethari, was it?
You didn't even give Rayla a chance
to explain herself.
Callum, it's no use.
Listen to me! Rayla doesn't deserve this.
I think it worked.
The reflection! He can see me.
Yeah. I'm here.
Surprised to see my face?
- Can he hear you?
- No.
But he can see how I feel.
[Ethari] Rayla.
Before you left, I told Runaan
that you were too goodhearted
for the work of an assassin.
So I know you did not betray them
out of malice.
But that doesn't matter.
They're gone.
He's gone. Because you abandoned them.
[Claudia] Answer me, Dad.
Why did you tell Soren
to kill the princes?
Careful. If you tell the truth,
you will lose her.
You will need her soon.
[laughs]
Oh, is that what you thought, Soren?
Claudia, did you really think
I would ask him to do such a thing?
Surely you know your brother is...
um, easily confused.
Wait, I know I'm not the smartest,
but I know what you said.
Oh, really? What do you remember?
You told me to return with the news
that the princes died.
You said, "Accidents happen all the time."
Soren, I was preparing you for the worst.
I knew tragedy might have
already befallen them...
No! You said that I'd know to do
the right thing.
Soren.
I said "do the right thing,"
and somehow you heard "kill the princes."
Oh... this is disappointing, son.
Even for you.
Claudia, you believe me, right?
Oh, Sor-bear.
I believe you thought you heard it,
but you obviously made a mistake.
We're just really lucky you messed up
the mission you thought you had, huh?
[chuckles] Wow.
High Mage, I've brought someone
who wishes to speak with you.
I understand now. They didn't make it.
None of them. Only me.
How do you know that?
This.
When assassins are sent
on a dangerous mission,
Ethari enchants one of these flowers
for each of them.
As long as the assassin lives
and breathes, their flower floats.
My heart goes out with this one.
Don't worry.
I promise I will return your heart to you.
[Callum] So when all the others sank,
and yours didn't...
[Rayla] They thought I ran away.
Just like my parents.
But you didn't run.
They have it all wrong.
- Does it matter?
- [Zym chirps]
[chitters]
[Rayla gasps]
If she's not useful, get rid of her.
She's worthless.
She's not worthless.
This may be a human,
but she fought bravely,
and she treated me, her enemy,
with warrior's honor.
Should we not do the same?
Oh, my sweet little sister.
If you truly believe
this one is so special,
we'll let the Light decide her fate.
[gasps]
No, you have to look.
You have to look.
If you want to live,
you have to look into the light!
[panting]
Hmm. A human with a pure heart.
How original.
[scoffs] Just take her.
[Janai] Thank you, sister.
[Sunfire Queen] Enjoy your pet.
Take my hand.
[exhales] There you are.
You know, I was never as strong
as the others.
This will only break the spell
for a moment,
but I couldn't bear to let you leave
without seeing you one last time.
But I don't understand, Rayla.
How could you abandon them?
I failed them.
It was my fault we were discovered,
but I didn't run away.
Ethari, we found something.
Callum, show him.
Oh, uh...
[in thick accent]
I'm Rayla's Earthblood elf friend.
Trees to meet you.
- Trees to meet you, too.
- Don't humor him.
- [Zym chirps]
- We found the Dragon Prince.
The egg wasn't destroyed.
And I knew that if we could get him home
to his mother, there could be peace.
It's a miracle. I can't believe it.
But, Rayla, you need to know.
The Dragon Queen is dying.
Since the death of her mate,
she's fallen very ill.
We have to get to her. It's the only way.
[whistles]
You can ride faster than you can walk.
[beast sniffing]
[Callum exclaims]
- [Zym chitters]
- [Callum grunts]
I'll send a message to the Dragon Queen.
If she knows her little one still lives,
perhaps she'll hold on.
[Callum grunting]
[Zym chirps]
Ethari, can I ever come home again?
I don't know.
It's a real moon opal.
When I gave its match to Runaan,
I told him,
"My love will be with you
even when the moon is not."
Goodbye, Rayla.
[Ethari] Runaan,
the last time I made you one of these,
it carried a message of death.
But this arrow will carry
a message of life.
Regina Draconis!
[bird screeching]