Ba-bum.
[croaks]
[panting]
[Rayla] Previously on The Dragon Prince...
A letter?
You'll understand in time.
I want you to break the seal when...
Well, you'll know when.
[gasps]
What is this place?
Wait.
Callum, I need to tell you something.
I know what happened.
He's gone.
Oh, no.
[theme music playing]
[roaring]
[Rayla] Callum, I'm sorry.
I tried to tell you the king was dead.
My stepdad.
He was more than just the king to me.
Your stepdad. I know.
I really tried,
but I could never find the right way.
And whenever I tried, I messed it up,
and the next time was harder, until...
Rayla, just stop.
I can't talk about this right now.
All I can think about is
how I'm going to tell Ezran
our father is gone.
I'm sorry, Callum.
I'm so, so sorry.
[sighs]
[yawns]
- [sighs]
- [footsteps approach]
So, have fun on your little date?
[sniffling and sobbing]
What happened?
What did he do to you?
Nothing happened.
Callum would never hurt me.
Oh.
Then how come you're all weep-ridden?
[scoffs] That is not an emotion, Soren.
My point is, are you okay?
Yeah. I'm gonna be fine.
[sighs] Because you're my sister,
as you know.
I'm always here for you...
to punch someone, or whatever you need.
- I know.
- Good.
We still have to bring the princes
back with us.
Whatever it takes, whatever happens.
I need to know that all this
won't get in the way
of doing what we came here to do.
It won't. I can do it.
Callum?
Morning, Ez.
- I had another weird dream.
- [Bait croaks]
I was running from that giant hippo.
The one made of taffy, remember?
- Uh, I think so?
- [Zym chitters]
Only this time,
there was someone riding on his back.
It was the baker.
The one who didn't like me.
He'd like you
if you stopped stealing his jelly tarts.
He said I was wanted
for crimes against dessert.
And to make the hippo chase me,
the baker told him I was jelly-filled.
- Ez...
- I was a pastry fugitive, Callum.
It was terrible.
And the worst part was he was right.
I was delicious.
Let's go for a walk.
So, Ezran,
I wanted to talk to you about...
life, and growing up
and how sometimes there are changes
you don't expect.
Is this the talk about sandwiches?
No. No, no, no. No, not that.
No, definitely not that.
Uh... [clears throat] Mmm.
Ezran, for a long time,
I treated you like a little kid.
And that wasn't fair.
You've grown up so much,
and I'm really proud of you.
Oh. Yeah.
[Callum] But when you grow up,
sometimes you have to face things
you're not ready for.
[Ezran] I know.
You know?
I know everyone's counting on me
to teach Zym how to fly.
- But that's just the start.
- [sighs]
Someone's gonna have to teach him
all the things he's supposed to do.
Everything he's supposed to be.
And he's meant to learn it all
from a big, strong King of the Dragons.
[Phoe-Phoe screeching]
But he doesn't have that.
All he's got is me.
Hey, don't be so hard on yourself, Ez.
I know it'll be tough,
but no matter what, you've got us.
Me and Rayla, probably Bait.
We're all here for you.
Thanks, Callum. That means a lot.
But I really wish Dad was here.
I keep wondering what he would do.
What he would say to Zym.
When I was little
and I wasn't listening to him,
Dad would say, "Ezran, you're a handful."
So, I tried to do that with Zym.
"Azymondias, you're a handful."
But he doesn't understand.
He doesn't even have hands.
I guess I just miss Dad.
He'd know what to do, you know?
Callum, what's wrong?
Nothing, Ez. I just really miss him, too.
I couldn't do it.
I couldn't tell him.
Callum...
And I understand why you couldn't tell me.
When you care about someone,
it's hard to hurt them.
Even when
what you're telling them is the truth.
I still should've told you.
You had the right to know.
I think maybe I did know.
Deep down, I knew.
I just hoped, if I didn't think about it,
maybe somehow, it wouldn't be true.
But he's gone. He's really gone.
[sobbing]
[Viren snoring]
The fire.
Huh.
[gasps]
No, no, no!
[exhales and groans]
Who are you?
When Soren said that Dad wanted us home,
- you knew he was lying.
- Yeah.
Unless, maybe Soren
was also trying to protect our feelings.
Oh, right. He definitely seems like
a thoughtful, sensitive,
feelings-y, protect-y kind of guy.
Yeah, you're right,
that's not really his style.
We don't have a choice anymore.
We have to leave.
And we have to do it now.
Get as far away from them as we can
before they even realize we're gone.
Whoa, wait a minute.
They're still my friends.
But they lied to you.
Soren lied to me.
Claudia told me the truth.
- We can't just leave.
- [Claudia] Leave?
Yeah. I'm sorry, but we've decided.
We're leaving today.
This mission,
taking the Dragon Prince back to Xadia,
it's the most important thing
we'll ever do.
- We can't go home with you.
- Oh.
Are you sure? I mean,
your dad is gonna be really disappointed.
- Soren, what is wrong with you?
- I'm just trying to...
Don't! Stop it, Soren.
Ugh, fine. Do what you want.
[yelping]
Stupid moths.
I'm sorry about him.
But before you go, Callum,
I have something I need to give you.
In private.
Oh. Uh, all right.
So, closed door? Open door?
What's... What do you...
Uh, closed is fine.
Closed. Good. Okay.
I have something for you.
Something you dropped.
That's my letter. From him.
You didn't open it?
Why would I do that?
It's for you.
Though, I mean, for the record,
I could have opened it
and pretty easily
re-sealed it with magic.
Wait, did you?
Did I? We may never know.
But, no. No.
So, are you going to open it?
No. I don't think I'm ready yet.
But thank you, Claudia.
You're welcome.
So, I guess this is goodbye.
Zym, come on.
You loved it in there as an egg.
Rayla, look.
[laughs]
He can't fly yet,
but he should be safe in...
- [Zym growls]
- Hey, how'd you...
- Bait, you're not helping.
- [croaks]
[Rayla laughing]
Let me guess. Once I was gone,
she tried to manipulate you
and convince you to go back home again.
No, she didn't.
Actually, Claudia really understands
how important it is
to get Zym back to Xadia.
Oh. That's surprising.
- [Callum] Mmm-hmm.
- But good.
Yeah. In fact, she understands it so well
that she and Soren want to come with us.
What? That is the worst possible plan.
How? How is it bad?
They're offering to help.
Or it's a trap.
[sighs]
[sighs] Callum, I know you trust them.
But if we let them come with us,
by the time we know the truth,
it'll be too late.
Do you understand? We'll lose everything.
So, then what are we supposed to do?
How can we figure out
if it's help or a trap?
- [loud banging]
- Can I help you?
I'm sorry.
Were you meditating or something?
I was.
So, you're done. Good.
We're leaving. And the other humans,
they're coming with us.
Hmm. And you're unhappy with that.
Callum trusts them,
but I know they're hiding something.
You see, to every truth,
there is a dark, shadowed side.
- Consider the half moon...
- You already did this.
Oh. Have I? Hmm.
Well, that's really all I've got.
Unless you're in need of a spooky monster
or fake food. Hmm?
Actually, there is something
you can do for me.
[Soren] Oh, yeah.
[grunting]
Where are Callum and Ezran?
Oh, they'll be here soon.
Ezran's still packing up his dragon.
It has been a pleasure
to have you all here.
I truly have enjoyed
you all sneaking past my defenses
and desecrating this sacred place
these past few days.
It will be lonely. Quiet...
but lonely without you.
I'll miss you so much.
- Ellis, you will always be welcome here.
- [barking]
[laughs] And you, too, little one.
You don't need the illusion any longer,
but I hope it serves as a reminder
that someone
is always looking out for you.
Okay, everyone's here now.
We can all hit the road.
All right. Time to go to the magical land
and do whatever.
So, you're ready to do this
the Soren way, right?
Yes, there's no other way.
Good. Then, when it's time to strike,
I'll give the signal.
What's the signal?
The signal is me attacking the elf.
[Claudia groans]
It's going to be a long journey.
Let me just go around this bush-corner
and see if I can find
some berries or something.
[Rayla grunts]
- Oh, no. It's a trap.
- Yup.
But why? I thought we were friends.
Sorry, but no.
I'm just a nice guy
and people get the wrong idea sometimes.
[sighs] You don't speak sarcasm so good,
do you?
No, I do not.
[yells]
[chanting indistinctly]
- [Ava whimpers and barks]
- Wait, Ava! Come back.
[snakes hissing]
[Zym whimpering]
I'm sorry, little guy.
You have to come with me.
[Viren gasps]
You can't see me.
On your side...
it's just an ordinary mirror.
[Soren and Rayla grunting]
What? You're running away?
Hey! Do either of the tiny princes
want to fight?
This elf is a coward.
I'm sorry. I know this feels
like a betrayal, but I can't let you go.
I have to do what's right.
I have to take you back home.
Please don't give me
the silent treatment, Callum.
Say something! Say you hate me.
Say anything.
[gasps]
Soren, something's wrong!
This is a trick!
A trick? Us? No.
- Sarcasm!
- Right.
What did you do, elf?
I can't wait for the look
on your big, stupid face
when you see this.
- Ellis, show them.
- [Ava barks]
Here's your moment, Ava.
Moonstone collar trick.
- They're illusions.
- [Soren] What?
You're saying they're not real?
- That's what "illusions" means, Soren.
- [Ellis laughing]
[both howling]
[Soren grunts]
- Not even close! [laughs mockingly]
- [grunts]
[panting] Where are the real princes?
[Ava barks]
[Ezran whooping]
- [Soren] Claudia, they're getting away.
- [Rayla grunts]
No, they're not.
[chanting indistinctly]
[all screaming]
[Phoe-Phoe screeching]
Claudia, please! Don't do this.
[Bait croaks]
- [screams]
- Stop! Let them go.
What are you doing?
Protecting them from you! [grunts]
Big mistake, chain man.
[Phoe-Phoe screeches]
- [Ava barking]
- [Ellis] Goodbye! I'll miss you guys.
Don't you forget about me.
Don't, don't, don't, don't.
We got 'em! I was right.
Yeah, you were right.
I wish I wasn't. I'm sorry.
[gasps]
[grunts]
You know
you're going to pay for this, traitor.
Traitor? General Amaya sent me
to protect the princes of Katolis,
and you just tried to kidnap them.
Everyone who votes "Corvus is a traitor"
raise their hand.
Two against one, traitor.
[muffled grunting]
What are we gonna do?
We betrayed our friends,
and it was all for nothing.
It wasn't for nothing. Look.
[gasps] The dragon!
We still have the dragon.
Come on out, you little...
[grunting] I hate the Moon. Ugh!
It's okay, Zym.
It's safe to come out now.
[growls softly]
[chitters]
[Ezran] We're up in the sky.
[squeals]
Wanna see how flying feels?
Come on, spread your wings.
[squeals]
[laughing]
[chittering]
[Ezran cheering]
Yeah!
[laughing]