Ba-bum.
[croaks]
[panting]
[man] Previously on The Dragon Prince...
Whatever happens, whatever accidents
or tragedies may occur...
above all else,
you must return with that egg!
I understand.
Humans weren't born with magic.
We were born with nothing.
But we still found a way
to do amazing things.
That's what dark magic
is really all about.
I'm sorry. It's just not for me.
Why should I trust you?
Hey, what was that? A shadow?
There's something up there.
[theme music playing]
[roaring]
- [device humming]
- [croaks inquisitively]
What do you think this thing is, anyway?
[snorts]
He said it was a key, but a key to what?
You practicing magic or are you losing
to Bait at a game of rolly-cubes?
Magic.
I think I'm getting close.
There's so much swirling around
in my head,
but I need a way to bring it all together.
- Like some kind of breakthrough?
- Yeah.
[Bait snorts]
What about you? You were born
with the Moon Arcanum.
Uh, I suppose so?
So when you do cool moon powers,
you're connecting to the moon, right?
What does that feel like?
Uh, I don't really think about it.
I just stand in the light
of the full moon,
and then there's a feeling like...
[mimics whooshing]
And then there's a sort of... ting!
And then...
[exclaims] Moonshadow powers!
[voice echoing]
Does that help?
No, not at all. But I enjoyed it.
Once we're in town, we can ditch Corvus
in jail or something
and be done with him.
We're so far off
Callum and Ezran's trail now.
Do you think we can catch up with them?
Of course we can! We promised Dad.
You know, I could help you track them,
if you untied me.
[laughing] No, no, no, no.
If I untie you,
you're just gonna try and escape.
Again.
No, not this time.
This time will be different. I promise.
- Huh.
- Pfft, no!
Hey, hey!
Fool me once, shame on you.
Fool me twice, shame on me.
Fool me three times, back to you again.
That's not how it goes.
Shame on you.
[grunts]
I have to be a mage again.
We saw a dragon in the clouds yesterday.
Things will only get tougher
once we get into Xadia.
And crossing the border?
That's going to be crazy dangerous.
Eh, well...
maybe not.
There's a river of lava!
One does not simply walk into Xadia.
Actually, one does simply walk into Xadia.
There's a secret path, the Moonstone Path.
It'll be safe and easy, even for you,
magic or no magic.
Come get some rest.
[sighs] You're right.
Let's go back to sleep.
[croaking nervously]
[horse neighing]
Excuse me. Excuse me.
We're looking for a town jail?
We've got a horrible traitor to lock up
for, uh, traitorous words and deeds.
Standard traitor stuff.
[crowd muttering]
Excuse me? Crownguard here.
Oh, something's weird.
I know! No one's listening to me.
What?
There! It's back.
[crowd exclaiming]
- Is that...
- A dragon?
[crowd exclaiming]
[soldier] Yeah, it's the third night
in a row it's flown over us.
And you haven't shot it down yet?
What are those ballistas for?
Well, it hasn't attacked us.
So? It's the enemy.
I'm taking command here.
Crownguard, I might have mentioned.
Hold on! The dragon isn't attacking.
It's just trying to intimidate us.
[scoffs] Well, then,
I'll just have to show it
that humans won't be intimidated.
[roaring]
Soren, please. Don't start a fight
you can't finish.
[roaring]
Ha! See? Scared it off.
Dragon problem solved.
[dragon roaring]
[roaring]
Oh, no. I know that sound.
That's not a good sound.
[Zym yips]
[whimpers]
Wait, we don't know
if it's safe out there.
Bait, stay with Zym.
[dragon roaring]
Get down!
What's it doing here?
Why is it attacking that town?
Uh, I don't know.
[townsfolk screaming]
Don't just stand there!
Get on those ballistas!
It's circling back. Get ready to fire.
Fire!
Soren!
What are you... [yells]
I don't understand.
These people need help.
Get as many as you can to safety.
Don't get yourself killed.
I think I really messed up
this time, Clauds.
I... I don't know how to stop it.
Don't say that yet. I have an idea.
It's the eye of a gryphon.
With this, I can enchant a ballista bolt
to never miss its target, no matter what.
Ugh!
So you just carry a gryphon eyeball
around with you?
Who does that?
Oh, how about, "Thank you for carrying
a gryphon's eye with you, Claudia.
You're so prepared. You're the best."
Thank you, Claudia.
- You're the best!
- [chuckles]
[roaring]
[chanting]
[grunts]
[roars]
[exclaims]
[groaning]
They hit it!
Get down!
[Callum] Ezran!
Is it dead?
[groaning softly]
[gasps]
How dare you?
You used King Harrow's seal
to summon the Pentarchy
and then you lied to them.
You called yourself the Regent of Katolis.
You committed treason, Viren,
and for what?
[sighs] For nothing.
You'll be removed
from the Council for this,
and you'll be lucky if that's all.
[Ezran] You're in pain.
Don't worry. We can help you.
[breathing heavily]
There! Beneath her wing.
[dragon groaning softly]
[Rayla] Come on. Help me.
[all grunting]
[grunts]
[horse neighing]
What are you doing?
The humans are coming.
We have to protect her.
We can't fight them, Rayla.
I can't just leave her.
Callum's right.
And we have to get back to Zym.
We did what we could.
Come on.
I always thought it'd be you
who took down a dragon, not me.
Huh?
I mean, wasn't this
one of your life goals?
Slaying a dragon? [chuckles]
Yes.
Huh. It's funny,
because I don't really care about it.
But... [chuckles]
I think it's dead,
but we can't be too sure.
Secure the dragon!
Zym! Zym, are you okay?
[whimpering]
[snorting]
[Zym whimpering]
I should have done something.
Rayla, you're always the one
who reminds us that the only thing
that matters is getting Zym back to Xadia.
Why are you hesitating now?
I'm not hesitating. This is different.
Every fiber in my body
is telling me this is wrong.
That dragon is defenseless
and I just left her there.
Welcome back!
I hope you had a pleasant trip.
How can you possibly remain so cheerful
in your dire circumstances?
Well, I think about it like this,
why see myself as chained down,
when I can be chained up?
[metal clanging]
I admire your tenacity.
[breathes deeply]
I have nothing left to lose.
[Claudia] There's so many things
we can do with a dragon.
There's even a chapter about spells
that use dragon snot.
It's some powerful goo.
We don't have the Dragon Prince,
but do you think if we brought this dragon
home, Dad would...
It's something, but...
it does weigh, I don't know,
about a million tons?
How are we gonna move it?
In pieces.
[Callum] I don't get it, Rayla.
Why are you so worried about a dragon
that just set fire to a town?
I've been thinking about something
someone once told me.
About how when one person hurts another,
then that person hurts them back,
it becomes a cycle that never ends.
Who told you that?
- You did.
- Oh.
But, Callum, to break that cycle,
someone has to take a stand
when no one else will.
You're right.
If we're really going to change things,
we can't just watch while humans and Xadia
keep hurting each other.
But how do I take a stand?
Believe me, I want to go
down there with you,
and be the heroes who stop
all the fighting and save the day,
but I can't do that.
I can't do anything!
It's okay, Callum.
I'm not asking you to come with me.
Protecting that dragon doesn't just feel
like the right thing to do,
it feels like the right thing
for me to do.
It's where I'm meant to be.
I'm going back down there.
If I don't come back,
you and Ezran can get Zym to Xadia.
I believe in you.
Wait, Rayla!
[breathes deeply]
It doesn't matter what happens to me.
Live or die, this dragon goes home.
Ugh, this guy again. Of course.
A dead dragon and a dead elf
all in one day.
Everything's coming up Soren.
[grunts]
[exclaims]
[both grunting]
- [Zym yips]
- [Ezran laughs]
What are you doing?
I'm just drawing, Ezran.
You seem upset.
Yep. I draw when I'm upset.
Argh!
Maybe there is something I can do.
Ezran, you have to stay here.
Protect Bait and Zym.
- [Zym exclaims]
- Hey!
- [Zym whimpers]
- Don't worry, Zym.
We're gonna have fun while they're gone.
Why don't we play a game?
[squawks]
[Rayla groans]
[groans faintly]
[Soren] Ooh, yeah. The thing about chains?
They're made of metal. Hard to cut.
[panting]
I'm not backing down.
Try not to kill her, Soren.
She can lead us to Ezran and Callum.
[Callum] She doesn't have to.
I'm right here.
[exclaims] Callum! You're safe!
What are you doing?
Your kind of magic.
You don't want to do this, Callum.
It's really dangerous
unless someone shows you how.
You already did.
[chanting]
[hissing]
[soldiers gasping]
[soldiers yelling]
Get up. You're free.
[Soren] Congratulations!
That was impressive. Really.
You did everything you could
to save a monster
that torched a town of innocent people.
But it didn't even matter.
You freed a dead dragon.
[growling softly]
[roaring]
Still bad at this, buddy.
[croaks]
Now, where's Zym?
Oh, no. I'm so stupid.
- Hide and seek was a really bad idea.
- [croaks]
[roaring]
- [grunts]
- We have to get out of here!
- [dragon roaring]
- [soldiers screaming]
[Soren shouting]
[roaring]
[Soren exclaims]
[groans]
- [Zym whimpers]
- [Ezran] Zym!
[whimpering]
[roaring]
The little dragon's coming with me.
[chanting]
[Soren] Claudia!
Help me.
Soren!
I'm here.
Come on, get up.
We have to get you some help.
I... I can't move, Claudia.
I can't move!
I'm ready.
[exclaims]
[breathing heavily]
[grunts]
Speak.
[stammering]
- I...
- [man] Speak, so I may hear you.
[gasps]
Who... who are you?
Ah...
How long I have waited to hear
the sound of another voice.
How may I serve you?