Ba-bum.
[croaks]
[panting]
[Viren] Previously on The Dragon Prince...
So, the most important things,
I've written down.
A letter?
Queen Aanya, would you allow me
to share a story with you?
Nine years ago, my oldest friend,
Prince Harrow,
became the king of Katolis.
But one day, two visitors came
from a faraway place, another kingdom.
[Aanya] They were my parents.
This winter, we will run out of food,
and a hundred thousand people will die.
I can use the heart of the titan
in a powerful spell
that will warm the land,
and allow us
to magically grow an incredible bounty.
[roaring]
[theme music playing]
[sighs]
[Harrow] Dear Callum...
Over the years,
there have been moments
when I let there be a distance between us.
Because I'm your stepfather,
I was trying to give you
the space I thought you needed
to love your real father,
even though he passed away.
Now, I wonder
if I should have held you closer.
I wonder if showing you
how much I loved you
would have been okay,
and would not have disrespected
your relationship with him.
Callum, I know I'm not your birth father.
But in my eyes and in my heart,
you are my son.
I see myself in you. I'm proud of you.
And I love you unconditionally.
[exhales deeply]
Oh, this isn't easy.
[croaks and whimpers]
Wait. You can't read, can you?
[snorts]
[Harrow] As I write this,
the sun is setting
while Moonshadow assassins
prepare to end my life.
A few months ago,
I took my revenge on Xadia.
Tonight, it is their turn.
I may not have long.
So I'm forced to ask myself...
what can I pass on to my sons
in the short time I have left?
In this letter, I will share with you
a lie, a wish, and a secret.
[Viren] Where is he?
[stammering] Sorry, sorry.
[chuckles] I'm not used to hearing
so much story all at once.
I just needed a quick trip
to the little king's room. [chuckles]
May I continue?
I am ready to hear more, Lord Viren.
Though I know how this story ends,
it warms my heart to hear about my parents
from someone who was there.
Yes. You must know as well as anyone
that while this appears to be
a story of epic battles
and legendary creatures,
it is ultimately a story of sacrifice
and love.
[horse whinnies]
[shouting]
[roaring]
[soldiers groaning]
[soldiers screaming]
[gasps]
[roars]
[soldier] Fire!
Aim for the cracks
between the rocky plates!
We can chain it down!
[roaring]
[sizzling]
[gasps]
[Harrow] Take aim at the center.
Fire right where we cracked into it.
[roaring]
[screaming]
Now what?
Push!
Over the edge!
[roaring]
[roars]
[Sarai screaming]
[grunts]
[roars]
[horse neighing]
[sighs]
The legend was true.
The heart of the titan
radiates with life and magic.
So, do you think you can...
Yes. We can save them all.
[all cheering]
Our people, they'll be fed.
Amaya, you did it!
Sister?
Amaya!
Time is short.
There's barely an hour until sunrise.
We can't risk the wrath
of the Dragon King.
We must take the heart and hurry back.
Yes, of course. We'll move as fast we can.
[Viren sighs]
The wounded must be left behind.
We can't afford to slow down.
"You don't need to whisper, Viren.
I'm deaf.
It'll be okay.
Once I rest a bit,
I can make it back by myself."
We won't leave you here alone.
I'll stay with Amaya.
We'll make it home together.
Everyone else should take the heart back.
They agree. Time is of the essence.
- No.
- But Harrow, they just said...
We leave no one behind.
We do not leave our wounded.
You wouldn't do this if it...
if it wasn't your wife's sister.
I've made my decision and it is final.
[Harrow] When I am gone,
your brother Ezran will become king,
and you will be his partner, his defender,
and his closest adviser.
Soon you will both face a lie.
The great lie of history.
Advisers and scholars will tell you
that history is a narrative of strength.
They will recount stories of the rise
and fall of nations and empires.
They will be stories of armies, battles,
and decisive victories.
But this isn't true strength.
It's merely power.
I now believe true strength is found
in vulnerability...
in forgiveness, in love.
[boys laughing]
[Harrow] There is a beautiful
upside-down truth,
which is that these moments
of purest strength
appear as weakness
to those who don't know better.
For a long time, I didn't know better.
I ask you and your brother to reject
history as a narrative of strength,
and instead have faith
that it can be a narrative of love.
[Villads] So, Rayla...
[chuckles] That's an unusual name,
isn't it?
Oh! [laughs nervously]
Yeah, uh, my human parents
had an unusual taste in names...
Villads with a silent D.
Hmm, 'tis fair. [chuckles]
So, what do you do for a living?
I'm an assassin.
[laughing]
Oh! You're not joking.
Well, I'm supposed to be an assassin,
but I've never actually,
you know, killed anyone.
Oh. Well, maybe someday.
Never give up on your dreams.
Thanks for the encouragement.
But the truth is, I'm not sure
being an assassin is my dream after all.
Oh! So, then... what is your dream?
Ugh, I wish I knew.
[Viren] With the heavy heart of the titan,
and the additional burden
of carrying the wounded,
our pace back to the Breach
was slower than I'd wished.
Dawn came.
As the sun rose on the horizon,
I could feel its heat on my neck,
like a hot doom I knew was coming for us.
But we pushed forward,
hoping to escape the inevitable
consequence of our trespass.
There's the entrance.
We've almost made it!
- Faster! All our strength now!
- [horses neighing]
[Viren] Suddenly, the heat disappeared.
There was a chill
as a shadow covered the sun.
But instead of relief,
I felt a cold dread.
[thunder rumbling]
[Harrow] Thunder.
[horse whinnies]
[Viren] The storm had come.
[screeching]
[laughing]
[gags]
I'm a crazy old man,
but let me share some wisdom, will ya?
[sighs] Why not? I love wisdom. Bring it.
Life is like a river.
Ugh! Oh, great.
That's exactly what I was afraid of.
[laughing]
You can't see too far ahead.
I can't see at all,
as I might have mentioned before.
You mentioned!
You don't know where the river of life
will bend and turn.
You don't know where it will go at all.
How is that supposed to be helpful?
Don't try to control where the river goes.
There's one thing
you can know and control,
yourself.
Look at yourself. Who are you, Rayla?
What do you stand for?
Once you know that,
then wherever the river takes you,
you'll be right where
you were always meant to be.
Villads, that's amazing.
When you started talking,
I was sure you were going to spout
some complete nonsense,
but what you said, it's beautiful.
[Villads snoring]
[Berto squawks] I'll tell him later.
[roaring]
We'll never make it.
We have to hold off the dragon
as long as possible
so those carrying the heart
can make it back.
Stop!
This is our day to sacrifice.
You get the titan's heart to safety.
Save all our people.
Come on.
[roaring]
[yelling]
I can help!
[roaring]
[roars]
Aspiro frigis!
[roaring]
For Aanya!
[both screaming]
They've bought us enough time.
We've made it!
[horse neighing]
- What is it?
- Viren...
Without him to perform the spell,
the heart is worthless,
and this was all for nothing.
Sarai, what are you saying?
I'll see you on the other side.
[Harrow] The last time I saw your mother,
she said, "I will see you
on the other side."
I don't know what lies on the other side.
But I do know I will be watching over
you and your brother always.
[Thunder roaring]
[roaring]
[grunts]
- Thank you.
- [grunts] Don't thank me yet.
[roaring]
Yah! Yah!
[coughing]
[gasps]
Come on. We have to run.
[gasping weakly]
[Viren] I was there when Queen Sarai
took her last breath.
[Sarai exhales heavily]
[Sarai groans]
[Viren] We returned home.
Xadia had stolen
precious loved ones from us.
Their loss changed our lives forever...
but their sacrifice changed the world.
The heart of the titan
yielded its incredible life force.
The spell worked.
It created fertility and abundance.
A hundred thousand lives were saved.
Families celebrated their life and health.
They were safe, alive, together.
The people of both of our kingdoms
knew who they owed their lives to.
These incredible heroes.
Three queens, three mothers...
became legends.
It should have been me.
I'm so sorry.
[female guard] Your Highness.
He's waiting for you now.
[sighs] Okay.
[male guard] Are you ready?
No, but you may open the doors.
[door opens]
[sighs]
Callum, I want to talk to you about life.
And growing up.
And how sometimes there are changes
you don't expect.
[door closes]
[Harrow] I've tried to be
selfless as a king,
but as a father, I have a selfish wish.
And that is for you and Ezran to be...
free.
Reject the chains of history.
Do not let the past
define your future, as I did.
Free yourself from the past.
Learn from it, understand it,
then let it go.
Create a brighter future
from your own hearts and imagination.
[Viren] I'm sorry you were never
able to know them.
Your mothers.
Thank you for sharing this story,
Lord Viren.
I feel lucky to have heard
so many beautiful stories.
This is how I've gotten to know them.
They were very brave,
and very strong, and wise.
I know it is not my place to say,
but I am sure they would have been
very proud of you.
It may seem strange to miss someone
I've never known,
but I miss them so much.
Queen Aanya, knowing what you know now,
can you see why I believe
that if your mothers were here today,
they would choose to join us
and fight by our side?
I think you are right.
Perhaps they would.
But I... will not.
What?
We owe Katolis a great debt,
there is no doubt.
We received so much kindness
and courage and sacrifice.
But I cannot repay a debt
of a hundred thousand
whose lives were saved
by sending a million men
and women to die in violence.
Did you not listen? Did you not...
King Ahling!
Help me talk some sense into her.
Viren, we sympathize
with the plight of Katolis,
but I'm afraid we can no longer...
Coward!
Traitors.
Each of you standing here today,
you betray humanity!
Lord Viren, I'm sorry.
Save your empty apology.
There is danger coming.
They'll be on your side
of the border soon.
You'll all pay the price
for ignoring my warnings.
[Harrow] And, finally,
you must be wondering
about the secret I promised to share.
Well, good news.
The secret is hidden
in the Banther Lodge,
right where you are right now.
How's that for planning?
Huh. Good thing we're at
the Banther Lodge, huh, Bait?
[croaks]
[Harrow] Right now, go upstairs
to the game room.
There, I have hidden an unusual cube
with rune symbols on each side.
[exclaims]
[Harrow] This cube is an ancient relic
that has been passed down
through the ages.
It belonged to an elven wizard in Xadia,
the Archmage Aaravos,
a master of all six primal sources.
It is hidden in a box of keys
because it is known
as the "Key of Aaravos,"
and legends say it unlocks something
of great power in Xadia.
Perhaps it will be you, Callum,
who discovers the key's secrets.
[croaks]
[Harrow] And one last
extra-super-secret bonus secret.
Did you know that Bait,
our most sour friend,
secretly loves belly rubs?
[snorting]
- Aww! Who's a tubby lumpa grump?
- [purring]
You probably thought
I was just a crazy old sea captain,
but I've got some good wisdom.
I'll admit it.
You do have some good wisdom.
You want to know the other secret to life?
Waterproof socks!
It's a metaphor.
Think about it.
You just showed me the socks.
That's not what a metaphor is.
[both yawning]
[yelps]
What's that for?
You're my brother,
and you mean everything to me.
Is this a trick?
[chuckles] No. I just love you.
- Well, I love you, too.
- [yips]
So are we there yet? Are we close?
[sniffs] We are close.
- I smell land!
- [caws]
Hey, what was that? A shadow?
Eh, you're asking the wrong pirate.
[Rayla] There's something up there.