Ba-bum.
[croaks]
[panting]
[chirping]
[Aaravos] Long ago, Xadia was one land...
rich in magic and wonder.
[Sol Regem growls]
[sniffs]
I smell death.
Is that why you summoned me here?
So you could insult me?
You and all your followers must give up
Dark Magic, immediately and forever.
It is humanity's only path forward.
It's a path backward.
You just expect humans to go back
to the way things were
before we had magic?
When humans starved and struggled,
helpless and pathetic?
Back to a time when we were lesser beings?
You are lesser beings.
You are arrogant!
Hmm. Lay down your staff and walk away.
Lay it down? But it was a gift.
That would be rude.
- A gift?
- Of course.
You didn't think
that a lesser being like myself
would be able to craft
such a powerful relic?
Who gave you the staff?
- [angrily] Who?
- One of the great ones.
[roars]
You... You promised my safety
if I came here!
Yes, you will be
safe high upon this peak...
far, far away from the city of Elarion.
You can't be saying... an entire city?
Hundreds of thousands of innocent people!
Children!
Give up Dark Magic
or I will reduce it to ash!
You wouldn't.
[huffs]
[screams] No!
[yelling]
[roaring]
[roars]
[grunts]
[theme music playing]
[Sol Regem growls softly]
[Rayla] That's no ordinary dragon.
[Callum] Is there such a thing
as an ordinary dragon?
His name is Sol Regem, the Sun King.
He was the king of the dragons
a long time ago.
But he was blinded when the wars began,
and he's become a symbol of rage
and bitterness.
[Callum] Okay, so, an enormous,
angry, blind dragon
is blocking our path to Xadia.
What do we do?
[chuckles] Well, we can't fight him,
seeing as you've just got
your cute blow spell,
and my swords aren't fit to be
his toothpicks.
[gasps] We'll have to sneak past him!
Callum, it's time for you
to get your first lesson
- in the ways of stealth.
- Nice!
I... I mean...
[quietly] Nice.
The secret of stealth
is that you don't have to be invisible.
You just have to be invisible
to your enemy's senses.
Well, he's blind, so we don't need
to worry about his sense of sight.
Exactly. That leaves only two senses
we need to fool, hearing and smell.
Wait, why are those the only two senses
we need to worry about?
Well, if it gets to his sense of touch,
we're in big trouble.
And sense of taste?
- [roars]
- [Rayla] Nice knowing you.
Got it.
All this stuff about senses
and appearances,
it kind of sounds like Moon Arcanum stuff.
- If you say so, mage.
- [Zym chirps]
[soldier] General Amaya,
we're running out of time.
I strongly recommend we gather
the battalion and abandon the fortress.
General!
General, the Sunfire elves
have already taken over the outpost
on the Xadian side of the Breach.
If the elves mount an attack,
we simply don't have the numbers
to hold this fortress.
When the elves mount an attack.
General Amaya, I'm sorry to interrupt,
but someone has arrived.
[roars]
[whimpers]
- [Zym whining]
- Come on, Callum, try to keep him quiet.
I know, it's just... [sighs]
Ez would know how to calm you down,
wouldn't he?
We just need to trust each other, okay?
- I've got you.
- [whimpers]
[Sol Regem growling softly]
[both sigh]
[Zym whimpers]
[whines]
[birds screeching]
- [whines loudly]
- [Callum exclaims]
[Sol Regem growls]
[yelps]
- [rock clatters]
- [Sol Regem grunts]
[whimpering]
[roars]
[roaring]
[Callum screams]
What now? [panting]
[Gren laughs and grunts]
[laughs]
I'm sorry to interrupt,
but where are the reinforcements
we requested?
We sent many messages to Lord Viren.
No reinforcements are coming.
Lord Viren has been arrested for treason.
"Lieutenant, you're right.
We can't defend the Breach.
But I won't abandon it.
Our only choice is to destroy it."
[growls]
- [Callum] Do we run for it?
- We'll never make it.
He'll just bite us in half
or slam us with his tail.
So, sneaking is out, running is out,
fighting is out. What's left?
- Burning to death?
- Definitely out.
[growls]
[sighs]
Looks like it's down to my least favorite
course of action. [sighs]
- Reason.
- [Callum groans]
Mighty Sol Regem,
I am Rayla of the Moonshadow elves.
[sniffs]
- [Sol Regem] What are you doing?
- Uh...
- I am bowing, great dragon.
- No.
I mean, why are you here?
We have been traveling
in the human kingdoms
on the business of Zubeia,
the Dragon Queen.
We humbly ask your permission
to cross back into Xadia.
What kind of business would send you
to the wretched human lands?
We are transporting something precious,
someone precious.
The new-born Dragon Prince, Azymondias!
Lies! You dare lie to me?
- The egg of the Dragon King was destroyed!
- [Zym whimpers]
No! Wait! I have him here.
[Zym whining loudly]
The Dragon Prince lives!
And he's very cute, isn't he?
- There's a good boy!
- [chirps]
[sniffs]
- How is this possible?
- It is a miracle.
He needs to go back to his home.
Please, allow us to pass,
so we can reunite the Dragon Prince
with his mother.
I do not understand how the Dragon Prince
came to be in the human lands.
However, I will allow you
and the dragonling to pass
back into Xadia.
But not the filthy human
who cowers nearby.
- [Callum sighs]
- [Rayla] Sol Regem...
- [Callum] It's okay. You go on without me.
- No! Callum, we're so close.
Rayla, getting Zym to Xadia
is all that matters.
Just tell the Dragon Queen
I helped a little. I'll go back home.
[Sol Regem chuckling]
Home? No.
There are two choices.
You all die,
or just the wretched, evil human dies.
[Zym whimpers]
I agree with you, Sol Regem.
Some humans are evil.
- Uh, Rayla...
- But not this one. Not Callum.
The only reason the Dragon Prince is alive
is because of this human.
He left his home and his family
to save the egg,
and he sacrificed everything
so Azymondias could be born.
He's noble and true.
When we met,
he could have had me captured or killed.
But he didn't, because without knowing me
or anything about me,
he saw past human hatred
and did what he knew was right.
He's smart and kind and brave, and he's...
my friend.
My best friend.
So, please, allow him to pass into Xadia
and help me take the Dragon Prince home.
Because I don't think
I can do it without him.
[sniffs]
I smell death!
What? No, Callum is different.
I smell the reek of Dark Magic on him.
He's no different.
He rips the life
and magic out of innocent creatures.
He must die.
The cable.
"It's done. Let's go."
[soldier] On your command, we'll pull
the cable and detonate the barrels.
"And a thousand tons of rock
and lava will seal the Breach forever."
[roars]
I'm sorry, Rayla.
But if me dying is the only way for you
and Zym to get across safely,
- then it's time for me to face the end.
- Calm down.
He can't use his fire breath yet.
He can only do it every few minutes.
He needs time to recharge.
Wait. We can't hide from his senses,
but maybe we can trick them.
Create a false appearance.
After all, we can only truly know
the appearance itself.
- Now you're sounding like Lujanne.
- Wow, really?
- That wasn't a compliment.
- Here's the idea.
I could use Aspiro to blow my scent
to a different place.
Like... like ventriloquism,
but with smells!
- Smelltriloquism!
- Uh...
- Vensmelloquism.
- It's a stupid idea.
But there might be something to it.
Time is up!
Give me your scarf!
If I wear it, I'll smell like you,
and I'll draw his fire.
Once he uses his blast, you and Zym
make a run for it while I keep him busy.
This is the worst idea you've ever had.
He's gonna burn you to a crisp.
- [Sol Regem roars]
- No, he won't. I'm faster than him.
And besides,
it's the only chance we've got.
I haven't bathed in two weeks.
This should do the trick.
[sniffs]
[gags and coughs]
Right?
Here goes nothing.
[roars]
We're ready to detonate
the explosives on your command.
Pull!
Now what? The trigger's been disabled.
[horse whinnies]
"Someone has to go out there
and set them off.
I... I'll do it myself."
But, Amaya, you won't survive.
- What did she say?
- She said the rest of us will.
[roars]
- [Sol Regem roaring]
- [panting]
Come on, Rayla, come on!
Foolish human!
[roars]
[panting]
[sighs]
[horse whinnying]
[whinnying]
[grunting]
[yelling]
[roars]
That arch. What if...
[whispers] Throw it!
He wants me to... throw up on the dragon?
[roars]
Oh, throw it!
Aspiro! [blows sharply]
[roars]
That was amazing!
Too close, but amazing.
Relax, I'm only slightly singed.
- Good thinking with Aspiro.
- [Sol Regem roars]
That arch isn't going to hold him forever.
Let's get out of here
before "too close" becomes "too late."
Thanks for letting me borrow this.
I think it's good luck.
[Sol Regem roars]
[Zym chirps]
[Aaravos] Do not despair. Be patient.
Your time will come.
You have put things in motion.
[Opeli] He is too dangerous.
There aren't enough locks and chains
in the Five Kingdoms
to contain the threat he poses.
Then, what are you suggesting?
There's only one way to neutralize Viren.
And that's to do it...
permanently.
[thudding at door]
[thudding continues]
What is the meaning of...
[growls softly]
King Ezran!
[growls]
[inhales and exhales deeply]
[Bait exclaims]