Ba-bum.
[croaks]
[panting]
[Janai] Previously on The Dragon Prince...
We'll let the Light decide her fate.
[panting]
A human with a pure heart.
How original.
But, Rayla, you need to know
the Dragon Queen is dying.
- We have to get to her.
- If she knows her little one still lives,
perhaps she'll hold on.
[Nyx] The dragon's lair
is only about a day's journey.
They call it the Storm Spire.
Xadia hates us.
They hate humanity.
[grunts]
[Viren] And they would destroy us
if we let them.
But we will fight back!
[theme music playing]
[roaring]
[critters chirping]
Aw, you're so cute.
Just too cute!
Hey, wait up!
[Viren whispering]
[horse whinnies]
- Hey, Dad?
- Soren.
I just have one question.
Now that we're in Xadia...
or should I say, New Katolis?
Or East Katolis?
Or Katol-east?
[sighs] Get on with it, son.
What's the plan?
You do not need to concern yourself
with the plan.
I mean, you do have a plan, right?
My plan will be revealed
at the appropriate time.
I am a Crown Guard.
Shouldn't the leaders know
what's going on?
Enough, Soren!
[sighs] If you want to lead,
you need to learn how to follow.
And if you want to learn to follow,
you need to learn how to shut your mouth.
Perhaps you could look to Prince Kasef
for an example.
[Soren] You think you're so great,
with your quietness, rugged battle stance,
and your horse with kind eyes!
[horse snorts and whinnies]
- So, what is the plan?
- To fulfill your wishes, of course.
- Is your wish to rule Xadia?
- I wish for humanity to flourish.
And it cannot flourish
with a knife forever at its throat.
So, you wish to conquer Xadia?
No!
No, my goal is a bright future
for humanity.
Right.
And this bright future will require us
to conquer Xadia?
[Viren sighs]
Yes. Yes, perhaps.
The key to achieving your noble aims
for humanity is simple.
It's the same as it has always been.
The key is the Dragon Prince.
Yes.
You must take down the Dragon Queen
and capture the baby dragon.
Then you will have the attention
of all the world,
and the power to do what you want.
But first, there is
something we need here in Lux Aurea.
You want us to attack the stronghold
of the Sunfire elves?
But we need to preserve our forces
for the final confrontation.
Viren, I'm nothing if not elegant
and efficient.
We'll risk as few lives as possible...
one.
Ah, mine.
Yes.
[Zym chirps]
[Callum] So, this is it. The Storm Spire.
[Rayla] Yup.
[Callum] And I take it
the Dragon Queen didn't make her lair
at a nice kinda halfway-up there
kind of place?
Nope. Tip-top!
- [Zym whimpers]
- [Ezran] Aw, Zym. Don't worry.
- You're about to meet your mama!
- [Zym chirps]
Your radiance, another human has come
to Lux Aurea.
He requests an audience.
You see, sister?
You bring one human,
and the next thing you know,
we are overrun with them.
Throw him in a cell.
But this human is the King of Katolis!
Oh?
Then put him
in the extra-nice ring of fire.
Sister, this human claims he knows
what happened to Queen Aditi.
What does he know about our grandmother?
So, uh, when we get up there,
are we gonna tell
the Dragon Queen we're... a thing?
Uh, I don't think it's gonna come up.
Oh, I see.
You're saying we should hide it from her.
Kind of a secret,
forbidden-romance situation?
Yes. Yes, that's right.
The Dragon Queen must never know!
I understand.
The world just isn't ready
for what we have.
[Callum chuckles]
This is elven writing.
Can you read it?
It says...
"Prepare to draw your last breath."
What do you know of my grandmother?
Allow my people safe passage
through Xadia,
and you will know the truth.
[chuckles] Your people?
Do you bring farmers and poets,
or do you bring an army?
Humans bring nothing but trouble,
and you are like all the rest.
If you allow us to pass,
we have no trouble with you.
Hmm. We will see if we can trust you.
The Light will decide!
Look into the Light!
[groaning]
[straining]
Ahh!
Your true form is revealed.
Ugly and evil. I am not surprised.
[panting]
But don't give up hope,
you will be purified.
You know, I think this interrogation
is going very well.
You're not dead.
Bad news, my human friend.
Your king came seeking passage.
[interpreter] What? That's impossible.
[Janai] The Light
revealed his true nature.
Tainted with darkness, rotten to the core.
[scoffs] Such an arrogant man.
[interpreter] That man is no king.
He may be the most dangerous human
in the world.
No matter.
The queen sentenced him to be purified.
After the ritual, I doubt there
will be anything left of him.
[interpreter] You don't understand.
If he's here, everyone is in danger.
We have to stop him!
[yips]
[panting] How tall is this thing?
[panting] Maybe we should just rest here
for a second.
[both panting]
Guys, we can't stop here.
We have to keep going.
[Sunfire Queen] There is nothing
to be afraid of.
The light from the Sun Forge
is one of purification.
It will only remove the parts of you
that have been touched by Dark Magic.
[gasps]
[exclaims]
The ritual has started!
[interpreter] We have to stop him!
Ugh! Humans disgust me.
Your kind could not be satisfied
with what you were given.
So you take what is not yours.
You take it within you,
and you turn it to filth.
[exhales sharply]
[screeching]
[grunts]
[gasps]
Your arrogance is so predictable.
[yelling]
You allowed my vessel
to walk right into your court,
and then you brought him
directly to the source of all your power?
[laughs]
Oh, the irony is wonderful!
You're just like your grandmother.
Would you like
to know the truth of her fate...
before you face yours?
[whispering indistinctly]
[screaming]
[shrieking] No!
[shouts]
[grunts]
[sobbing] No!
[all panting]
[panting] The air's so thin.
I can barely breathe.
Thanks.
[sighs] It's too much.
Zym, we can't leave them here.
I don't know if I can keep going.
Zym!
[grunts]
[slurping]
[chirping]
Zym, how long was I out?
[yips]
[growling]
Hey!
I've met you before, when you crashed.
You're okay now!
[panting]
I understand!
[yips]
[Claudia gasps]
[Soren] Dad?
I have been granted a great gift.
The power we need to defeat Xadia
and save humanity is now ours!
We must evolve.
When we strike against the Dragon Queen,
we will face elves and dragons,
and they will rain fire upon us.
[all exclaim]
But with this gift, I will inoculate you.
And instead of destruction,
that fire will be our nourishment!
Now, come forth.
[all murmuring]
Do not be afraid.
You will understand when you see the first
to change...
my own beloved son, Soren.
Step forward, my son.
Let me help you.
I don't wanna do this.
Step forward.
I... I'm afraid.
[Kasef] I am ready!
I am ready to receive the gift!
[all gasping]
[chanting]
[chanting continues]
[roaring]
[breathing heavily]
[roars]
Guys! Wake up! You gotta wake up!
I know how to fix everything.
The gateway wasn't a warning.
It was the solution!
What? What are you talking about?
To make it all the way up,
you have to draw your last breath.
[panting] It's a rune, Callum!
And the trigger words are Ventus Spiralis.
How do you know all this?
I met an old friend.
[sighs]
[panting]
Ventus Spiralis!
[inhales deeply]
[Bait groans]
Rayla, wake up! Come on!
[coughing]
We're gonna be okay!
Hey, that isn't part of the spell.
Uh, yeah! So, uh...
you were gone for a while,
and now, uh, this is a thing, so...
[Ezran] What?
Wha...
Soren. What's going on?
Where are you going?
I can't stay here anymore, Claudia.
You've seen what's going on.
What Dad turned Kasef into.
What Dad turned into.
Maybe he's just doing
what needs to be done.
Claudia, you're changing, too.
But it's not too late.
Come with me, Claudia. You can leave him!
Please, Soren, don't...
don't do this to me.
Don't make me choose. Not again!
Okay.
Good bye, Clauds.
No!
No! No, no, no!
Now, it is time for all of you
to embrace this power!
[roars]
[chanting loudly]
[chanting continues]
[growling]
[gasps]
We're here.
I can't believe we've made it!
We've brought him home.
Azymondias, the Dragon Prince!
He's here to see his mother.
It makes my heart leap
to see that he lives.
But you're too late.